Three, two, one!
-Cheese!
ADAPTED FROM ZHU YI'S NOVEL,
SHE'S A LITTLE CRAZY, ON JJWXC.NET
-Kiss!
A Fluttering Feeling I Can't Ignore.
GRADE 10, CLASS 1
That's all for this class.
I would like to make an announcement.
During today's last two classes,
we've invited a psychology lecturer
from Jiangyi University
to give a psychology seminar
at our school.
Students who feel like they need it
may attend.
It's not compulsory.
Students who aren't attending
will self-study in the classroom.
Keep quiet. Understand?
-Yes!
Class is dismissed.
Will you two
attend the psychology seminar?
No.
It sounds like a dry lecture
with a bunch of unintelligible theories.
How boring.
Jiang Jia said she saved us seats.
-I'll tell her to save two only.
-Hold on!
Jiang Jia?
Are they going too?
They're already there.
I think
life has been pretty stressful lately.
There's no harm in attending it, right?
Let's go.
That is why communication is so important.
Good and effective communication
is often the key to solving problems.
THE FIRST HIGH SCHOOL
SPECIAL SEMINAR ON PSYCHOLOGY
I noticed
that some students were nodding off.
Why?
Did you think what I said earlier
was boring?
Then let's talk
about something more interesting.
What is considered interesting?
You usually listen to music, right?
Who do you like listening to?
-Of course.
-Jay Chou!
You have a pretty good taste.
THE FIRST HIGH SCHOOL
SPECIAL SEMINAR ON PSYCHOLOGY
I remember Jay Chou had a song
called "Her Eyelashes."
When I was in high school,
the song was often played
during the lunch break.
I liked memorizing vocabulary
at lunchtime,
while my deskmate
liked napping on the table.
Whenever I closed my textbook
to memorize the words,
I always saw her long eyelashes
in the corner of my eye.
But later on, I gave up
memorizing vocabulary at lunchtime
because it was so ineffective.
I wasn't sure if it was that song
that affected me
or something else.
That was until I learned a certain word.
"Fluttering."
I wonder if you have ever felt this way.
When someone becomes special to you,
you just can't seem
to keep your eyes off them.
That's so accurate.
Even a simple smile
or sudden eye contact
will be caught by someone who cares.
They will remain excited for a long time.
Some of you here
must've had similar experiences.
The feeling is both confusing
and novel.
In fact,
these are all normal parts of adolescence.
I don't think he was right at all.
"We become sneaky
when we like someone"?
I don't think so.
He said "careful," not "sneaky."
That's more or less the same.
Anyway, if I like someone,
I would show it openly
and let everyone know about it.
How about you, Lurang?
I think you would be the sneaky type.
Figure yourself out first.
How rare!
You're not buying snacks.
Jiangjiang spent a fortune yesterday
on a beautiful glass jar,
so she has used up all her money.
It's all right.
You can eat mine.
Why did you buy a glass jar?
It's a secret.
That's right.
I just got my contest prize money.
Take your pick. It's on me.
Thank you.
Don't grab too much.
You're a hearty eater.
Gu Ran, you're awesome.
I'll help myself then.
Rangrang, these are delicious. Take them.
Do you know what will appear on your face
after eating too much junk food?
A smile?
You're exceptionally handsome today.
You're handsome.
Shall we?
Let's go.
Doesn't he seem a bit too happy today?
Look at that girl.
She's quite pretty.
I also think her hair clip is pretty.
Jiang Jia has an identical one.
It's pink.
I think it looks cuter
on Jiang Jia though.
I mean,
Jiang Jia has a bigger face,
so it suits her better.
That's all.
Let's go.
It's a beautiful sunny day.
Do you know?
He had just bit it
and the teacher called him.
So he spat it all out into his hands.
Su Zaizai.
Where's Jiang Jia?
She went to see Qianyu.
She has something important to do.
I just remembered that
I forgot my homework. I'll go get it.
You guys go ahead. Don't wait for me.
There should be no one around
at this hour, right?
Which one
is Qianyu's seat?
"Li Cheng."
"Huang Ming."
"Wang Zhi."
Found it.
What are you doing in our classroom?
I...
Sorry, I just came to drop something off.
Gu Ran,
how could you scare people
at night like that?
I was about to say that to you.
How could you secretly sneak
into another class
at night like that?
I didn't.
Jiang Jia, are you dumb?
If you don't leave your name on the gift,
how will the receiver know who sent it?
That doesn't matter to me
as long as they receive the gift.
You're such a coward at times.
You don't have a crush.
You wouldn't understand.
Whatever.
Why wouldn't I understand?
Are you sure
your keys are in the classroom?
-Someone is coming.
-I'm sure.
I found them.
Luckily, you didn't lose them outside.
Let's go.
Thank goodness. We weren't seen.
What are you staring at?
Are you stunned?
Nonsense.
I didn't even want to hide.
We weren't doing anything bad.
Then why are you blushing?
I'm not.
It got scratched.
It was all your fault.
You just had to hide.
Have you forgotten about the time
Zaizai was accused of stealing money?
I don't want to cause misunderstandings.
Still,
wouldn't the consequences be worse
if we both got caught hiding?
Why?
The school has been
cracking down on puppy love.
Who would be so unkind to themselves
as to be involved with you?
You're so clumsy.
THE FIRST HIGH SCHOOL
ACADEMIC TRANSCRIPT REQUEST FORM
"Needed for going abroad."
Is Qianyu
going abroad?
That's all for today's class.
A round of applause, please.
All right. Thank you for the support!
Thank you
for giving me your attention.
This session
was mainly about the eyes.
It's not something you can learn
in a day or two.
So make sure
to practice it more at home.
One day, your eyes will be like mine,
bright
and piercing.
By the way,
your senior schoolmate, Shen Qianyu,
will be leaving the country soon.
He has about a week left.
You all should cherish your time with him.
So then...
Is Qianyu going abroad?
That's right.
-He...
-It's because of my parents' job transfer.
I had no choice.
Yes, I think...
Does the countdown start today?
Hold on. You guys keep interrupting me.
I seem to be the extra in this class.
You guys have a chat and catch up.
Though I haven't known you for very long,
I'm still grateful to all of you
for joining the Drama Club.
I hope I'll have the chance to see you
on a bigger stage in the future.
Keep it up.
Did you find out about it yesterday?
Yes.
When I went to drop off the stars,
I accidentally saw the documents
he had prepared for his departure.
Why is it so sudden?
Zaizai, I've made up my mind.
About what?
I didn't give him the stars in person
because I thought
we had a lot of time left
and could slowly get to know each other.
But there is no time now.
I don't want to have any regrets.
So what do you plan to do?
Did you know
that we will meet 29,2 million people
in our lifetime?
When I think about it,
meeting you at the age of 16
should be one
of my life's few lucky moments.
The first time I saw you,
you were sitting on the grass
and playing the guitar.
There were so many people around,
but I saw you right away.
"I couldn't help
but start to get close to you.
I asked around for your grade and class
and learned about your preferences.
I admit that I'm not a persistent person.
But after meeting you,
I've found a new meaning to persistence."
What do you think?
I'm not done writing it yet.
I think it's pretty good.
I've never written a love letter though.
I'm not sure if this is how it is written.
You're so good at writing essays,
so you should be fine.
Really?
Yes. Also, look.
Over here.
Su Zaizai,
Jiang Jia,
have you turned in your math homework yet?
Are you guys
copying homework?
You're right!
We just have one question left.
We're done. Here you go.
Wang Nan's footsteps don't make a sound.
Luckily, he didn't see it.
It's okay. You didn't write your name.
That's true.
Zaizai, is the letter with you?
I think I stuck it in my homework.
Where is my homework?
I just turned it in.
There are so many people.
We're done for.
It's okay.
Mr. Lin is a serious procrastinator.
He probably won't
grade our homework so soon.
Let's come back at lunch break.
All right.
Zhang Lurang,
I heard that Class 9's math papers
were mixed up with ours.
Ms. Zhang sent me to help you sort them.
It's fine. I'm almost done.
It's okay. Let me help you.
Su Zaizai got so many questions wrong.
She got almost all the main questions
at the back wrong.
If it were you,
I don't think you would want random people
looking through your papers.
I was just stating facts.
She was never good at math.
She wasn't even in our grade's top 100
in the last midterm exam.
Excluding science scores,
she would be in our school's top 20.
Even including those scores,
I can be in the top 20.
Why can't I talk about her bad results?
MATH BOOK, SU ZAIZAI
She makes so many mistakes
even in her regular homework.
What is this?
"The first time I saw you,
you were sitting on the grass
and playing the guitar.
There were so many people around,
but I saw you right away."
Su Zaizai is writing a love letter
to someone.
Do you know this guitar player?
This is her privacy.
You only said that
because it belongs to Su Zaizai.
You can leave if you don't want to help.
MATH BOOK, SU ZAIZAI
Rangrang.
You're here as well.
The first one over here.
Rangrang,
did you see something?
No.
Your name is written so big
that it's unforgettable.
They're planning
to switch to a new student club
even before Qianyu leaves.
What do you mean?
Isn't that guy from the Guitar Club?
Is that so?
Su Zaizai is writing a love letter
to someone.
Do you know this guitar player?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You can ask me directly
if you have questions about guitars.
It's a good thing we asked him.
Otherwise, it would be so embarrassing
if Qianyu saw the absurd music theories
that I wrote in the letter.
Zhang Lurang!
Are Guan Fang and I invisible?
You've gained some self-awareness.
What were you two talking about over here?
You looked so excited.
It's a secret.
By the way,
we'll have a fitness test in this class.
The boys will be doing pull-ups.
How many can you do, Rangrang?
It's a secret.
Are you two the only ones left?
It's your turn. I'll hold your ankles.
Get ready.
Sir,
Mr. Xu sent me to ask you for the key
to the basketball equipment room.
Has Class 1 finished the fitness test?
The key.
I think I left it in the office.
I'll go and get it.
Sure.
You can record your own scores.
Okay.
I think you're more reliable.
You don't seem likely to cheat.
Record their scores for me.
Okay.
Ready.
Start.
Thirty seconds left.
Twenty-two.
Twenty-one.
It's 22.
Non-standard sit-ups don't count.
Time is up.
You guys did 36, right?
Thirty.
You did 26.
You just passed the test.
Rangrang,
you're truly stern and impartial.
Rangrang, are you having a bad day?
No.
Are you still denying it?
You touched your neck.
Rangrang,
did you see something?
No.
Your name is written so big
that it's unforgettable.
You didn't see
what I put
in my homework, did you?
Could it be that you thought
I wrote that for someone else
and got jealous?
No.
I have to lecture you about this.
You couldn't even recognize my handwriting
after all the tutoring classes we've had.
This is so heartbreaking.
As a punishment,
you should read my notes carefully again.
You'll have to remember it this time.
As for making me suffer in PE class,
I'll forgive you.
Lurang,
I warmed up some milk
and made some for you too.
Thank you, Uncle.
What happened to make you so happy?
I...
SU ZAIZAI'S EXCLUSIVE SECRET
All right. Go to bed early.
Remember to drink the milk.
Okay.
Qianyu?
What brings you to the Grade 10 area?
I need to go
to the Office of Academic Affairs.
Are you leaving very soon?
I'm leaving in about two weeks.
Two weeks. That's so soon.
I have one more recital
before I go abroad.
If you have time,
you can come and watch it.
Consider it a farewell.
ADMISSION TICKET
Qianyu only gave me this ticket.
Does this mean
that I'm special?
ADMISSION TICKET
Two days ago, you were so upset
about Qianyu leaving the country.
Why are you in such a good mood today?
You're over the moon.
Did you win the lottery?
You can say that.
It's a good thing anyway.
Why do you all
have good things going on recently?
Lurang is also in a good mood today
for some reason.
So what's up? You haven't told us yet.
Don't envy me
after I tell you guys about it.
Qianyu invited me to his recital
next Friday night.
So?
So
I won't be joining you guys that day.
I'm letting you know in advance.
Why won't you be joining us?
We're going as well.
Qianyu was at the basketball court
during lunch.
He told us about it.
He even invited all of us.
So I wasn't the only one.
What's wrong with her now?
Her special prize became a pity award.
Why do you have tutoring
with Zhang Lurang on the weekend?
The monthly exam is coming up.
You know how poorly I scored
on the last math exam.
Who will go shoe shopping with me then?
He Yu and Fu Yao are both busy.
Why don't you ask Guan Fang?
A guy might provide a different insight.
You have a point.
Then I'll ask him.
Hello, Guan Fang? Are you free tomorrow?
Grocery shopping with your grandma?
Never mind then. Bye.
Who else can I ask?
Do you have any other plans?
You're all dressed up
as if you're meeting someone important.
What? That's nonsense!
Don't put it like that.
This is how I usually dress.
Don't flatter yourself.
I didn't say it was me.
Let's get going. It's getting late.
How could you not
show appreciation
for what you've been given?
I freed up my busy schedule
to go shopping with you,
but you don't have any gratitude.
But then again,
am I the only one here today?
Yes, it's just you.
You have a good taste
for choosing me.
This had nothing to do with my taste.
I asked everyone else.
You're the only one free.
-I...
-Wait, no.
My elderly neighbor was free as well,
but I was worried
his fashion sense would be outdated.
So on second thought, I went with you.
At least you're a boy.
Your tastes should differ
from that of a girl.
What did you mean by "at least"?
How pretty.
Try them on if you find them pretty.
Forget it.
I'm not here to buy these today.
Excuse me. I would like to try these on.
That was close.
You've clearly never worn heels before.
Why did you still buy them?
I'm a size 37.
These are size 37 shoes.
They should fit me.
Besides,
I'm already walking
much more steadily, okay?
But didn't you like
that pair of sneakers a lot?
We have to make choices
about a lot of things.
We can't have it all.
Are you doing this for Qianyu's recital?
Why are you asking the obvious?
If you were Qianyu,
what would you think of me?
How would I know?
True.
You'll never be him.
Still, thank you
for shopping with me for so long today.
Nobody has been so patient
with me for a long time.
I'm very happy.
Let me get that.
Thank you.
Traces of the youthful thoughts that year
seemed to have been exposed
along with the early summer.
Sorry. Please excuse me.
Then they put on a not-so-clever disguise.
He created a safe area with his arms,
but blamed the heat
for his sweaty palms.
And only one of the two parties knew
that the seemingly coincidental encounter
was actually a calculation
more sophisticated than a math problem.
The gifts
they mustered the courage to give
were cloaked in mischief.
They chose
to silently say in their hearts,
"I want you to be happy."
However, love would always
quietly slip out
in every glance at him
and secretly written
into a diary under a desk lamp.
These trivial and scrupulous moments
are like the candy
a child hides in their pocket.
If we unwrap the candy
and sniff it during the night,
the next day would seem
a little more worth anticipating.
Let's all relax
after such a long class.
Let's play a game of imitation.
We shall start with Guan Fang.
Each of you will imitate an animal.
Begin.
Hurry up.
Rangrang is cuter
than a kitty in every way.
No, to me,
he is even cuter than cute.