Three, two, one!
-Cheese!
ADAPTED FROM ZHU YI'S NOVEL,
SHE'S A LITTLE CRAZY, ON JJWXC.NET
-Kiss!
Today's Jiangyi News FM 96,7...
Thank you, ma'am.
-Put it there when you're done.
-...is almost over.
Okay.
It has been raining for days.
Listeners, take your rain gear
when you go out
to avoid catching a cold.
More great content will come tomorrow
at the same time.
Why doesn't he run?
Why is he walking in the rain?
Idiot.
Ma'am, two bottles of cola.
Thank you.
Lost Rainy Days,
I Long to Be Soaked Once More.
Good morning,
this is Jiangyi News FM 96,7.
Today is the first day of school.
Listeners, are you ready
to embrace this new journey
with a new look?
Here's a little tip.
The most special memories in life
will start right now.
Every decision determines the way
that you will go.
It's mysterious and unknown,
isn't it?
Well, this is just a little suspense.
New friends, new challenges,
and new stories.
When you're expecting them,
they're also expecting you.
Now, be on your way.
Susu.
Handshake.
The other one.
Good dog.
You're up.
Yes. Good morning, Uncle.
I had to get up this early.
At five o'clock this morning,
the dog ran into my room,
demanding to go outside.
But when we got out,
there were no other dogs,
so we hurried back.
Naughty dog.
Zaizai.
My mom prepared this for you.
You have dark circles.
What's going on?
I browsed posts about our new school
until morning.
What's the point of doing that?
Of course,
it's to learn about our new school.
Let's hurry or we will be late.
CHENYANG NEIGHBORHOOD
I heard
there are several brilliant freshmen.
But I don't know if it's true.
Anyway, I found out
about the two most famous guys.
One is Zhang Lurang.
And the other is Gu Ran.
Why are they so famous?
They have really good grades.
Many students in our school
have good grades too.
So they must be special somehow.
Zaizai, hurry. We're going to be late.
Stop dawdling. Just tell me.
What is your name?
Which class are you in?
I'm asking you.
Su Zaizai, Grade 10, Class 9.
Jiang Jia. I'm in the same class.
Hey, you!
Come over.
You, come over!
JIANGYI UNIVERSITY WELCOMES YOU
Good morning.
Do you know what time it is now?
What is your name?
Come on.
Do you refuse to tell me?
JIANGYI UNIVERSITY WELCOMES YOU
ZHANG LURANG
"Zhang Lurang."
That's not me.
Your name is on the book. Don't deny it.
Write down his name. He's Zhang Lurang.
Zhang Lurang.
One of the famous students.
Are you also in Class 9 like them?
-I'm actually...
-Got it.
Class 9.
What are you waiting for? Hurry to class.
Okay.
Li Hao.
Here.
Feng Meimei.
Xu Ting.
Here.
-Zhao Wenjing.
-Here.
Girls, you're late.
Introduce yourselves to the class.
My name is Jiang Jia.
Jiang, as in ginger.
Jia, as in excellent.
Okay, sit down.
My name is He Yu.
Yu, as in jade.
And the other student?
My name is Su Zaizai.
Zai, as in together.
So you're Su Zaizai.
Didn't you get full marks
in the English entrance exam?
Yes.
Okay, sit down.
Good for you.
My name is Wang Nan.
I was in No. 3 Junior High.
I'm Fu Yao.
I hate English tests.
Could you teach me English?
Okay. I'll ask you
if I have questions too.
No problem.
Sir, Zhang Lurang hasn't come yet.
Zhang Lurang?
He's in Class 1.
Why would he come here?
Class 1?
Is Zhang Lurang here?
There he is.
Are you Zhang Lurang?
Lurang.
-Wang Yang.
-Here.
-Han Zheng.
-Li Maosheng.
-Here.
-Zhang Renli.
-Your books.
They're in order.
What took you so long?
I was late and stopped
by students on duty at the gate.
What?
So then, what are you going to do?
Are you nervous?
No.
I'm just concerned about you.
I've heard
that tardy students' names get recorded.
-And...
-My name wasn't recorded.
It wasn't?
I'm glad to hear that.
Or Zhang Lurang would appear twice.
Don't you think
you're overly interested in me today?
Am I?
Not at all.
And you're not only interested,
but also
a little bit guilty.
Am I?
Actually, I didn't do anything
that would hurt you too much.
Where are you going?
The broadcast studio.
The broadcast studio?
The more I think, the weirder I feel.
Why did Zhang Lurang pretend
to be in our class?
Maybe he misremembered his class number.
I'm guessing he did that deliberately.
I heard that points got deducted
from their class when someone was late.
Su Zaizai,
only you haven't paid for the uniform yet.
Okay, I'll pay for it now.
Where is my wallet?
I picked up a wallet.
Is there any ID in it?
I haven't opened it.
Look inside.
You might find the owner's ID in there.
I told you to check.
You just wouldn't listen.
I remember
I put it in my pocket this morning.
Calm down, Zaizai.
How about I pay for it first? Then you...
You can do a lost-and-found broadcast.
Maybe a student picked it up.
Is your student ID card in your wallet?
Yes.
That makes things simple.
The ID has your photo and name on it.
Whoever finds it will know it is yours.
But...
But I didn't put my name
on my student ID card.
Then whose name is it?
It's...
Attention.
This is a lost-and-found broadcast.
High school student, Liu Yifei.
High school student, Liu Yifei,
please come to the broadcast studio
to pick up your lost wallet.
Is there a Liu Yifei here?
Then I could be Daniel Wu!
I'm Joey Wong. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
I'll stop looking for my wallet now.
Look, what a good day today!
I'm going out for some fresh air.
What's the hurry?
Wait.
Su Zaizai,
you're that Liu Yifei, aren't you?
THE FIRST HIGH SCHOOL, LIU YIFEI
Yes, it's me.
High school student, Liu Yifei?
Check if anything is missing.
"Zhang Lurang. Gu Ran."
FINDERS
Were they the ones who found this wallet?
Two boys brought it here.
They just left.
Zhang Lurang?
Isn't he the guy we met this morning?
We can still catch up. Hurry.
Faster, Zaizai.
There they are.
Zaizai, hurry up.
Over here!
Zhang Lurang! Gu Ran!
Hey!
What? I didn't get a good look.
Gu Ran?
It's him. Is his name Gu Ran?
Do you know him?
I've seen him at the corner store.
What?
Regarding military training,
that is all I have to say.
Now, I'll talk about disciplines.
Today is the first day of school.
But some students were still late.
The Office of Academic Affairs told me
that students on the tardy list
will have to stand guard
at the military training base.
Nine students were late this morning.
Two are from our class, the honors class.
Someone was not only late,
but also misremembered his class.
What is it?
Do you wish to be in Class 9?
Let me read their names.
From our class,
Zhang Lurang
and Gu Ran.
Su Zaizai and Jiang Jia.
Behave when you're punished tomorrow.
Try to be the most energetic students.
Tomorrow morning at 8 a.m.,
assemble at the school gate.
Remember.
Do not be late.
Since when did you become Gu Ran?
When you changed your name
to Zhang Lurang.
Students have military training together.
I guess I can meet Gu Ran again.
-It's so hot.
-I'm melting.
Why isn't the teacher here yet?
It's taking so long.
Why can't we get on the bus yet?
-It's too hot.
-Where is our teacher?
It's too hot.
Students, here's the thing.
There are too many of us.
One bus can't hold all of us.
I just checked Class 1's bus.
There are some vacant seats.
Who would like to go?
How could this happen?
I don't want to go to Class 1.
Who would want to join another class?
Class 1?
Class 1.
Su Zaizai.
Gu Ran?
Sit beside me.
I...
May I call you Zaizai?
Zaizai.
Sir, I'll go to Class 1.
Okay.
Su...
Su Zaizai, right?
Very good.
Su Zaizai set a good example.
Who else wants to go?
-Sir, we can also go.
-We can go.
Go.
Okay. Time is running out.
You guys can get on their bus.
When you get off, come back to me.
Su Zaizai, are you out of your mind?
Think about it.
Gu Ran found my wallet.
I haven't had a chance to thank him.
I get it. Come on.
Why are Class 9's students
coming to our bus?
Some buses are full,
but ours isn't.
Lurang, cover me. Hurry.
Sorry.
They're so noisy.
How can I focus on my vocabulary?
What's wrong?
Class 9's students are coming.
Yes. So?
Aren't you also from Class 9?
Are you afraid of seeing them?
Who said that?
Hey.
There is space here. Put your bags here.
Okay, thank you.
CHIBI THREE KINGDOMS
Thank you.
-Weird.
-Why are they here?
Why didn't I see Gu Ran and Zhang Lurang?
They stand out. I should have seen them.
I did.
Gu Ran just helped me put away my bag.
Did he?
Where is he?
There.
That one.
I can't see them.
I only see the back of their heads.
JIAOYUN GROUP
You brought so many snacks.
Is this a vacation?
Do high school students
not know anything about military training?
From this day on,
Class 1, Class 5, and Class 9
will be in my charge
this week.
You can call me Mr. Fang.
Who allowed you to move?
Did you see Gu Ran diagonally behind us?
Destiny set us up in adjacent teams.
These difficulties are no big deal.
Zhang Lurang is there too.
Lurang.
Did you see that?
They peeked at me.
Who talked?
Learn to be independent,
confident,
and self-reliant.
Do you understand?
-Yes.
I can't hear you! Do you understand?
-Yes!
Everyone, be at ease.
I'm so tired.
Hand in
all of your snacks and electronics.
You have three minutes.
Place all your prohibited items
into the bins at the front.
We weren't told in advance
that electronics are forbidden.
Come on, Zaizai. Hide some.
Be quick.
You're good at hiding things.
I sewed my PSP into my pants.
Clever, aren't I?
Hurry up.
I think Mr. Fang is right.
Be disciplined and independent.
What?
You. What are you hiding?
Hello, Mr. Fang.
Take them out.
Mr. Fang, there is no more.
What is in your shirt?
It's my fat.
You're playing dumb, aren't you?
Put your hands up and jump three times.
Start.
Jump harder. Go on!
It would've become my fat sooner or later.
Do 50 frog jumps. Get ready.
Fall out!
She's quite funny.
Funny?
No, sir.
Then what were you laughing at?
Mr. Fang,
I had a face twitch.
You're playing dumb, aren't you?
Do 50 frog jumps with her. Get ready.
But I...
If you dawdle, do another 20.
Yes, sir!
You're from Class 1.
But you said you were from Class 9.
You did that on purpose, right?
I never said I was from Class 9.
I won't argue with you.
Why are you jumping so hard?
We jump at the same pace.
As long as we jump together,
we can fudge the numbers.
Really?
Of course.
Don't worry. I'll wait for you.
Are you still chatting?
Do you plan to jump until nightfall?
The last one to finish
will clean the playground tomorrow.
Why is Mr. Fang so...
Seriously?
Liar.
Despicable.
I will never trust you again.
He sure is competitive.
You'll get used to that.
The rest of you, take your luggage
to your dorms and do some cleaning.
Also, each dorm shall send some students
to fetch daily necessities
behind the dorms.
Jiangjiang,
are you okay?
Yes. I'm still alive.
I just have a leg cramp.
The punishment doesn't matter.
But Zhang Lurang is way too terrible.
I agree with you.
The line is quite long.
How about I go
to the infirmary for medicine
for your legs and heat stroke?
Okay, I'll get your daily necessities.
Okay.
Who is this Zhang Lurang you mentioned?
The one who did the frog jump with me.
But I think he's a good guy.
Him? He isn't charming at all.
By any chance,
have you met Gu Ran?
Gu Ran? I've heard about him.
Two freshmen are very famous.
One is Gu Ran.
The other is Zhang Lurang.
Gu Ran is really excellent.
He has great grades.
He's also very polite.
Most importantly, he's a Good Samaritan.
He's a handsome role model.
Zhang Lurang can't compare to Gu Ran.
Not at all.
Jiang Jia and Su Zaizai.
Way to go.
I've actually been keeping a low profile.
I'll show him to you when I can.
You won't be disappointed.
You make me want to see him now.
Tell me your class and name.
Class 1.
Gu Ran.
Is he Gu Ran?
He's so cool.
He's unbelievably handsome.
Class 1.
Look.
Class 1, Guan Fang.
Is anyone here?
Doctor?
Is no one here?
I heard our dorm has no air-conditioning.
I'll enjoy it here for a bit.
Just a second.
It feels so good.
My air-conditioning.
Doctor,
what took you so long?
I think
I have a heat stroke.
So I laid down in bed for some rest.
Doctor?
Then you can't use the AC.
I'll turn it off.
Hey, wait!
You don't need to.
I have a special physique.
When I have a heat stroke,
I feel dizzy,
weak all over,
and a little bit nauseous.
Nothing can make me feel better
except for air-conditioning.
-Doctor.
-Do you need medicine?
-Yes.
-Have you registered?
The register book is on the desk.
Before you leave,
write down your class
and the medicine you took.
Register?
Doctor,
I haven't taken anything.
I just came and got some rest.
Is there another student here?
What's wrong?
Her?
She's seriously ill.
Tell me. What's wrong with you?
Is this how I record?
Okay, done.
Hello, I'm Zaizai.
This is how I'm going
to record my daily life.
Today is September 2nd, 2012, Sunday.
I'm a high school student
from this day on.
Thinking of tomorrow's military training
gives me a headache.
But I've packed a lot of snacks.
This week should go by smoothly.
One more thing.
Today, I have to thank this
for letting me see him again.
I even learned his name.
Gu Ran.
Thanks to him, I got my wallet back.
I suddenly feel excited
for every day to come.
Su Zaizai, why did you lock the door?
Don't you know
you have military training tomorrow?
I know, Mom. I'll go to bed soon.
Anyway, I...
Su Zaizai!
Okay, let's call it a day. Good night.
Hey, do you feel honored?
I seem to have done only two things today
and they both have to do with you.