Three, two, one!
-Cheese!
ADAPTED FROM ZHU YI'S NOVEL,
SHE'S A LITTLE CRAZY, ON JJWXC.NET
-Kiss!
Something That Only I Don't Know About.
Thank you!
Okay, next is the intermission.
I want to add a simple interaction, okay?
-Okay!
-How is this?
I will select a lucky member
from the audience
to come on stage and sing us a song.
-Okay!
-Sure!
Okay, I see that each of you
has a number card.
So I'm going to pick a number randomly.
The one who is called
will sing a song on stage.
Okay?
-Yes.
Okay. Which number should I choose?
Let's go with my lucky number, 49.
Who is holding number 49?
My number is so close.
Rangrang, it's you.
Gosh. It really is you.
You should try your luck on the lottery.
Raise your hand quickly.
Do you want to sing? You can take this.
I can tell Gu Ran can't carry a tune.
Zhang Lurang, are you not going?
Rangrang, I've never heard you sing.
I thought I could hear you sing today.
I don't know what song to sing though.
So you agree to do it.
Number 49 is over here!
Lucky number 49, please come up on stage.
Yes!
Go for it!
The Code of Hammurabi
Enacted by an ancient Babylonian king
Was inscribed on a black basalt
Over 3,700 years ago
You stand in front of the showcase
Staring at the inscription on the stele
But my eyes quietly fixed on your face
That I love so much
Priest, temple, war, bow, and arrow
Whose past do they bring forth?
How beautiful!
I never get tired of looking
at the sea here.
The best part is it's free!
Why aren't you excited about the beach?
What's wrong?
I know.
Zaizai was recording
while Zhang Lurang was singing.
So how did it turn out?
This is so cool!
We were too excited.
But I meant it.
Well,
let's change the topic.
We shouldn't just be chatting
when we come to the beach.
What should we do then?
Well?
-Guan Fang, I just bought this outfit!
-Isn't this fun?
Jiangjiang, I'll help you.
-Gu Ran.
-Is this a declaration of war?
Come on! Take your shoes off!
We've been sunbathing for so long.
Our clothes should be dry by now.
We should enjoy ourselves to the fullest.
But aren't you crossing the line
by holding someone underwater?
This feels so nice.
It feels like the breeze
is blowing all my worries away.
It's the taste of summer.
Speaking of summer,
I think of
the summer sleeping mat on the balcony
and my grandma's mung bean soup.
For me,
it's sitting in an air-conditioned room
holding half a watermelon
and scooping from the very center.
In my mind, it's the moment
when I splash cool water on my face
after playing basketball.
It's so refreshing.
I bet you have a strong body odor.
Body odor?
Yes.
Is there?
What about you, Zhang Lurang?
What comes to mind
when you think of summer?
The banana-flavored popsicles
that can be split into two.
I like eating that too.
My grandma makes
delicious banana-flavored shaved ice.
Let's have that when we get back.
How I wish
this summer could go by more slowly!
We'll return next summer!
And the summers when we're 18,
19,
and all the years to come!
But I still like this summer
most of all!
THE FIRST HIGH SCHOOL
AFFILIATED TO JIANGYI UNIVERSITY
It was a close call.
I almost got placed in Class 5.
Luckily, I pulled through
and passed the minimum score threshold.
We're fated to be in the same class.
We can't escape it.
But I noticed that most of our classmates
are from our Class 9.
He Yu. Fu Yao.
This is great. You're here too.
Wang Nan is in this class too.
He's fetching teaching materials
from the office.
Sit.
A few people still aren't here yet.
I wonder if we'll have any cute guys
in our class.
Zaizai, look.
WELCOME, NEW STUDENTS!
Guan Fang?
Did you choose liberal arts too?
With my reserved
and cultured demeanor,
it would be a shame not to.
I know.
I do look like a science whiz.
It's normal for you to be surprised.
No, we're not.
First of all,
welcome to Liberal Arts Class 2.
I see many new faces.
Of course, I've met some of you
last year.
I'll introduce myself again.
My name is Lin Mao. I teach math.
From today on,
I'll be your homeroom teacher.
Before we start the class,
I have to inform you of something.
Grade 11 is a watershed in high school.
I hope you make good use
of your evening self-study
to work on your weaknesses
and build a strong foundation
for Grade 12.
Okay.
Let's get started.
Let's look at the vocabulary
in the first chapter.
It feels like something is missing
with Guan Fang gone.
Lurang.
You're all I have now.
Gu Ran.
Are you bothering Zhang Lurang
now that Guan Fang is in liberal arts?
If you're bored,
you can sit by the podium.
I'll talk with you.
Okay, let's continue.
Don't laugh.
Guan Fang!
What brings you here?
We came to check on him.
He's so delicate. What if you bully him?
Is he delicate?
Do you have amnesia?
I knew it.
A mere wall
is no obstacle for us.
These are the main points
and example problems
from the first math chapter.
I sorted them out during the summer break.
You can go over it
during the evening self-study.
Did you prepare this specifically for me?
I was doing it anyway.
I see.
Enough.
Let's go somewhere tomorrow afternoon.
No.
You don't even know where we're going.
I know you must be up to no good.
I'm not going wherever it is.
Are you sure?
I'm absolutely sure.
Fine.
Qianyu said he sent us presents.
I thought we could pick it up tomorrow.
But someone doesn't want to go.
Count me in.
I won't turn down a present.
Are you two sure you're here for me?
GUAN'S DESSERT SHOP
This is heavy. Gu Ran, open it.
Let me see.
It's for Guan Fang.
Transformers!
I must be dreaming!
This is mine.
This is for Su Zaizai.
This is for Lurang.
Maybe the presents
were shipped separately.
Don't worry.
That's right.
Your present must be precious.
That's why it was sent in its own parcel.
It must be arriving soon.
Qianyu, are you there?
QIANYU
What's up? Did you receive the presents?
Was anything damaged?
No.
We all like them very much.
But Jiang Jia hasn't received hers yet.
There have been many lost parcels lately.
I'll go and check tomorrow.
As for Jiang Jia,
I didn't know what to buy for her.
Can you help me buy one for her?
Tell me immediately
once my present arrives.
You have a bad memory.
You'll surely forget
if I don't remind you.
QIANYU: CAN YOU HELP ME
BUY ONE FOR HER?
What should I buy?
Excuse me.
Can you wrap this up nicely?
Is it for a girl?
No worries. I'll wrap it nicely.
How should I tell her?
Well,
Qianyu asked me to buy this for you.
That won't do.
Although I bought this present for you,
it's not much different from the others.
You got a present.
Don't be upset about not getting one.
Gu Ran.
Why did you ask for me?
It's...
Well...
Jiang Jia.
Has Qianyu's gift to you arrived?
See? I told you.
Yours was shipped on its own.
I wonder what is inside.
It's so beautiful.
Look.
It looks really nice. Thank Qianyu for me.
Do you like it?
Of course.
I'm coming.
Are you surprised that we're here?
No, I'm taken aback.
What brings you here?
We were supposed to meet at the library,
but you didn't show up.
Su Zaizai and Zhang Lurang
have found a place to study.
We're worried that you were home alone
and fell sick
like last time.
So we came.
I bet you couldn't find seats
at the library.
The reason is not important.
I'll go wash up.
I keep feeling like we lack something
that is essential for doing homework.
Gu Ran, do you have snacks?
They're in my room. Help yourself.
Don't take everything.
Gu Ran keeps so many snacks.
I won't hold back.
QIANYU
As for Jiang Jia,
I didn't know what to buy for her.
Can you help me buy one for her?
Are you coming back this year, Qianyu?
Probably not this year.
We'll see.
Add the values of these two lines.
There is an auxiliary line in the middle.
You don't have to.
There's no need.
It won't connect.
I guess you do have a conscience.
You didn't clear me out.
I know I'm unbelievably handsome
after I clean up a bit.
But you don't have
to stare at me like that.
Did you buy a membership first?
Ten seconds left.
No way.
I'm done.
Okay.
Gu Ran, you lost.
What did you write?
It must be wrong.
We were only competing on speed,
not accuracy.
A bet is a bet. I have a question for you.
Answer me honestly.
Fire away.
Are you...
hiding anything important from me?
I like...
I ate that watermelon.
I ate the watermelon you bought yesterday.
What?
Gu Ran,
so it was you.
I didn't even get one bite.
Seriously? It's just a watermelon.
Guan Fang ate it too.
-I...
-Guan Fang.
I couldn't resist the temptation.
No, you're overreacting. Don't do that!
Stop moving!
Don't get physical.
Jiang Jia, where did you buy this watch?
It looks so nice.
Someone gave it to me.
Someone special gave it to her.
Special?
How special?
It's...
my good friend.
"Good friend."
Evening self-study is starting soon.
Where is Su Zaizai?
I think she went
to ask Zhang Lurang some questions.
I don't feel it during the day.
But it feels spooky
when the classroom is empty
at night.
For you,
this should be scarier.
But I have you to teach me.
I'm not afraid of scary problems.
Look, I solved another one.
A reward.
Why did the power go out?
Maybe the circuit breaker tripped.
I bought them before.
There are still some left.
Let's wait.
Let me see.
You got one wrong again.
"In contraposition, if not B,
then not A.
Out of two propositions,
the condition
and conclusion of one proposition
is the negation
of the other's condition and conclusion."
You have to understand this logic.
Even in this ambiance,
why are you going over the problems?
What was that?
Well, speaking of contraposition,
I came across a trendy saying
on the forum a while ago.
The contrapositive of "I like you" is,
"If someone doesn't like you,
that person wouldn't be me," right?
"I like you"
isn't a proposition.
Because the matter of the heart
can't be judged true or false.
But how can liking someone be false?
If we were
to change the subject to equal value,
the proposition
could be altered like this.
"If I exist,
my love for you exists."
Try to convert this to a contraposition.
"If I don't like you anymore,
then I wouldn't be me."
What are you talking about?
Is it about yesterday's blackout?
No, Mr. Lin just came and said
we can't have co-ed deskmates.
We have to change seats.
I heard from my friend in Class 6
that they have to change seats too.
Why?
I know.
I passed by the office just now.
I saw the dean
and Class 3's homeroom teacher
in a meeting with two students.
As I bent down to tie my shoelaces,
I heard that these two students
snuck out to the school field for a stroll
during yesterday's evening self-study.
They ran into the dean,
who was also out for a walk.
And when that happened,
they were holding hands.
Could it be...
No wonder the school started
cracking down on this.
So it has happened already.
You take so long to tie shoelaces.
Is that important?
The point is how the school handles this.
I think
the teachers will inform us
in the afternoon.
Before class starts,
I have something to brief you on a matter.
Evening self-study sessions
just started recently
and there have already been
close interactions between boys and girls.
The school takes this very seriously.
I hope you can
put your focus on what truly matters.
Evening self-study is provided
to help you study.
Don't exploit this period
for something inappropriate.
Of course,
I believe you all
prioritize your studies.
But please be alert.
Report to me if you notice anything.
Do you all understand?
-Understood.
Good.
Let's continue.
Rangrang,
you're up to 70% accuracy now.
Well done.
Hello.
I just left
from asking Ms. Zhang questions.
I'm coming down now. Wait for me.
Why are there people
in the club room at night?
Hurry up.
Here.
You're so slow.
Look at this.
Three moves.
You're going to lose in three moves.
Think carefully.
Here.
-Watch.
-Su Zaizai.
Mr. Lin wants you to go to the office now.
Three moves.
-I'll give you three moves.
-Okay.
Bring it on. Five.
Here.
Mr. Lin.
Come in.
Mr. Lin, you tell her.
Okay.
Well, we asked for you because...
Don't beat around the bush.
Let me do it.
Have you two been close lately?
Yes.
You're still young.
Placement tests are in two months.
Every second in high school is crucial.
Don't waste your time on other things.
Ms. Zhang,
it's not what you think.
What do you mean?
We have a photo of you two.
Hurry up.
Look at this. Explain it.
We were going over problems.
Did you have to do that
in an empty classroom?
Someone has reported this to us.
What does this mean?
It means
that your behavior has affected others.
Well, Mr. Chang,
it's not that serious.
These two tutor each other.
We all know that.
Maybe those who aren't aware of this
had a misunderstanding
and took this photo.
Right?
You.
Why are you nodding?
Listen, Su Zaizai.
Su Zaizai.
Ms. Zhang told me
that you're joining
an English recitation competition.
And Zhang Lurang
is joining a physics competition.
You're all grown up.
We shouldn't waste our time.
Am I right?
You've grown up and are big kids now.
I'm sure you know what is important.
We must place our time and energy
on preparing for the competitions.
I can win first place
even without preparing.
Me too.
What...
Look at them.
Mr. Chang,
if you call us here
but refuse to believe what we say,
did you bring us here just to accuse us?
Su Zaizai.
Forget it.
You can go back.
Mind your behavior from now on.
You may go.
You must win first place.
Don't mind them, Mr. Chang.
The teachers have found out about you two.
Do you still plan to bug him?
So you told on us.
Yes. So what?
I told the truth.
How can you be such an idiot?
I really can't stand you.
Do you like Zhang Lurang?
So why are you trying to get my attention?
What nonsense are you saying?
Just drop it, will you?
You only look dumber by doing this.
By the way,
here's a heads-up for you.
I will let Zhang Lurang know
that it was you who told the teacher.
Go ahead and cry.
After you cry it out,
be a better person.
You...
This kind of thing
had better not happen again.
THE FIRST HIGH SCHOOL
AFFILIATED TO JIANGYI UNIVERSITY
I heard a parent came here
because a student is dating.
The boy is even in an honors class.
How daring.
I'm not griping.
Perfect timing, Lurang. Come here.
Mom, what are you doing here?
If I didn't come,
I wouldn't have known
what you were up to at school.
Your homeroom teacher
called me last night.
She said you've been getting close
with a girl in another class lately.
You...
It's not that serious.
They're just tutoring each other.
And you know about it, don't you?
He should focus on his studies at his age.
I'm not asking you
to be as excellent as your brother.
But you should at least not make us worry.
By the way,
didn't you come to see me
for something else?
Yes.
I got so mad at him that I forgot.
I came here to ask you
about Lurang's school transfer.
What documents are needed?
Talking in person is...
Transfer? What transfer?
I've discussed this with your dad.
You're transferring back to Suyang.
-It's...
-I'll take the NCEE in Jiangyi.
Take the NCEE in Jiangyi?
Your uncle doesn't have
much time to look after you.
Could you get into any good university?
Lurang,
class is starting soon.
Go back to the classroom.
Give that to me. Put the homework down.
Go now.
Why are you looking at me?
Look at him. How can I be at ease?
Why are you so mad? Sit.
Stop taking his side.
It's not a serious problem.
Lurang, regarding the NCEE...
Uncle, can I stay in Jiangyi for the NCEE?
You don't have to take care of me.
I'll move into the school dorm.
That's not the reason you have to go back.
Your student registration is in Suyang,
so you have to take the NCEE there.
Actually, your mom was right.
The Suyang school has honor classes
for both science and the arts.
If you go back too late,
you won't get into an honors class.
After all,
the two schools' curriculums differ.
You will more or less be affected.
If you're taking the exam somewhere else,
you need to prepare many documents.
If you insist on staying,
I'll try to figure something out.
Okay.
There is still some time.
Don't worry too much about it.
Rest early.
SU ZAIZAI
NEVER MIND. I'LL CONTINUE
DOING HOMEWORK. IT'S NEVER-ENDING!
Rangrang.
I bet that you hadn't left,
so I waited here for you.
I think I've gotten used to commuting
to and from school with you.
Something feels missing when I'm alone.
Rangrang,
is something on your mind?
Is it because someone reported us?
If possible,
can you talk to me about it?
I haven't decided yet.
Then come to me when you want to talk.
I can tell you some jokes.
I was talking to a girl from my class
in the hallway just now.
The dean saw us and kept staring at me.
Is that necessary?
Beats me.
They're so strict on this now.
Zhang Lurang from the honors class
gets such good grades.
A girl from another class
keeps pestering him.
What bad luck.
I bet he must be annoyed.
SCHOOL TRANSFER APPLICATION
-Let me help you.
-No, thank you.
I saw you in the office
when I handed in homework earlier today.
Were you and Mr. Lin talking
about the academic competition?
No.
Before you transfer,
you need to fill out this application.
Fill this out.
As for the rest of the procedures,
your mom will handle it.
By the way,
there are a few months left.
Have you told Gu Ran and others?
Not yet.
You should tell them soon.
Give them time to process it.
SCHOOL TRANSFER APPLICATION
Whenever I'm down,
food can always cheer me up.
Guan Fang said
his grandma recently made a tasty dish.
Su Zaizai, be quiet.
I'm sorry.
I...
You've arrived home. I'll get going.
EXCLUSIVELY FOR RANGRANG
Let me help you.
No, thank you.
Su Zaizai, be quiet.
Zhang Lurang from the honors class
gets such good grades.
A girl from another class
keeps pestering him.
What bad luck.
EXCLUSIVELY FOR RANGRANG
I bet he must be annoyed.
I'm done eating. I'm leaving.
I will be happy.
Crap.
I'm not happy.
Not even jellies can make me feel better.
I must be beyond saving.