Three, two, one!
-Cheese!
ADAPTED FROM ZHU YI'S NOVEL,
SHE'S A LITTLE CRAZY, ON JJWXC.NET
-Kiss!
Can You Come a Bit Closer?
What the heck?
This is the freshmen's party,
but a senior stole the show.
Then why didn't you volunteer
to show off your talents?
You could've been in the limelight.
Well, I don't have any talents.
By the way, who is that guy?
Not only can he play the guitar,
but he's also good-looking.
He's posing a threat to me.
His name is Shen Qianyu.
He's Grade 12, Class 6's class rep.
He's also the leader of the Drama Club.
He can play the guitar and the piano.
No wonder he's a bit more popular than me.
Zhang Lurang,
look.
Don't those two girls
grinning from ear to ear
look familiar to you?
They're Su Zaizai and Jiang Jia.
Jiangjiang,
I want to leave.
Zaizai.
He plays the guitar so well.
THE FIRST HIGH SCHOOL
AFFILIATED TO JIANGYI UNIVERSITY
Why is the first class math?
And our homeroom teacher teaches it.
We saw him during military training.
He doesn't seem very stern.
It's math that is scary,
not the teacher.
Just leafing through the textbook
makes me sick.
He's coming.
Good morning, class.
-Good morning, sir.
This is the first class of the new term.
Although we've met a few times
during military training,
I would like to introduce myself first.
LIN MAO
My name is Lin Mao.
I teach math
and I will be your homeroom teacher
for at least the following year.
However,
I don't want you to fear me
like the way mice fear cats.
I want to be friends
with every one of you.
Whatever you're interested in,
we can discuss it together.
For example, basketball.
I may play better than you guys.
All right, let's get back to business.
Now that you're in high school,
there are several things
I need you to understand.
The most important thing is diligence.
From now on,
you're high school students.
You need to focus on your studies.
We'll take an assessment test
in the first class
to see how good your English is.
Now, hand in everything irrelevant
to the test.
In times like this,
I wish I could hand myself in.
GRADE 10, CLASS 9
All right. We'll call it a day.
Take a break, class.
Hurry, go.
Mr. Lin,
do we have student clubs this year?
Student clubs?
There is no news about that yet.
When will it be decided?
Wait for further notice.
Are student clubs canceled?
Didn't Mr. Lin just say
it hadn't been decided yet?
Why is it suddenly canceled?
Right. Who told you that?
I heard
that it's Zhang Yan who asked
to have them canceled.
Who is Zhang Yan?
Our English teacher
and Class 1's homeroom teacher.
I see.
I heard of her before the semester began.
Everyone calls her
the Joy Killer.
Wherever she goes,
there are no more extracurriculars.
None.
Seriously?
No student clubs anymore?
Class dismissed.
What are you doing?
He's a top student.
I feel like I'm not good enough for him.
Maybe everyone is stupid
in his eyes.
You're exaggerating.
Su Zaizai,
don't you think you're obsessed with him?
So what?
Are you just going
to keep staring at his photo?
No.
I'll stare at him through the window
when he delivers homework,
in the hallway when he gets water,
and on the playground
when he does morning exercise.
Those are all different places, okay?
Just staring at him will get you nowhere.
You need to try to get to know him.
For example, his hobbies, interests,
and the type of girl he likes.
Maybe you can ask Gu Ran.
Although he has a punchable face,
I think he knows Zhang Lurang the best,
aside from Zhang Lurang himself.
Would he tell me?
Give it a try.
If he refuses to tell,
we'll have to bribe him with a drumstick.
Maybe you should wait
until we're alone.
No.
I can't wait.
Actually...
Go ahead.
Don't be shy.
I have a question.
Okay.
Well...
What kind of girls do guys like?
My kind of girl
has long hair,
small eyes, and a round face.
She needs to be gentle
and not too tall.
No bangs.
Her name should be three characters.
Her surname can't be Jiang.
I see.
How about Zhang Lurang?
You want to win over my friend first.
Zhang Lurang likes...
Do you think I would tell you?
Be honest.
You have no idea, right?
I guess
you're not that close.
You grew up together,
but he has never shared this with you.
You want me to prove you wrong.
Do you think I'll rise to the bait?
How naive.
How did it go?
Weird. He's being so weird.
Did he not tell you?
As dumb as he is,
he actually didn't fall for my trick.
This is so odd.
What's more,
how does he manage to be so obnoxious?
It's fine.
I can ask him myself.
It won't be the first time
I've put my foot in my mouth with him.
I'm used to it.
Shen Qianyu.
I can't even enjoy my food.
Why?
What happened?
It's tiring to be popular.
It's nothing. I'm used to it.
I agree.
I'm used to it too.
Lurang,
I need to ask you an important question.
What...
What is your type?
What?
I mean,
what is your ideal girlfriend like?
Girlfriend?
I can answer that.
I'll be happy just looking at her
and want to spend every day with her.
Even if we do nothing when we're together,
all your worries will be gone.
-I don't have a type.
-Impossible.
You must have a type.
Think carefully.
How about now?
I don't have a type.
That's impossible.
You're not being honest with us.
Aren't we friends?
Why won't you tell us?
Spill it.
Tell us.
-Say it.
-Tell us.
My type?
A girl that stays by my side every day.
Fine, I have a type.
Tell us.
She has glossy hair.
Glossy hair.
Her eyes are big and round.
She always looks very smart.
Girls with big eyes.
And has good grades.
Most of the time,
she has a big appetite.
A big appetite?
I see.
She needs to be a foodie.
And she likes sports.
Passionate
and upbeat?
She's very needy
and loves to follow me around.
Is that really what Zhang Lurang said?
Yes.
Both Gu Ran and Guan Fang confirmed it.
I think he was basically describing me.
Jiangjiang, I have to go.
I have something important to do.
What are you going to do?
I'll become Rangrang's type.
Are you sure you want to do this?
My hair is glossy.
I already fit the first criterion.
So I'll move on to the second one.
I need to make him think that I'm smart.
He's coming.
Su Zaizai,
do you understand
what the teacher taught us yesterday?
Yes, I got it right away.
By the way,
as for the problem we discussed yesterday,
I think this is the answer.
The braking process of the car
is a uniformly decelerated linear motion.
Given the initial velocity
and braking distance,
we can know that the answer
is 12 m/s.
Well? How did I do?
How long did you spend
memorizing that question?
It took me half an hour last night.
Although I'm bad at physics,
I'm sure
that when you said the answer,
you got the unit of acceleration wrong.
You said meter per second.
So what is the correct unit?
Meter per second squared.
This is embarrassing, Jiangjiang.
Let's take a detour back.
Are you giving up?
It's fine.
I'll move on to the next criterion.
What a coincidence, Rangrang.
Are my eyes big and round enough?
Look, I didn't ride my bike today.
I'm going to jog home.
Jog home?
Yes.
I really love working out.
I love sports so much
that I can't sleep if I haven't exercised.
Okay, keep running.
I'll wait for the bus.
Rangrang, do you need company?
If you do, just say the word.
No, thank you.
Aren't you going to jog?
I can jog every day,
but I don't get
to go home with you every day.
Rangrang,
do you take this bus every day?
Yes.
I take this bus home too.
Where do you get off?
It's far away.
How many stops away is that?
Five?
Six?
Su Zaizai.
Be quiet.
Okay.
Rangrang,
we know each other now.
What do you know about me
other than my name?
It's fine if you don't know anything.
Let me officially introduce myself.
I have
big round eyes
and glossy hair.
I eat a lot and love sports.
My type?
A girl that stays by my side every day.
Tell us.
She has glossy hair.
I'm very smart too.
Most importantly,
I'm needy.
I'm very needy.
I love to follow people around.
What are you looking at?
My girl.
Do you already have one?
Don't you think
you're too young for that?
So when you described your type,
you were talking about your pet?
Her eyes are big, right?
Yes.
Big and round.
His pet?
Yes. She's a golden retriever.
I knew we couldn't count on Gu Ran.
In just a few days,
I've made a complete fool of myself.
Don't be upset.
I'm not upset.
I'm full of regret.
We still have student clubs.
You're not in the same class,
but if you are in the same club,
you'll get a lot of chances to see him.
It's not too late to rebuild your image.
You're right.
But I heard
that the clubs might get canceled.
A meeting will be held to decide that.
I'm so frustrated.
Okay, let's call it a day.
Your homework is the textbook problems.
It's due tomorrow. Class dismissed.
What's wrong?
You all look so listless.
I told you
not to hold out hope.
Mr. Lin hasn't told us the result yet.
I bet the clubs have been canceled.
My Shen Qianyu.
It seems
that you heard the news about the clubs.
I didn't see it coming either.
Mr. Lin, is it a done deal now?
Yes.
After all,
the time for signing up has been set.
Canceling the clubs now
would be unreasonable.
Then can we...
What does that mean?
Sign-ups have been set,
so the clubs won't be canceled!
Great!
Okay, quiet down.
Now you're energized.
But I have to remind you
that if club participation
affects your grades,
they can be canceled at any time.
Do you understand?
-Yes.
Okay. Wang Nan.
Come with me to get the sign-up forms.
Sure.
My drama club. My Shen Qianyu.
My happiness is back.
Have you decided on Drama Club?
Of course.
Zaizai, why don't you join it with me?
I want to sign up
for the same club as Zhang Lurang.
But I feel that Zhang Lurang is too aloof
to join any club.
No, he's not aloof at all.
He just doesn't talk much.
Are you asking me
which club Zhang Lurang will join?
He'll join whichever club I join.
You can't expect us to buy that.
I can vouch for him. He's not lying.
We have Zhang Lurang's sign-up form.
So it's true.
Which club are you going to sign up for?
Basketball.
Only on the basketball court
can we showcase our remarkable skills.
Basketball?
Playing basketball is dangerous.
Could you give it a second thought?
A second thought?
Sure.
However,
this person doubted me just now.
I'm upset.
Then what do you want?
How about I buy you milk tea for a month
if you get Zhang Lurang
to join the Drama Club?
-That's not...
-No problem!
But you need to specify the cup size,
frequency, and brand.
Let me be frank.
Milk tea is not enough to bribe me.
Just milk tea...
And the number
of our grade's prettiest girl.
The prettiest girl in our grade?
Yes, the prettiest girl in our grade.
Many guys want to have her number.
Right?
Why didn't you say so sooner?
Go straight to the point next time.
It's a deal then.
Here, try it.
How is it?
Mango pomelo sago
is our signature dessert.
It's great.
-It's delicious.
-I'm glad you like it.
I came with He Yu once.
It was very delicious.
Why are they here?
Why are you guys here?
What a dumb question.
This is our buddy's home.
Look, it's my family business.
Zhang Lurang, what a coincidence.
Are you Xiaofang's classmates too?
What do you want to have?
I'll make it for you.
Don't you think
it's too much of a coincidence?
A bit.
Those girls are so cunning.
It is a coincidence.
Why are you so sure?
She's bad at acting.
Look, Guan Fang.
They're chatting with your grandma.
What are they talking about?
My grandma must be praising me.
I know her.
She sings my praises to everyone.
It's so embarrassing.
Guan Fang was still wetting the bed
in primary school?
Yes.
And he insisted that it was sweat.
Don't you think
he was a silly child?
Grandma never knows
how to keep a low profile.
Look, they glanced at me too.
Listen, all elders love me.
Your grandma must be praising me too.
Yes, for sure.
Lurang,
you need to talk more sometimes.
Elders don't like
boys like you.
But I think
that boy over there is nice.
He looks like a good boy.
I agree.
Rangrang, are you full?
Yes.
You didn't eat much.
Rangrang, are you taking the bus too?
Yes.
What a coincidence. Me too.
Didn't you say you love sports?
Taking the bus home with you
is also a kind of sport.
Student card.
I'll pay for you.
Thank you.
Student card.
Sir!
If you're not feeling well,
you can take my seat.
Mind your own business.
I'm not feeling unwell.
That's right.
I saw you trying to lean on that lady,
so I thought you had trouble standing.
When did I do that?
You're mistaken.
Didn't you see her getting
in my way?
You kept moving closer to me.
Yes, I saw it.
Young girl,
you can't make wild accusations.
There are so many passengers.
Did anyone else see that?
Anyone?
Anyone at all?
I saw it.
I saw it too.
Yes, I saw it too.
You're shameless.
Scumbag.
No point in arguing with a scumbag.
Yes, let's just call the police.
-Wait, guys.
-Scumbag.
You're all lying!
I can't bother you today.
Luckily this is my stop
or I wouldn't let it slide.
Get off!
Wait and see!
-He's embarrassing.
-He should be arrested.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Weren't you afraid?
I was afraid.
I was only so brave because you're here.
Why?
Because you would back me up.
I wouldn't.
But you did.
I didn't.
We are arriving at Jiangxia Park.
Please exit from the back door.
The next stop is Chenyang Neighborhood.
I'm getting off at the next stop.
Me too.
CHENYANG NEIGHBORHOOD
Why are you following me?
I'm not. I live...
I live over there.
I'm on my way home.
See you tomorrow.
Rangrang,
good night.
Zhang Lurang,
did you sign up for the Drama Club too?
Gu Ran filled out this form
for you, right?
This is his handwriting.
What's wrong with the Drama Club?
It's great.
Everyone should sign up
for the Drama Club.
Don't you think so, Lurang?
The Drama Club?
We thought about it carefully and decided
that the Drama Club was the best.
Yes.
Playing basketball outdoors is too tiring.
Staying indoors is much better.
We don't mind getting exhausted,
but we can't let you suffer with us.
Yes.
Is he angry?
That expression usually means he gives in.
Something is off.
What is off?
Jiang Jia sent me
that girl's number on WeChat yesterday.
She still hasn't accepted
my friend request.
What's weirder
is that her profile picture is a lotus
and her username is Flowers in Summer.
That sounds like it could be my mom.
Don't say that.
She's just mature.
Do you think Jiang Jia fooled me?
No way.
She has no motive.
Her motive...
Why didn't it occur to me yesterday?
What?
How is it possible
that she would give me
another girl's number?
Why is that impossible?
She's in love with me.
I need to find a chance to talk to her.
Of course my mom didn't add him.
She said someone called Mr. Charming
kept sending her friend requests.
She directly rejected him.
I said I accidentally gave out her number
and she told me off.
She said someone with that username
can't be a good student.
What if Gu Ran finds out?
I don't care.
Getting Zhang Lurang
into the Drama Club is what matters.
What are you making?
Paper stars.
I'll make a jar of stars
and give it to Shen Qianyu.
What's the use of that?
It's useless.
But it's romantic.
I'll be able to see Shen Qianyu
when I go to the club this afternoon.
He's definitely as outstanding,
gentle,
and humorous as usual.
This is our first club meeting.
Let me introduce myself first.
I'm Xiao Kai,
your teacher in the Drama Club
and the teacher
of Grade 12 acting classes.
Where is my Shen Qianyu?
Zhang Lurang isn't here either.
Maybe he isn't coming.
The club is so boring
without him.
Sorry.
Sorry for being late.
Come in and take a seat.
Being late is better than being absent.
Sit.
Hey, Qianyu.
You look so happy.
I didn't know you were so into me.
What were you murmuring?
Be quiet, everyone.
Let me introduce someone to you.
The boy beside me
is Shen Qianyu.
Qianyu is
the president of the Drama Club.
Qianyu, say hi
to everybody.
Hi, everyone.
Clap!
-Clap!
-Sorry, sir. We're late.
Come in and take a seat.
Is this seat taken?
No.
Today is September 11th, 2012.
I took the bus with Rangrang
for the first time
and couldn't help but secretly film it.
That was close.
I almost got caught.
This is my sad face.
I made a big fool of myself today.
His girl is actually...
Forget it. Tomorrow is another day.
Let bygones be bygones.
Darn. I missed my stop!
Today, I desperately wanted
to summon Aladdin
to fulfill just one of my wishes.
I wish I could erase
Rangrang's memory of me today.