Three, two, one!
-Cheese!
ADAPTED FROM ZHU YI'S NOVEL,
SHE'S A LITTLE CRAZY, ON JJWXC.NET
-Kiss!
My Wish When I Was 17 Was About You.
TO SU ZAIZAI, FROM ZHANG LULI
It has been a while, Zaizai.
I can't use my phone anymore
as the NCEE is around the corner.
I can only write letters instead.
I was on the phone with Lurang
a while back.
He was in a good mood
and told me a lot about you guys.
I don't know anyone else.
But from the way he talked about them,
they must be just as interesting as you.
You said Lurang became friends with you
because you kept bothering him.
Let me tell you in secret.
I've seen Lurang play
with that toy many times.
He must be happy to have you as a friend,
but won't admit it.
My brother is cute in that way.
By the way,
I talked to my parents after I got back.
I get the feeling they're slowly changing.
I hope things get better.
Zaizai, I wish you all the best too.
Zaizai!
You're going to be late for school!
I'm coming!
THE FIRST HIGH SCHOOL
You used to be excited about your birthday
before it even arrived.
Why don't you want to celebrate this year?
I know there are some things
that I can't avoid,
but I can't help but think about the fact
that my birthday
is before the winter break.
After my birthday,
Zhang Lurang will go back to Suyang.
I suddenly don't feel like celebrating it.
It's exactly because he's leaving
that we must enjoy your birthday
so that it's meaningful.
We must have a good time.
Come on.
This is so difficult.
What is so difficult about buying a gift?
Winter is coming.
You can buy a scarf or gloves.
Or...
Bracelets are nice too.
Most girls like pretty things.
Do you?
Are you asking that question
to mock me for not being like most girls?
Forget it.
There is no use
keeping it after buying it.
I got this from the spicy hot pot event
at the canteen.
I have no use for it. You can have it.
No.
Knowing Jiang Jia's personality,
she'll wait outside the canteen tomorrow.
I found this on the roadside.
I'm lucky, aren't I?
That is too fake.
Gu Ran.
Guilty conscience? You look spooked.
What do you want with me at this hour?
Well,
it's just that
I just bought Su Zaizai's birthday gift.
It's one of those carved wooden dolls.
Don't you know her better?
What do you think?
Sure, Zaizai will probably like it.
Is that all?
Yes. What else could there be?
By the way,
the store where I bought the gift
happened to have a promotion,
buy 2 and get 20% off,
so I was suckered into buying this.
I have no use for it,
so I guess you can have it.
If you don't want it...
Why would I turn down something free?
You don't like me, do you?
Who did you say I like?
You?
How is that possible?
What is so good about you?
Besides having big eyes,
fair skin, a small face,
curly lashes, and tall,
what qualities do you possess?
I...
What I meant is that
you're not really my type.
Don't overthink it.
That is good.
I thought you had a thing for me.
That scared me.
Don't flatter yourself.
We finally made it to the Friday
without evening self-study.
We're leaving first.
-Bye.
-See you next week.
Let's go.
Let's go get Zhang Lurang and Gu Ran.
Dinner is on me today.
I've even decided on the restaurant.
If you're treating us,
we might make you broke.
I'm happy because it's my birthday.
Su Zaizai, Mr. Lin wants to see you.
I wonder what it is about.
Why don't I text you the address?
Head there first. I'll catch up with you.
Okay, then we'll leave first.
Okay.
Sir.
Mr. Lin, you wanted to see me?
It's no big deal.
Grade 10 just had their monthly exam.
They're eager to get their English scores.
I don't have enough graders,
so I wanted to ask for your help.
Grade the multiple-choice questions
using this answer key.
It won't take long.
Are you
in a hurry to leave?
I'm not in a hurry.
Okay.
Then you can grade at that table.
Here.
Thank you.
Are you done?
Goodbye, Mr. Lin.
Thank you so much for today.
Be careful on your way home. Bye.
It's late.
Why don't you guys go home first?
What? I guess we have no choice.
We'll celebrate your birthday tomorrow.
It's fine. We can do it anytime.
MS. SU ZAIZAI, THE CHALLENGE BEGINS!
THIS WAY, PLEASE
COME ON, YOU'RE ALMOST THERE
SU ZAIZAI! TURN AROUND!
-Happy birthday to you
-Happy birthday.
Happy birthday.
I thought you all left.
Why would we?
Even if they left, I wouldn't.
You go too far to belittle others
to make yourself look good.
We wouldn't leave either, okay?
So? Isn't my idea better?
I asked Mr. Lin to delay you for a bit.
What do you think? Isn't it great?
Your gift has grown wings
and flown to your room.
This is the most important part now.
Su Zaizai, make a wish.
It's Lurang's first birthday celebration.
He doesn't even celebrate
his own birthday.
My wish is simple.
It's not too much
if I make two wishes, right?
For my first wish, I hope everyone can be
as happy every day as they are today.
What about the second wish?
I'm not telling you my second wish.
Su Zaizai, you've changed!
You can't get me!
Be careful!
My second wish
is to spend Rangrang's 18th birthday
with him.
Rangrang.
Hey.
Are you free right now?
What's up?
Can you come downstairs?
I'm outside your house.
Yes! I'll come down right away.
Rangrang.
Did you want to see me?
Happy birthday, Su Zaizai.
Your gift.
I think you'll like it.
Thank you.
This is my happiest birthday ever.
When you get back to Suyang,
I'll use it to take a lot of pictures
and send them to you.
Can you grant me a wish too?
What is it?
Will you come back
after I use up all the photo papers?
Okay.
Don't break your word.
One by one.
Don't rush, kids.
Why are there still so many people?
The school-organized ID photo session
is so popular.
What time are you leaving tomorrow?
Nine o'clock.
We'll be in class at that time.
We won't be able to see you off.
It's all right.
I'm not going very far anyway.
I can come back during the holidays.
Yes, we can visit you
if you can't come.
Besides, a year or so isn't that long.
It will pass by quickly.
Yes, very quickly.
Then let's make a deal
to keep in touch.
It's good enough
if you don't harass Zhang Lurang.
Harass?
It's care.
-What is going on?
-I don't know.
Why hasn't the line moved at all?
Sorry, excuse me.
-Excuse me.
-Watch out.
Is something wrong?
Kids.
Calm down, kids.
We're having technical issues.
We're getting someone to fix it.
It might take a while.
I know a bit about computers.
Can I take a look?
Sure. Come on.
-Can he really do it?
-I know, right?
All right.
This guy is amazing.
You fixed it so quickly.
It's just a hobby.
Gu Ran,
you're amazing.
You kept it from us.
I just got lucky today.
Why are you being humble?
You're really good.
I only use the computer to play games
and surf the Internet.
Yet you know how to fix it.
It's actually not that difficult.
Well,
my talent did most of the job.
All right. We can proceed.
Are you guys friends?
Yes, best friends.
If it weren't for this boy,
we might have had to wait a long time.
Why don't we let them
take the photos first?
-Sure.
-Okay.
Let's take your photos first.
Really?
Let's get changed
into the outfit for the photoshoot.
It's so cold. I'm glad the heater is on.
Boy, you're up first.
All right, sit up.
You're smiling so happily.
You're in a good mood
after fixing the computer.
Okay, three, two,
one.
Okay, look at the camera.
Three, two, one.
Tilt your head a little to the left.
Okay, three, two, one.
Let me see yours.
It looks really good.
Students, get your photos.
Okay.
Why do I look so creepy?
Let me see.
I want to see it too.
Let me take a look.
Let me see.
Where is mine?
What are you doing?
Excuse me.
Can we get another photo?
Guan Fang,
don't be nitpicky.
I meant a group photo.
Sure. Go on.
No one is left anyway.
No rules this time.
Pose however you want.
-Let's go.
-Go on.
I'm standing here.
Move over.
Don't move.
The boy in the middle, don't be so stiff.
Relax and smile.
You look the best when you smile.
How old are you guys?
Seventeen.
Okay, when I count down to one,
shout "17" together.
-Okay.
-Come on.
Three, two, one.
-Seventeen!
Rangrang.
Remember to memorize English vocabulary
when you are in Suyang.
Don't forget to correct the math problems
that you get wrong.
Drinking a glass of milk before bed
helps you sleep.
Be careful
when you go home alone at night.
Smile more
or people will think
you're difficult to get along with.
No.
You had better not smile.
What if everyone finds out
that you have a nice smile?
What will I do then?
Su Zaizai.
Let's aim
for East China University together.
It's snowing.
That means
it's our second winter together.
Rangrang, happy one-year anniversary.
Let's make an exchange.
Think of it
as proof of what we just talked about.
Okay.
Look.
A snowflake left a mark.
So you can't break a promise
that you made to someone
during the first snowfall
or there will be serious consequences.
What consequences?
I will get angry.
That's very serious.
Zaizai!
NEW SEMESTER, NEW ATMOSPHERE
Come.
Rangrang, I heard from Mr. Lin
that you can't use your phone either.
So I began writing my first letter.
Now that school has started,
are you getting used to Suyang?
To be honest,
I'm not used to taking the bus
and going home alone.
So I started biking again.
-Hello, Mr. Lin.
-Su Zaizai.
Hi, Susu.
I saw Susu
when I passed by your house.
She doesn't pounce on me anymore.
I'll work harder to win her over soon.
How are you doing over there?
The new school is great.
But the curriculum moves
at a faster pace than in Jiangyi.
I've adapted to it.
I scored 122 in English
in the last monthly exam.
I haven't fallen behind.
You can rest assured.
That supermarket
that you went to with the flash sale
has been converted into a bookstore.
I found out when I went to buy materials.
You can check it out
when you get the chance.
Spring comes
later in Suyang than in Jiangyi.
I heard that the winter jasmine
in Jiangyi has bloomed.
You must be so happy.
Study hard.
Why do you still remember the flash sale?
That was so embarrassing.
Don't remember these things.
Let me tell you something interesting.
On April Fool's Day this year,
Guan Fang and Gu Ran acted
in The Emperor's New Clothes.
It was hilarious.
It's a pity
that you couldn't see it.
By the way,
I'm also studying hard.
Jiang Jia and I signed up
for an intensive summer math class,
so I can't visit you in Suyang.
TO ZHANG LURANG
I went south in September
to take part in a competition.
It's the furthest place
I've ever been to alone.
Everything is beautiful there.
Standing on the beach,
I suddenly wanted to go back to Jiangyi.
It would have been different
-if you guys were there with me.
-No.
-By the way,
-He looks good in anything.
-Luli got into East China University.
-No need to pick out clothes.
Mom and Dad wanted him to study finance.
He chose his favorite major, Biology.
I envy him.
I'm so happy for him.
I don't know if it's just me.
After entering Grade 12,
-I feel as if I've grown up overnight.
-We're going to be late.
I'm exhausted every day.
I wish I could be without care
and sleep for three days and three nights.
But every time I see
Grade 10 and Grade 11 students looking
admiringly,
yes, looking admiringly at us.
I feel that I can hold on a little longer.
I had a physical exam today.
I seem to have an irregular heartbeat.
I have a rapid heartbeat.
It keeps thumping.
It's all my fault.
I shouldn't have thought of you
during the physical exam.
RANGRANG, I...
Rangrang,
I miss you so much.
Okay, that is all for today's class.
The school is doing a survey on the NCEE,
including your target universities
and majors.
Please fill it out as per your situation.
Wang Nan, please distribute the forms.
Thank you.
Zaizai, where do you want to go?
East China University.
I've made a deal with Rangrang.
MY IDEAL UNIVERSITY AND MAJOR
Guan Fang,
what do you want to study in the future?
I want to study economics.
What is with that look?
I've never made a mistake
doing the accounts
for my grandma since I was a kid.
I'm obviously financially savvy.
What about you?
Me?
Medicine.
Both my parents are doctors.
I can't lose to them.
Jiangjiang, enough about us.
What about you? What do you want to study?
I haven't made up my mind yet.
It's okay. Take your time.
You can fill it out after the NCEE.
There is no rush.
Did we get our math exam back?
I put it in your desk drawer.
MATH EXAM
Do you two have any paper?
I meant tissue paper.
Su Zaizai, do you have any?
Su Zaizai.
-Su Zaizai.
-The paper?
Which problem?
Are you two okay?
I think they've gone dumb from studying.
Both of them are so distracted.
There is still some time before the NCEE.
Could it be that they are too stressed?
Maybe.
Let's go to your house tomorrow.
I miss your grandma.
We can also take those two to relax.
Sure. Leave it to me.
I forgot my soccer ball. I'll go get it.
Head back first.
How forgetful.
Has he gone dumb from studying too?
Am I the only normal person here?
I suddenly feel amazing.
Why are you sighing?
Haven't you heard a saying?
"Everyone's luck is limited.
If you keep sighing,
your luck will slip away."
Why are you here?
I was picking up my ball over there.
I was about to get it,
but a gust of wind blew it away.
I looked up
and it was you sighing.
Tell me.
What is going on lately?
Zaizai's dream
is to be a diplomatic interpreter.
Guan Fang wants to study economics.
You all have dreams.
But I don't.
I don't think I've ever thought about it.
All I knew
was that after primary school
came junior high
and after that was senior high.
But I now realize
there will be no more rules after this.
I have to proceed on my own.
It's weird, right?
Few people have no dreams.
I don't even have any strengths.
Who says you don't?
Do I have any?
You...
Never mind. I won't give you a hard time.
Come on. It's time for evening self-study.
No matter what,
we have to pass the NCEE first.
Hello.
It has been a long time.
Today is January 1st, 2015.
It's the start of a new year.
The second semester of Grade 12
is coming up.
We only get one day off for the holiday.
I'm going back to school tomorrow.
There is nothing special
about the holiday.
All I do is study.
But there is a silver lining.
Rangrang sent me a letter again.
This is the seventh letter.
The contents
are just New Year's greetings.
He also expressed his sadness and guilt
for not being able to be by my side
in the coming year.
I understand.
I'm very forgiving anyway.
He can make it up to me later.
Also,
I've only used three photo papers.
Don't blame me for being slow.
I thought about using them all at once.
But I think this is too reckless.
Also, I won't make Rangrang
into someone who doesn't keep his word.
So I won't finish them
until I get some decent grades.
All right, I'll stop here.
I'm going to continue studying. Bye.
The phrase "Reading a letter
is like talking face to face"
gives us enormous courage
to overcome obstacles in our way.