Three, two, one!
-Cheese!
ADAPTED FROM ZHU YI'S NOVEL,
SHE'S A LITTLE CRAZY, ON JJWXC.NET
-Kiss!
We're All Grown Up Now.
My...
My son left his test paper here
and asked me to pick it up.
I see.
Is your son in Grade 12 too?
Yes, Grade 12.
Well, Grade 12 students
have tight schedules,
so he asked me to get it for him.
I'm sure.
He's definitely not a student's parent.
He said his son is in Grade 12,
but he headed for the Grade 11 building.
And he looked sneaky and guilty.
A lot of things have gone missing lately.
It must be his doing.
The lock on the west gate is broken.
It hasn't been fixed yet.
And he came from that direction.
There is a good chance
he will leave from there.
Sirs, please go catch him.
Go check it out.
I'll leave first.
Let me know if anything happens, sir.
Gu Ran?
You have no idea
how good my sixth sense is.
I could tell he was not a good man,
so I was extra cautious.
You're not an idiot.
You didn't expose him to his face.
Of course.
I've reached my house. Bye.
Jiang Jia.
You actually have a lot of strengths.
Like what?
You're brave
and always righteous.
You're calm and not reckless.
It took you two nights
to make that up, didn't it?
No.
When we talk about strengths,
people always immediately think
of extraordinary intelligence
and innate talent.
We believe
everyone possesses courage and composure.
That's actually not true.
Does everyone stand up
when they see injustice?
No.
Does everyone empathize with the weak?
Also no.
Your uncommon bravery and righteousness
are really hard to come by.
Aren't they strengths?
You're such a sweet talker.
Tell me more next time.
You enjoy the praise, don't you?
JIANG JIA, GRADE 12, CLASS 2
TARGET FIELD OF STUDY, REPORTER
TEACHING BUILDING B
Are you aiming for East China University?
Yes.
That's the same as Lurang.
He told me that he wants to go there too.
Let me look at your report card.
If you want to go there,
you need to get at least 110 in math
even if you can score
consistently above 135 in English.
You still need to work harder in math.
Feel free to ask me
if you have trouble with math.
Okay. Thank you, Mr. Lin.
By the way,
English is your strong suit.
Taking the autonomous admission exam
will give you an advantage.
Although East China University
is not included,
there are still some good schools.
Bring it home and take a look.
2015 CHENGJING UNIVERSITY
AUTONOMOUS ADMISSION INTERVIEW
AUTONOMOUS ADMISSION EXAM
Excuse me.
Do you have a pen?
-Hold on.
-Thank you.
2015 CHENGJING UNIVERSITY
AUTONOMOUS ADMISSION INTERVIEW
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Which school are you from?
Jiangyi's First High School.
What about you?
I'm from Suyang No. 1 High School.
Suyang No. 1 High School?
Then do you know Zhang Lurang
in Grade 12?
Zhang Lurang?
I get it.
Zhang Lurang was studying in Jiangyi
before he transferred.
It must be your school.
He sure has a lot of influence.
Do you know anything else about him?
Not really.
He usually keeps a low profile.
Are you trying
to find out his phone number?
I can't help you with that.
He doesn't even accept gifts from girls.
He seems completely focused on studying.
You should give up on him.
You are
really obsessed with him, aren't you?
This photo editing looks so real.
My deskmate did the same too.
But his eyes turned out crooked.
Next, Su Zaizai.
Is Su Zaizai here?
I'm coming.
Good luck.
AUTONOMOUS ADMISSION EXAM
I was a bit nervous at first.
But I felt better after a while.
I answered all of the teachers' questions.
I'm glad to hear that.
Zaizai, what time is your bus?
Gu Ran, Guan Fang, and I
are eating near the bus station.
We can pick you up.
There are still more than two hours
before the bus leaves from Suyang.
That gives me time
to visit Rangrang's school while I'm here.
But he can't use his phone.
He won't know you're there.
Gu Ran, don't eavesdrop.
It's not eavesdropping
if you're on speaker.
It doesn't matter if he doesn't know.
I just want to take a look.
I have to go now. Bye.
SUYANG NO. 1 HIGH SCHOOL
TENTH PLACE, ZHANG LURANG
HONOR ROLL
Sir.
Can you help me take a picture?
You're not from this school, are you?
No, I'm not.
But my friend studies here.
Then I'll make sure I take a nice photo.
You can send it to him later.
Thank you.
Don't stand there.
Pictures come out better
with the view over there.
It's okay.
I'll stand here.
TENTH PLACE, ZHANG LURANG
Thank you.
Su Zaizai.
Rangrang?
It's not the weekend. Why are you here?
Gu Ran called Luli and said
you came to our school.
I happened to be nearby.
So I rushed over
to see if you were still here.
Gu Ran sure sends news fast.
It has been a while. I...
We miss you.
It has been a while.
You mentioned the school in your letters.
Now that I've come to see it,
it feels as if I've been here before.
It's mystifying.
Do you want to look inside?
Rangrang, is that the tree
that you said is even older than us?
Actually, there is
nothing special about it.
It's just that when I just arrived,
I wanted to tell you about everything.
Then you should write more.
I don't mind reading it.
Gu Ran said you're here
for an autonomous admission interview.
Yes.
My current grades are not good enough
to get into East China University.
I think I should play it safe.
That's good too.
Rangrang, I didn't expect you
to be so popular in Suyang too.
They must be wondering who I am
and why I am with you.
Rangrang,
I took the autonomous admission interview
not because I wanted
to give up on East China University.
I just don't want
to gamble everything on the NCEE
and make everyone worry about me.
After I get back to Jiangyi,
I'll study even harder.
But whether we can get
into the same university or not,
you should pursue your own goals.
Let's not give up our dreams
for other people.
I don't like that.
Becoming better together
is the coolest thing.
All right.
You too.
No matter what the result is,
it's okay if we give it our best.
100 DAYS TO THE NCEE!
Before we begin,
I have two pieces of good news to share.
Our class's Xu Mingliang
has passed and received
a guaranteed admission offer
from the University of South China.
Also, Wang Nan,
Su Zaizai, and Chen Min
have passed the autonomous admission exam.
You can say your hard work has paid off.
Congratulations.
Okay, let's start our lesson.
Don't you think
it's too early to give up now?
As long as you work hard,
you can always find the answers
to the textbooks' problems.
But you will encounter
many difficult problems
in your life in the future.
Those have no standard answers.
Of course, you may not understand
what I'm saying now.
But years later,
you will definitely miss this hot summer.
So students,
let's cheer up
and don't do anything you will regret.
It's never too late
to start working hard.
Now is the best moment.
Rangrang, Mr. Lin is indeed your uncle.
His words
have ignited passion in all of us.
I've never felt so motivated before.
Rangrang, this will be my last letter.
As the NCEE approaches,
time suddenly feels like sand
slipping through my fingers,
gone in the blink of an eye.
I've even been eating
a lot faster.
GUAN'S DESSERT SHOP
Stop studying. Quick.
Eat your food.
Eat some wontons.
I'm really tired.
But when I think
that you're also working hard
someplace else,
I feel like I can keep persevering.
I have good news.
My math scores
have been consistently above 100.
Rangrang, I believe in miracles again.
TO ZHANG LURANG
See? You clearly can do it.
Luli.
Lurang.
Sometimes, taking one more step forward
doesn't seem to be that difficult.
The countdown in our class
is updated every day.
Throwing coins into the wishing fountain
has become a popular trend in the school.
I don't believe in these things.
But I think that if you were here,
you would be enthusiastic about it.
So I decided to throw a coin as well.
Many people attribute this experience
to life-changing significance.
But I just hope...
FROM ZHANG LURANG TO SU ZAIZAI
...you won't let your efforts go to waste.
Su Zaizai,
the mimosa flowers are about to bloom.
Candidates, please cooperate
and go through identity verification
and security checks.
SUBJECT: LITERATURE
SUBJECT: MATHEMATICS
SUBJECT: COMPREHENSIVE LIBERAL ARTS
SUBJECT: ENGLISH
The exam is over.
Candidates, please stop
writing immediately.
If any candidate continues
to answer questions,
proctors will stop them
and issue a warning.
THE FIRST HIGH SCHOOL
AFFILIATED TO JIANGYI UNIVERSITY
2015 GRADUATION CEREMONY
FOR THE FIRST HIGH SCHOOL
AFFILIATED TO JIANGYI UNIVERSITY
-Let's take a picture together.
-Okay.
Let's take another one. Hey!
Su Zaizai, let's take a picture.
-Here.
-Sure.
I wasn't ready.
Hey.
I've taken pictures with them.
Let's take one.
You did? Okay.
Okay, all done.
Wait a minute.
My eyes were closed.
Let's take one more.
Fine.
There you go.
It's blurry. Let's take another one.
For a guy,
why are you so fussy about a picture?
No more.
Guan Fang, let's take a picture.
-No!
-Come on. Let's take another one.
You're so annoying!
Quick. Just one more.
-No.
-What are you doing?
Stop it.
-Go away.
-It looks nice.
Let's take another one.
-Please.
-Let's do it.
Okay.
How about the three of us together?
Hello, Rangrang.
-Let's take one more!
-Guess where we are now.
-At school?
-You deserved that.
It's the graduation ceremony.
All the graduates are here.
It's strange though.
Today, I'm suddenly reluctant
to leave the school
that I used to be sick of.
And the stern dean
has been smiling all day today.
Rangrang,
happy graduation.
Su Zaizai.
Happy graduation.
-Lurang!
It has been so long! This is so sudden.
I wanted to come back
for your graduation ceremony.
You're a great friend.
You've gotten thinner.
But you're still just as handsome.
Zhang Lurang, perfect timing.
Let me take a group photo for you.
Good idea. Come on.
Come.
Stand closer together.
I'll start counting.
Three.
Two.
One.
-Cheese!
I'm not bragging here.
Grandma's new pineapple shaved ice
is really amazing.
You guys have to try it.
Grandma, Gu Ran and the others are here.
GUAN'S DESSERT SHOP
Grandma?
Grandma.
Did she go out?
But the shop isn't locked up.
Guan Fang!
Hurry to the hospital.
Your grandma fell and was unconscious.
The ambulance left just a while ago.
Sir, which hospital?
-The People's Hospital.
-Thank you!
GUAN'S DESSERT SHOP
Excuse me.
How is the elderly person
who was just brought in?
-I'm her family.
-They're still conducting tests.
How is she now?
We're currently trying
to contact Chen Lan's family.
Okay.
I'm Chen Lan's family.
Ranran, what are you doing here?
Mom,
he's my friend.
Where are your parents?
It's just me. She's my grandma.
Ms. Chen, how is his grandma doing?
The preliminary diagnosis
is a ruptured spleen
and hemorrhagic shock.
She's undergoing some tests.
She needs immediate surgery.
I'll explain the procedure
and risks of the surgery to you first.
Then you can sign the consent form.
Come with me.
We'll wait here.
And then complications may arise,
such as bleeding,
gallbladder dysfunction,
bile duct stricture,
and hepatic dysfunction.
This is a common surgery, right?
Yes.
Are there risks during the surgery?
All surgeries have risks
and various unexpected situations
may occur.
But we'll do our best.
Thank you.
What else can I do?
You're already doing a great job
staying calm at your age.
After you sign this,
you can wait outside the operating room.
SIGNATURE OF NEXT OF KIN
I'll sign it right away.
SIGNATURE OF NEXT OF KIN: GUAN FANG
Mom.
The surgery has been quite successful.
Your grandma will come out soon.
But further observation is still needed.
Thank you, doctor.
Everything is okay now.
Thank you.
If you're sleepy, take a nap.
It's okay.
I'm not sleepy.
She woke up at noon.
But she's still feeling weary.
She dozed off quickly.
I'm glad she's awake.
We won't be going inside then.
We should let her get more rest.
Remember to pay the fees
and collect the medication.
Okay, thank you.
You look like you haven't slept all night.
You should get some sleep.
I know my way around.
We can handle the little things for you.
Yes. You probably haven't eaten either.
Rangrang and I will buy you some food.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Go.
It has only been just a few days.
But your wrinkles have increased a lot.
Why don't we buy
those toners or creams
mentioned on television
that disappear wrinkles immediately
after use?
Let's see if they work.
It would be great if they did work.
Grandma?
You're awake.
I thought
I heard Gu Ran and the others talking.
Yes, they will be here later.
Is the graduation ceremony over?
Mr. Chen said they waited
outside the school entrance
on their children's graduation day.
I didn't even know.
And I couldn't go to pick you up.
Your high school graduation ceremony
only happens once.
I had planned to close the shop early
to attend it.
But in the end,
I couldn't make it.
Instead, you ended up coming
to the hospital
and having to bustle around.
Time really flies.
I always felt
like you were shorter than me yesterday.
But in the blink of an eye,
you've grown so much.
You've become an adult.
Grandma,
come send me off
when the university semester starts.
And when I find a job,
you can pick me up and drop me off.
By then,
I probably won't be able to walk anymore.
Then
I'll be the one who picks you up.
If that doesn't work,
I'll carry you on my back.
That would be so tiring.
But when I was little,
didn't you always carry me like that too?
Good.
Good boy.
Can she be discharged now?
I'll do the discharge paperwork in a bit.
That's great.
Have you seen how well Guan Fang
has been taking care of her?
My mom used to compare me only to Lurang.
Now, great.
She will use Guan Fang too.
I always thought
I would become an adult
once I turned 18.
But recently, I've suddenly realized
that being an adult
means taking on responsibility.
My grandma has had a hard life.
It's my turn to protect her from now on.
I'm really glad to have you guys here.
That means adults also need friends.
Yes, they do.
Because only with friends around
can adults
temporarily not act like adults.
The evening after the rain
is so beautiful.
The weather tomorrow will be nice.
Yes, I'm sure it will be.
Rangrang, I'm home.
You should go back and rest early.
Su Zaizai.
The weather
will be nice tomorrow.
You mentioned it earlier.
So
will you be free?
I'm really going to graduate.
I just realized
how reluctant I am to leave.
Actually, there is one thing
in high school
that I have always regretted.
That is,
I never had the chance
to experience being in the same class
as Rangrang.
It's such a pity.
I wanted to sit next to him
and spend 12 hours with him every day
from morning to evening.
Then I would pretend
to borrow a pen from him.
And I would look over...
Rangrang, what are you doing here?
What are you recording?
I'm recording precious memories
of our high school graduation.
Then did you record it?
Yes, I did.
Thank you, Rangrang.
At this moment,
we are deskmates.
How nice!