Three, two, one!
-Cheese!
ADAPTED FROM ZHU YI'S NOVEL,
SHE'S A LITTLE CRAZY, ON JJWXC.NET
-Kiss!
On Doomsday, I Want to Tell You...
Over here.
Let me help you.
What did you pack in here? It's so heavy.
Just some souvenirs.
Be careful. Don't break anything.
Will we be arriving after 12 a.m.?
Yes.
Have you forgotten
what today's date is?
It's the 20th today.
After midnight, it's doomsday!
Is it really doomsday today?
Suddenly, I feel
that this train ride is different.
What are you doing?
Texting my grandma
to tell her it's doomsday today.
Our fate
as grandparent-grandchild ends here.
In the next life,
I want to be her grandson again.
Did she reply to you?
Yes.
What did she say?
"You little rascal."
It feels like we're wandering
at the world's end now.
Could it be
that only this train
will escape doomsday?
It seems like I can't hide this
from you after all.
To be honest, this train is heading
to Hogwarts.
Hogwarts?
What's that?
Seriously? You Muggle!
Muggle?
What's a Muggle? Is it tasty?
What time is it?
Why is your shoulder next to my head?
Excuse me?
Clearly, you rested your head
on my shoulder.
I don't even get a thank you.
Thank you.
It's already 11:55 p.m.
There are five minutes left.
Why do I feel more anxious
as we get closer to midnight?
If...
I mean, hypothetically speaking,
if it's really doomsday in five minutes,
what should we do?
Then
let's leave something behind at least.
In the final five minutes,
each of us will get one minute
to say something.
I'll go first.
It's the final minute.
Let me summarize my life as Guan Fang.
I used to be clueless
and had a distorted understanding
of this world.
Then I met a group of people,
including everyone here,
who truly changed me
and reshaped me.
I really like the person I've become now.
Sit properly!
It's the final minute.
Actually, I have no regrets.
Well, there is one.
I couldn't fly to the US
to watch a basketball game.
It's a shame that I couldn't see Kobe.
Stop exaggerating and scaring yourselves.
I'm an optimistic person.
I have really good luck.
Whenever I buy a soda,
I always get an extra bottle.
When I play claw machines,
I always get the one I want the most.
So as long as I'm here,
this train will reach its destination.
I'll let you have my final minute.
I don't need it.
Then I...
I hope this world
can split up with doomsday.
Then there won't be doomsday anymore.
Then we'll still have thousands
and millions of minutes
to build a future
with the most important people
in our lives.
Everyone, there are 13 seconds left.
Ten seconds.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
-Six.
-Five.
-Four.
-Three. Two.
-One.
-Nothing happened.
-We're safe.
We're okay!
Yes!
It's okay now.
We survived doomsday together.
I'll tell you guys a secret.
I just saved the world.
But you have no idea.
You've been watching
too many science fiction movies.
Now it's a new day, right?
It's another day of school.
That's even scarier than doomsday!
THE FIRST HIGH SCHOOL
AFFILIATED TO JIANGYI UNIVERSITY
Question number five
should be in the past tense
based on the context,
so the answer is C.
All right.
That's all for today's class.
Class is dismissed.
No homework?
Did she forget?
Miss, you haven't assigned
English homework yet.
Why did she have to bring it up?
The academic competition just ended.
I won't assign homework for this weekend.
You need to take breaks from studying too,
so get some rest.
Next week, we'll hit the ground running
and prepare for the final exams.
Do you want to play basketball?
Guan Fang,
I'm busy tonight.
Can we switch our duties today?
I'll cover your shift on Monday.
Okay, no problem.
Thank you, man. I'll get going.
Bye.
I guess I can't play ball.
Do you believe it
when I say Wang Hao will leave
faster than anyone else next Monday?
Guan Fang is just too easygoing.
He always thinks
it's better to avoid trouble.
If it were me...
What would you do?
I would verbally agree
and pretend nothing happened.
In any case, Ms. Zhang would hold
the one on duty accountable,
not me.
We have to teach
such an opportunist a lesson.
You and your evil ideas.
Guan Fang is easygoing.
It's not something bad.
Being easygoing is fine,
but being too easy is not good for him.
I made some observations.
Liu Quan threw his basketball
into the drain yesterday.
It was a newly-bought ball.
He treasured the ball very much.
But he didn't get angry.
Also, his deskmate, Li Ming,
always spins his pen.
Every now and then,
the ink stains his clothes.
He doesn't react at all.
Really?
From the day I knew him,
I've never seen him
initiate a conflict with anyone.
It doesn't seem good for him.
It makes him an easy target for bullying.
Tomorrow, we're going
to his place to eat, right?
We can give him a word of advice then.
I told Xiaofang to invite you over,
but you guys never came.
I thought it was
because my cooking was bad.
How could that be, Mrs. Guan?
Your cooking is far better than my mom's.
Just tell me what you want to eat.
Thank you, Mrs. Guan.
GUAN'S DESSERT SHOP
Excuse me!
Your food is spoiled.
How can you sell it?
Spoiled? That's impossible.
Are you saying we're falsely accusing you?
Grandma,
you can carry on.
Get back to work.
GUAN'S DESSERT SHOP
Please calm down.
Our ingredients
are delivered on the same day.
This has never happened before.
We also ordered the mango pomelo sago.
There's no problem at all.
If I say this is spoiled,
it's spoiled.
How about this?
Your check is waived.
How about that?
We ate something at your place today.
If it gives us food poisoning,
we'll have to go to the hospital.
What are you going to do
about the medical expenses?
You're clearly trying to extort money.
Watch what you're saying!
You shouldn't go too far.
Well, sirs.
Buy something to eat and drink
to nourish your health.
You're a sensible kid.
I'll see you two off.
You guys can carry on eating.
Give me back the money.
What?
Give the money back.
There's no reason for us
to give the money back to you.
Is there something wrong with you?
You need a beating.
What?
What are you trying to do?
Give it back.
Why is he not back yet?
Could Guan Fang be getting bullied?
It's possible.
Those two people look like bullies.
I'll go and check.
Sir,
it's our first time doing this.
We were out of our minds.
We won't do it next time.
We'll avoid your shop next time.
Next time?
No, there won't be a next time.
We promise.
Yes.
Hey! What are you doing?
How much money could a student have?
That's enough.
Sorry, sir.
We were wrong.
-Let's talk it out.
-We were wrong.
Just don't hit us.
Don't just stand there. Apologize to him.
-I'm sorry. We won't do it next time.
-I'm sorry.
That's more like it.
Listen.
Don't let me see you guys around the shop.
-Do you hear me?
-Don't worry.
Get lost!
Gu Ran is so imposing.
I didn't expect you to be so capable.
Are you okay?
It's nothing.
These guys are so weird.
They suddenly acted
like they were being bullied.
Look,
you shouldn't be scared
of people like them.
Just look at me.
Did you see how scared they were?
But they're too timid.
I didn't even hit them.
They're cowards
who have never seen the world.
Thank you.
Grandma, I'm back.
Xiaofang, come here.
Why are you so serious?
Did you get into a fight again today?
Grandma, what are you thinking?
I'm not someone who loves to fight.
I'm glad to hear that.
I'm genuinely worried.
You used to come home
with injuries all over your face.
You would get new injuries
on top of the old injuries.
That was such a long time ago.
I was young and ignorant at the time.
Grandma, please stop bringing up my past.
Jiang Jia and Su Zaizai teased me
for over a week about my bed-wetting.
Don't bring it up anymore.
I'm glad you didn't fight.
But your friends now are pretty nice.
I like them.
You should be more like them.
I don't want you
to be who you were before.
Grandma, don't worry.
I won't.
You must be hungry.
I made stewed ribs for you.
It's your favorite.
Come and get some.
TEACHING BUILDING B
Wang Hao.
Didn't you switch duties with Guan Fang?
Aren't you going to clean?
Guan Fang, unfortunately,
my relatives are visiting today.
How about you do the duty today?
I'll return the favor next time.
What do you think?
I can go home later.
Well,
I'll stay for duty
and go home after that.
You can go now.
I don't have much homework today.
I'll come and help out before going home.
Okay, Grandma, don't worry.
I'll be right there. I'm hanging up now.
Buddy,
he was the one who took our money.
Were you the one
who picked on my friends?
It was him.
Did you ask me before you did that?
Okay.
Wait!
I dare you to leave.
If you leave, we'll go to your grandma.
It's called Guan's Dessert Shop, right?
That old woman
is pretty old.
It wouldn't be unusual
if she stumbles or bumps into things.
Yes.
-What are you doing?
-Do you dare?
What do you want?
I'm not exaggerating.
Guan Fang has clearly changed.
It's not just about the duty.
Someone tried to take over
our basketball court today
and he didn't let them.
He won a game and took it back.
If it were before,
he would have let it go.
This shows
that what we taught Guan Fang
is effective.
That's right.
We've essentially saved his future.
That's noble.
Get him!
Do you want to escape?
Beat him!
I...
This is not just a change.
He has practically transformed.
Help him out!
I apologize for what I said before.
Gu Ran didn't teach you.
Instead, you should teach him.
GUAN'S DESSERT SHOP
If I had known
he was so good at this,
I wouldn't have joined in the fight.
Luckily, we found out in time
or else it would be embarrassing for us
to teach you more nonsense.
At first,
I didn't want you guys to find out.
It's nothing to be proud of.
You could say it was what you would call
a rebellious stage.
It was in the eighth grade.
At that time, I just felt
learning those dry subjects was useless.
I just wanted to make a name
for myself with my fists.
I mistook immaturity for brotherhood.
My temper would explode
at the slightest provocation.
Listen closely.
If I ever see you
messing with my friend again,
I'll beat you up every time I see you.
I'm not exaggerating.
At that time, almost no one at school
wanted to have anything to do with me.
Even the teachers
thought I was a troublemaker.
The most common phrase
I heard back then was,
"One bad apple
spoils the whole barrel."
Look at you.
You can't even stand or sit properly.
Stand here properly as punishment.
To prevent myself
from spoiling their precious barrel,
I started skipping school even more.
Maybe it wasn't just rebellion.
I was already a bad person.
So was what those hooligans did
something that you used to do?
You're quite legendary.
But looking back now,
I was so full of myself back then.
I thought I was tough and cool.
When I skipped PE class,
my parents gave me a beating.
Didn't your grandma punish you?
Right. Why did you eventually change?
Later, I suddenly realized...
Just leave.
Sorry.
The so-called invincibility
that I thought I had
was because someone
was silently facing
the consequences for me.
I caused trouble.
She apologized.
I don't know when it started
to become a given.
Mrs. Guan, I'll be honest with you.
No school would dare
to accept a student like Guan Fang.
We've given him so many chances.
But he keeps repeating his mistakes.
We truly have no other choice,
but to advise him to drop out.
Miss, you're right.
But Xiaofang
was a really good kid when he was young.
I'll try and talk to him again.
He used to listen to me the most.
-We're in a difficult position here.
-I beg of you.
Please.
-My grandma used to be quite fierce
-He used to listen
-when she was younger.
-to me the most.
She had a reputation in the neighborhood.
I've never seen her pleading
with someone in such a humble way.
Xiaofang, let's go home.
Let's go home.
STUDENT AFFAIRS OFFICE
That was when I realized
that she seemed to have aged a bit.
Xiaofang,
sometimes, I envy you.
You can still study at your age.
You still have opportunities
to do what you like to do.
Actually, fists can't save the world.
You still need to use the pen.
Stop fighting
and focus on studying, okay?
I can't even imagine
how she managed
to bear so much criticism
and calmly discuss the future with me
when she has such a frail body.
That's the end of the story.
After that, I turned over a new leaf
and became a different person.
Well? I used to be quite lost, right?
No, a reformed bad boy is the coolest.
It's super cool.
GUAN'S DESSERT SHOP
Bye, Mrs. Guan.
-Bye, Mrs. Guan.
Goodbye.
GUAN'S DESSERT SHOP
Come on. Let's go home.
Let's head home.
It feels cold all of a sudden.
Let's go.
GUAN'S DESSERT SHOP
Watch your step.
I'm okay.
How fast time flies.
It's another year already.
I only learned today
that you wanted to be a boxing champion
when you were young.
As you said, that was when I was young.
I'm a lot older now.
Do you blame me
for being too strict with you back then?
How could I?
As you said, that was when I was young.
I'm a lot older now.
Yes, you'll be another year older soon.
Do you still have any dreams now?
Yes.
I hope...
I hope you can continue to accompany me
for a very long time.
"With lowered head
and skillful fingers playing endlessly,
talking about countless things.
Slowly...
Slowly plucking and strumming.
Plucking and strumming..."
"The emperor will no longer
attend the morning court."
"The emperor..."
What? Don't mess around.
You have an exam in ten minutes.
Can you memorize it all?
I'll memorize as much as I can.
This cold air is like a natural energizer.
I'll no longer believe
those study methods online.
What methods?
They say that knowledge
will enter your brain
if you sleep with books as your pillow.
I slept on the books all night.
Then what happened?
I woke up with a stiff neck.
Let's go.
It's about time.
Good luck.
-Bye.
-Rangrang.
Good luck.
You too.
Stop studying. Let's go.
Rangrang,
when are you going back to Suyang?
Tomorrow.
That's so soon.
Take these.
What about you?
I'm not cold.
Your gloves are surely different.
I don't feel cold at all.
You're exaggerating.
What's wrong?
We'll be apart for a month
once you go back to Suyang.
Every glance counts now.
I have to make good use of my time
and look at you more.
It's only a month.
Relationships between people
need maintenance.
Even just a week without contact
can cause the feelings to fade.
I don't want the first thing I say to you
when you come back to be,
"It has been a long time.
Do you still remember me?"
So I'll text you.
I'll take the initiative to keep in touch
since I'm used to it anyway.
Well, I'll go now.
I'll reply to you.
I will reply to your text messages.
It's a deal then.
It's snowing.
It's the first snowfall.
I noticed that when the world
created grandmas,
it seemed to follow a fixed formula.
Thank you, Grandma.
Grandmas' sliced apples
always have
the subtle flavor of green onions.
Grandmas always hunch over,
yet their steps are steady.
Grandmas' bright white aprons
are tidy and clean.
Come and have some.
Have some fruit.
Grandmas always think
we never have enough to eat.
Here you go.
We still have grapes.
Here.
Enjoy yourselves.
Grandmas' living spaces are small,
too small to fit large furniture.
Yet they are also spacious.
They are spacious enough
to encompass our entire childhood.
I kind of miss my grandma,
but I dare not tell Dad
because I know
he misses his mom too.
I KIND OF MISS MY GRANDMA,
BUT I DARE NOT TELL DAD
BECAUSE I KNOW HE MISSES HIS MOM TOO