Three, two, one!
-Cheese!
ADAPTED FROM ZHU YI'S NOVEL,
SHE'S A LITTLE CRAZY, ON JJWXC.NET
-Kiss!
Copy and Paste, I've Learned It.
WELCOME TO EAST CHINA UNIVERSITY!
FALL ORIENTATION
WELCOME, NEW STUDENTS
Rangrang, my parents have headed home.
I'm in the registration area.
What about you?
I am on my way to the dorm
after getting my student ID.
I'll see you tonight.
Go straight ahead and turn right.
Have a great semester!
Excuse me.
Where do I report
to the College of Foreign Languages?
Are you an English major?
How did you know?
It was just a guess.
I didn't expect to be right.
I am a sophomore in English.
I'm going to the registration area too.
I'll take you there.
Okay.
-I'll get that.
-Thank you.
Block C is just ahead.
You're very lucky.
Cafeteria 3 is right outside Block C.
It's our university's best cafeteria.
Will there be stir-fried tomatoes
with watermelon?
What?
I saw it on the university forum
over the summer.
It's said to be a disgusting dish.
That's not really true.
However,
we have stir-fried pineapple
with cilantro.
I'm just kidding. It's a joke.
By the way,
is the College of Engineering dorm
also around here?
The College of Engineering?
I think it should be Block F.
Do you have friends there?
I'll let you settle in. I'll go now.
Thank you.
Hi, I'm Su Zaizai.
I'm Zhang Xiaoxiao.
Your bed is next to mine.
Hi, I'm Deng Qin.
I'm Chen Xin.
Allow me.
You all arrived so early.
It's so unfair.
The guy who escorted you here is so nice.
The one who accompanied me
was promoting phone cards the whole time.
Just be content.
I had no escort
and my luggage broke.
It took me half an hour
to lug my luggage here.
You're a warrior.
I've arrived at my dorm. What about you?
I've arrived too!
Rangrang, when I was walking here,
I noticed that the path
from my dorm to your dorm
is a heart shape.
East China University is different indeed.
Even the routes are thoughtfully designed.
Rangrang, which dorm are you in?
210.
Gosh, you're really incredible.
My bed looks like a doghouse
no matter what I do.
Zhang Lurang,
I saw the registration form just now.
Are you from Jiangyi?
We're from the same hometown.
What a coincidence.
What about you? Where are you from?
Me?
I am a local.
Just ask me if you have any questions
about the area.
I know all the places
for good food and fun.
Okay.
Rangrang, go to your balcony.
Rangrang!
Zhang Lurang, are you free tonight?
How about dinner together?
Sorry, I have a date.
I saw this on the forum over the summer.
Many university students
have mentioned this restaurant.
Luckily, we came early.
If we had arrived any later,
we wouldn't have gotten a table.
Listen,
the beef noodle I ordered
is the signature dish here.
Why do you seem
to know all about this place?
Of course.
Trying all the yummy food here with you
is at the top of my to-do list.
I'll get two bottles of yogurt drinks.
Here are your noodles. Enjoy it hot.
Thank you.
Luckily, they didn't add cilantro
or it would take forever to pick out.
Excuse me.
Would you like to have your photo taken
as a memento
for our tenth-anniversary event?
Okay.
Are you ready?
All right.
One,
two,
three.
MAYBE IT'S THE SPECIAL SOUP
OR THE PERSON
WHO IS PEEKING AT MY WRITING.
What did you write?
COPY AND PASTE
"Copy and paste."
Don't you know it?
Copy and paste means
I agree with your actions and words.
Have you learned it,
Rangrang?
Rangrang, look.
There is a food street
one block over from this one.
A forum post recommended
a candied hawthorn shop.
I'll take you there next time.
But military training starts tomorrow.
I don't know when we'll get to come out.
That's right, Rangrang.
The next few days will be very sunny.
Make sure to use sunblock.
Otherwise, you will get a dark tan.
No.
You won't remember.
I've decided.
I'll remind you every day.
What happens if I get a tan?
If you get a tan,
I'll have to get a tan with you.
Otherwise,
we won't be a good match.
Rangrang,
I heard them say
that this military training
will also have a singing activity.
Do you remember "Secret,"
the song I wanted to sing to you
in our freshman year of high school?
It's too bad I didn't get to sing it.
I'll have to practice this time.
You were so talkative just now.
But suddenly,
you're so quiet.
I felt like you were coming closer to me,
so I couldn't hold back.
What couldn't you hold back?
To take advantage of you.
Su Zaizai,
I've learned that thing
that you mentioned today.
What?
Copy
and paste.
The first floor?
I really envy you.
Our dorm is on the fifth floor
and there is no elevator.
I think
I'll be slim
after a semester of taking the stairs.
Isn't that great?
You can lose weight.
Don't take it too far.
By the way, I heard
that it has cooled down in your area.
It will be a nice few days
during your military training.
It's nothing compared to what you have.
You're in the same university
as Zhang Lurang.
You must wake up laughing
from your dreams.
Copy
and paste.
Your colleges are not too far apart.
You can kiss once in a while.
What kiss? Don't talk nonsense!
I mean that you can visit him in person.
Zaizai, have you two made any progress?
Tell me more about it.
My roommates are back.
I'll hang up now. Bye.
Zaizai,
are you not feeling well?
Your face is so red.
No.
The air conditioning isn't on.
I'm a bit hot.
So our school does have handsome guys.
Look, it's the guy who escorted you.
All present!
Attention!
March in place!
One,
two.
One.
All present.
Stand still!
You,
step forward.
Everyone else, continue!
-Do it one more time.
-One!
Two!
One!
Do you realize that you're marching
with the same hand and foot?
-Sir.
-Two!
-Speak.
-One!
I can overcome it.
Two!
Every year, there are indeed
a few uncoordinated souls.
I didn't mean you.
One!
Two!
Isn't she cute?
-One!
-Yes, she is.
Two!
One!
I don't think you can do it yourself.
-Two!
-I'll get someone to help you.
-One!
-Xie Linnan!
One!
Linnan,
were you also under Mr. Wu last year?
I was also uncoordinated.
One!
He spent a week correcting my march.
I ended up as a flag raiser.
One!
Why do you think he asked me to help you?
He knows I have the experience.
Two!
One!
Your stance is very problematic.
Practice the fixed stance first.
Condition a reflex to lift your left leg
as you raise your right arm.
Hang in there.
One!
Two!
Good.
Xie Linnan is quite a good teacher.
Keep it up.
Mr. Wu,
the chief instructor wants a word.
Mr. Li asked me to inform you.
All right, I got it.
Keep practicing.
Here.
Replenish your energy.
I'll just have this.
Rangrang,
I finally realized what it means
for a day to feel like a year.
I'm exhausted.
I wish I had jelly right now.
They are also milk-flavored.
It would be even more perfect
if there was chocolate cake.
Rangrang,
are you a magician?
Well, I also want a yogurt drink.
It's plain.
Peanut candy?
Mutton skewers?
I'll buy some now.
I'm just kidding with you.
I can't eat that much.
Rangrang,
is your bag actually Doraemon's pocket?
Why does it have everything?
I didn't know what you wanted to eat,
so I bought all your favorites.
Let me see what else you have.
What is this?
During military training,
I saw that your shoes were too big,
so I bought you a pair of insoles.
This will give you more support
and make you more comfortable.
Rangrang,
you're the best.
It has only been a day
and my skin has gotten a shade darker.
Don't worry.
Winter will make you fair again.
What are you looking at?
The military training photos
on the online forum.
I spotted a few handsome guys.
Unfortunately, they aren't
as hot as the guys in our college.
My gosh, this guy is handsome.
He's a new student
in the College of Engineering.
-Let me see.
-He has the looks.
He will be voted
the most handsome man in school.
He's quite handsome.
He is actually...
He's the hot topic on the online forum.
There are requests for his details
on the confession board.
I wonder
who will win his heart in the end.
Actually, he and I...
He's such a perfect guy.
If anyone in our dorm can win his heart,
I'll buy her milk tea for a month.
Me!
I can do it.
I want strawberry milk tea.
Young girl,
you're too young.
Don't say such words so hastily.
Get the milk tea ready.
Watch me in action.
Everyone, rest in place.
CONSTANT SELF-IMPROVEMENT,
RESPONSIBILITY TO ALL
-Go.
-Go quickly.
Zhang Lurang, go for it!
Zhang Lurang!
Su Zaizai.
Play along for a month of milk tea.
Zaizai should be at the dorm.
I'll get a bottle for her.
-Hi, I'll have a ham sandwich.
-I'll have a ham sandwich.
Sorry, there is only one sandwich left.
I came first. Give it to me.
Why? I ordered it first. Give it to me.
I was going to buy this.
I just went to get something else.
Then it's your fault
for going in the wrong order.
There's a saying,
"The order of play decides the winner."
Here, give it to me.
No, give it to me.
Listen, I won't give in to you.
What is wrong with you?
What?
-No way! It's my friend.
Did you two go to high school together?
So were you two a couple already?
I was just kidding with you guys earlier.
Wait.
How could you joke about this?
Listen, I'm very angry now.
Do you know
how bad it feels to be lied to?
Don't be angry.
I'll buy you milk tea.
Milk tea isn't enough.
Unless
you tell us more
about how you met
and how you got together.
I love to hear the love story
of a good-looking couple!
I'll get chips.
I'll get yogurt drinks.
Do I really have to share?
Let me think about it.
I first met him in the summer
before my freshman year of high school.
It was raining
and I was at a tiny mart.
He was soaking in the rain
without an umbrella
and I rudely called him an idiot.
To be honest,
I think it was quite romantic.
Later on, we got together.
What do you mean by that?
You skipped
way too many important parts of the story.
-Have I?
-Haven't you?
For example, who did the pursuing
and in what way?
And who confessed their feelings
and how did you start dating?
You should at least tell us these.
Of course,
it was me.
I dropped all kinds of hints
so many times!
In the end, I got lucky and got him.
Zaizai, you said you got lucky,
but I don't think so.
With the way you like him so passionately,
I think Zhang Lurang could reject anyone
but Su Zaizai.
If I were a guy, I would like you too.
I can't be late
on my first visit to the department.
Rangrang, let's have
dinner together tonight.
All right.
I'll find you after class.
Okay.
NEW MEDIA DEPARTMENT
-Yes, it must be published tomorrow.
-Add the effects here.
-Okay.
-We'll set the publish time tonight.
There is too much in the back.
-Okay.
-I'll add the materials here.
Linnan, a new student is here.
I didn't expect you
to be the first one here.
Linnan.
I'm the president
of the New Media Department.
She's Wu Ling, the vice president.
These are our members.
-Hello.
-Welcome.
Hi, everyone.
It's a bit chaotic, isn't it?
We are not usually like this.
Tomorrow, the school website
will publish a promotional video
made by our department.
For various reasons,
we're working against the clock.
We don't have time
to welcome our new members.
Is there anything I can do to help?
Do you know how to use Photoshop?
Our cover needs to be revised.
-I know a little.
-That's great.
You can use that computer.
I'll tell you what to edit.
The font looks a bit awkward.
Maybe it needs to be softened a bit.
The font size should be smaller as well.
Rangrang,
I just left the department's classroom.
I think it's so fulfilling
to complete something with everyone.
I was afraid
I would be bored outside of class,
but I guess I was worrying too much.
Rangrang, did you also
sign up for a department?
I haven't been there yet.
Rangrang, don't you have a class now?
I can't help but reply to your messages.
Linnan?
What is so important?
You almost ran into the lamppost.
I had to reply to an important message.
Thank you for your hard work today.
There's usually a welcome party
for new students on the first day.
But you had to go straight to work.
I found it quite interesting.
But a party is still necessary.
How about this? Let me buy you dinner.
Consider it a welcome to the department.
Why don't we all get together
when everyone is free?
The more, the merrier.
My roommate is still waiting for me.
I'll get going now. Bye.
What is it?
The university website
just published the promotional video
that we worked on all afternoon yesterday.
Many people have shared it.
The department president sent me the link.
Were you involved in it?
I only edited the cover and font,
but I feel a sense of accomplishment.
A reward for you.
Is that all?
Won't you praise me?
Zaizai, you're amazing.
Right, Rangrang.
I'm going to a seminar in the afternoon
on the East Campus.
Afterward, I have
two advanced English classes,
but I might not get back in time.
Can you go and save a seat for me?
What time?
It's 3:30 p.m. in Room 302.
Rangrang, you're the best.
Xie Linnan is here too.
Did he fail this course?
I don't think so.
He won a scholarship last semester.
He must be here for the credits.
Can you make it back in time?
The class is about to start.
I'm stuck in traffic. I can't be sure.
The numbers are not quite right.
Everyone knows my rules, right?
Five points for each absence from class.
Three absences
result in an automatic failure.
All right.
Let's start with a roll call.
Wang Meng.
Here.
-Xu Liang.
-Here.
Gu Haibo.
Here.
Chen Chen.
Su Zaizai.
-Here.
Do we have students with the same name?
I don't think so
and if I'm not mistaken,
this Su Zaizai
is a girl.
She is absent, isn't she?
I'll record it then.
-Jiang Jiang.
-Here.
-Liu Jun.
Chen Meng.
Su Zaizai.
Linnan?
I'm sorry.
I wanted to cover you for the roll call,
but I didn't expect
someone else would too.
I messed it up for you instead.
It's okay. It's my own fault.
Su Zaizai.
Linnan, I'll get going now.
Let's go.
Rangrang,
did you answer the roll call for me?
You got marked absent
because another guy raised his hand too.
That is
the New Media Department's president.
He also showed me
to the dorm on my first day here.
It's not my fault.
Are you two close?
No.
Rangrang, do you feel threatened now?
I have already had five points deducted
from my normal grade.
I'll be in trouble if it happens again.
Why don't you go to class with me
and supervise me from now on?
Aren't you afraid
your lovely girlfriend will be targeted?
Are you really not afraid?
I'm afraid.
It's clearly the answer I want to hear.
But when you say it,
why do I feel guilty
for having teased you?
Rangrang,
you must have done it on purpose,
yet I love it.
ZHIMING BUILDING
What must come will come.
Who will do
the English presentation this time?
I did it last time.
The usual rules.
You can play slides and videos.
Okay. Give me your flash drive.
I'll take a look first.
I think I forgot to get the flash drive
that I put in your bag last time.
Can you check if it is there?
I have it.
Are you in your dorm?
I'll come and get it.
I happen to be free at the moment.
I'll bring it to you.
Where are you?
You can present from there.
Rangrang.
Hello.
Hi, guys.
The seats up front are nice. Let's go.
The lighting is better there.
Thank you.
You went to class with me last time.
Although I wasn't there,
I'll return the favor
and accompany you this time.
Do you not have class later?
Aren't you doing a presentation?
I'll go after watching your presentation.
When you get back,
check the flash drive.
There is a surprise.
This is a clip
from the film The Shawshank Redemption
that our team used as a source
for this presentation.
This concludes our presentation.
Thank you.
AUTOPLAYING NEXT VIDEO
Rangrang.
Rangrang, I think I like you
a little more today than I did yesterday.
What happened?
I have no idea.
It played automatically.
Why are you so quiet?
It's so embarrassing.
How can I ever face anyone again?
Within a day,
I bet the whole school will know
that a girl expressed her love
for her boyfriend in public.
I would rather live in a tree
than go to class anymore.
How could you laugh?
I think
it's quite cute.
That's because you're not the one
who is embarrassed.
Then
I'll express my love for you
in class next time.
Really?
What are you laughing for?
I just feel
that I like you more today
than I did yesterday.
Rangrang!
-Rangrang!
Su Zaizai, you have become famous.
I know of your heroic deeds
even when I wasn't in that class.
It's all over the school forum.
They say a girl in our school
played a romantic documentary in public.
Now our college has become famous too.
It was an accident.
I didn't know
the next video would automatically play.
How many times have you watched this?
At least five times.
Zhang Lurang, tell us the truth.
Did you do it on purpose today?
I could see it best from off-stage.
You were so close to the computer.
If you wanted to turn it off,
we wouldn't even hear her second sentence.
I was slow to react.
Shoot. I think I really did get a tan.
I hope
the last military training of my life
will pass quickly.
Zaizai, what are you recording?
Do you mean this?
This is my diary.
I've been recording for three years now.
You're so persistent.
After all, I have the dashing Rangrang
as my motivation.
What was that?
Nothing.
That's right, Zaizai.
The counselor said
we can change our clothes and shoes
if they don't fit.
Didn't you say your shoes are too big?
Do you want to come along?
It's okay.
Now, there is
no better fit for me than these shoes.
If a person
knows another person well enough,
his love for that person
must be beyond imagination.