Three, two, one!
-Cheese!
ADAPTED FROM ZHU YI'S NOVEL,
SHE'S A LITTLE CRAZY, ON JJWXC.NET
-Kiss!
I Have Someone Who Listens to My Problems.
Are you not going back
to Suyang this year?
My uncle will be spending
the New Year alone in Jiangyi.
I told my parents
I will keep him company here.
That's great.
We can hang out every day.
This is the fourth year
we've known each other,
but it's our first time
celebrating the New Year together.
It's snowing.
What are you doing?
Last year,
I made a wish when it was snowing
to be with you when it snows this year.
See? It came true.
So I'm making a wish for next year.
What did you wish for?
It won't come true if I say it out loud.
I'll tell you
when it comes true next year.
Rangrang, look at me.
My eyes feel a bit cold.
This way, my eyes won't be cold.
But I can't see,
so you have to hold my hand.
At some moment, I realized
how wonderful it is
to be in love in winter.
Rangrang!
The wind and snow
give us a great excuse to hug.
Thick coats can't hide
the warmth of our heartbeats.
Warming our hands
with the heat from roasted sweet potatoes
is an excuse
just to hold each other's hands.
In spring, we interlock our fingers
-Rangrang!
-through the long sleeves,
spending the time away lazily.
And that seems to be just fine.
When summer rolls around,
it's a new summer.
Rangrang and I will start
to prepare for our internships.
All the best.
He studies aircraft manufacturing.
I don't know anything about that.
I thought it was
just about creating airplanes.
He says
flying is the most romantic pursuit
of humankind.
There is nothing cooler
than being a conductor of air currents.
He seems to glow
when he talks about this.
I suddenly realized
I couldn't let myself fall behind.
Sometimes, when I'm talking
to my friends on the phone,
I feel as if we're back
in high school again.
Jiang Jia passed the interview
for the television station.
She is about to become an intern reporter.
Way to go. That's cool.
Guan Fang is getting ready for graduation.
Why isn't the car here yet?
As for Gu Ran,
he seems to be getting ever busier
with his studies abroad.
He often misses our calls
due to the time difference.
Even when he shows up,
there are dark circles under his eyes.
It's really as we said in the beginning.
Everyone is shining in their own field.
LOVE EAST CHINA,
TRAVEL FAR AND MAKE YOUR MARK
The sycamore trees outside
flourishing once more
mark the long-awaited arrival
of our graduation day.
-Let's see.
-Let me see.
Zaizai, are you sure
about going back to Jiangyi for work?
Yes, I'm going with my boyfriend.
I'm jealous
that you guys get to live at home.
Jiangyi is huge.
My workplace isn't in the same area
as where my parents live.
We plan on renting a place together.
How nice!
-I agree.
-Gather around!
-We'll head over first.
-Bye.
Rangrang, we're going
to take graduation photos now.
You're probably still busy
at the office and can't make it.
I'll tell you a secret.
I look great in this outfit.
I'll send you more pictures.
Zaizai.
Happy graduation.
Rangrang!
Why did you come back?
That's because you're happy.
You would want to share your joy.
That's why I'm here.
Gather around!
Wait here.
Zaizai.
Take this.
Hurry.
Look at the camera.
One, two, three.
-Happy graduation!
I know you've been busy with graduation.
So I took it upon myself
to set all of this up.
See if there is anything you don't like.
How could I not like what you did
with the place?
I have it all thought out.
We'll put up our photos here.
Did you arrange all of this?
Do you want to rearrange anything?
I added all those things myself.
Once you move your stuff in,
this place will actually be our...
Home.
See if we need anything else.
I do think something is missing.
All right. That completes everything.
You seem to match my bed
so well.
I'll unpack your stuff.
Why are you running off?
Are you shy?
I tested the bed.
It's very soft.
Do you want to test it out tonight
with me...
Sure.
If you want to test it out,
why wait until tonight?
I was just kidding.
I'm serious.
This is it.
Let me make an introduction.
This is Su Zaizai,
our Data Department's
new intern translator.
Say hello.
Hello, everyone.
Nice to meet you.
Just call me Zaizai.
-Welcome.
You can sit there.
Our new colleague
looks so young.
Yes. Let's continue.
Go through this part again.
-And this part.
-Okay.
You sure know how to spruce things up.
My boyfriend says
to fill a new environment
with your own things
to have a sense of belonging.
Is there anything I can help with?
Translate this client's information.
Okay.
-This.
-Okay.
Rangrang, I'm getting off work!
I still need a while.
You can head home first.
If it gets too late, don't wait up for me.
Go to sleep early.
The temperature dropped today.
Remember to close the windows.
All right. Good job today.
That's all for today.
We'll continue tomorrow. Get some rest.
-Okay.
-I'm off.
-Bye.
Bye.
Hey, beautiful.
Do you want to go to a cinema
and hold hands in the dark?
I'm exhausted.
Let me recharge.
Rangrang,
why don't I tell you a joke?
I have a sweetheart.
His name is Rangrang.
But unlike his name,
he never rings.
We just came back from the cinema.
May I interview you, Mr. Zhang Lurang?
How would you rate the movie we watched?
100 points.
Why?
The movie itself is 50 points,
but I'll give it 100 points
because of the person who sat beside me.
What pickup line book
has Rangrang been reading?
He has been so cheesy lately.
What are you saying?
I said that the temperature in Jiangyi
has been dropping fast.
It's cold.
Let's hurry home then.
Are you almost all packed?
Well, you can have what I can't take.
-Then the limited-edition games...
-No.
I have a good buddy
who loves games.
I bet he hasn't played much without me.
I'm giving them to him when I get back.
You wrapped that ring
that you bought days ago so nicely.
Is that for your buddy too?
Either way, it's not for you.
I envy you.
I want to go home too.
Hot pot.
Sichuan fish with pickled greens.
Pork knuckles.
I'm hungry. I'm buying food.
Do you want any?
I'll pass. You can go ahead.
Gu Ran!
-Hello!
-Gu Ran, you're still up!
Guan Fang is back in Jiangyi too,
so I figured I would try my luck.
Finally, we all made it to the video call.
Those two are usually absent.
I always make it on time.
Well, I'm packing right now.
Are you coming back soon?
Are you coming back?
When? Do you want me to pick you up?
In a few days,
after I settle everything here.
Don't pick me up. I don't have much stuff.
Okay.
Jiangjiang, are you working?
Yes.
I made an appointment
with the interviewee.
I'm waiting here for them.
PRESS PASS
Winter is so cold this year.
It's colder than last year.
I'm going to be here until night.
I should've worn more layers.
Are you near Tianmen Bridge?
Your background looks so familiar.
I'm right outside the Garden Community.
We often passed by here in high school.
We're almost at our stop.
We have to go.
You guys carry on. Bye!
We'll get together when you get back.
Bye!
Those two mushy lovers.
I need to go too.
I need to help my grandma
buy some meat for the shop.
It's urgent.
I'm hanging up. Bye.
Hey, don't hang up yet.
We want to see her too.
Are you going to tell me
you need to hang up too?
I do have work.
You're so busy. It's good to be busy.
I'll be all right,
all alone in a foreign country.
It's fine.
But I do have some time to spare.
You're not leaving again
after coming back, are you?
No, I'll stay in Jiangyi
to continue my graduate studies.
Then I guess
we'll be seeing each other a lot.
Jiang Jia, come here.
Okay.
I need to get back to work.
I'm hanging up. Bye.
Jiang Jia,
did the interviewee tell you
how much longer they will be?
Let me check.
They're stuck in traffic.
They need another half an hour.
A delivery?
I didn't order anything.
Well, it's for me,
but the kind stranger didn't leave a name.
I'll enjoy it then.
Things will be lively in Jiangyi
after Gu Ran comes back.
In high school,
he and Jiangjiang used to fight
every time they saw each other.
After so many years apart,
they should get along better now.
I think they're actually rather close.
Really? Why?
Intuition.
Su Zaizai?
It really is you!
I thought I got the wrong person.
Wang Nan?
You've become more handsome.
Why are you back?
I'm on vacation.
Are you two...
It is exactly what you think.
Nice going.
-Wang Nan. Come on.
-Yes?
I have to go. Let's talk again soon.
-Bye.
Bye.
Rangrang, you remember him, right?
Yes.
"Handsome," right?
I can't believe you still remember
such a tiny detail.
I've nearly forgotten.
Be honest.
Had you already fallen for me
at that time?
No.
Rangrang, it's super obvious when you lie.
But you still won't admit it.
Tell me. Was it back then?
No.
Was it? I bet it was.
Huo, Huo, Huo
The Huos' martial art fist forms are agile
When we strike, no one can escape
Huo, Huo, Huo
Life flows by in the small town
The courage is still clear
Our true memories
I still remember you
Live on proudly
How long has it been since we last met up?
We can do it more often
now that we're all in Jiangyi.
I heard you got an offer
from a company in Yong'an.
-Are you not taking it?
-I'm not.
I'm young.
I'll have plenty of opportunities.
But right now,
I want to spend more time with my grandma.
Jiangyi is good, isn't it?
You guys are here.
Why are we talking about this?
We're charged by the hour.
Let's keep singing.
Come on!
-Staying up all night
-Talking with you until our livers explode
-Shopping with you
-Till our feet turn flat
-Thank you so much
-For making me live again
-Letting me know once again L, O, V, E
-L, O, V, E
-Come on. Let's drink.
-Cheers.
Can Su Zaizai handle her liquor?
Aren't you going to stop her?
She's enjoying herself. Let her be.
Keep drinking.
-One more.
-No.
How much did they drink?
I swear they only had one glass each.
I didn't know they were such lightweights.
I don't think
she knows it herself.
What's wrong?
I feel awful.
Do you feel awful?
Does your stomach hurt?
My head hurts.
My feet hurt too.
My fingernails hurt too.
I want a hug.
Rangrang.
It's raw.
I'm never letting you drink again.
Shoot. I'm going to be late.
Why don't I give you a ride?
It's okay, Rangrang.
The company will pick me up. I'm off.
Zaizai.
Did you forget something?
You're making me shy.
Fine.
I'm off.
After working on this project for so long,
it's finally coming to an end.
Zhang Lurang,
are you going to today's gathering
that Xiaochen mentioned?
What gathering?
It's actually a group blind date.
Our department has the most singles.
So we contacted the Testing Department
and arranged a dinner gathering.
I'll pass.
We know you have a girlfriend.
Think of it as making new friends.
My girlfriend is away on a work trip.
I need to go home and call her.
Your girlfriend is clingy.
Actually, I'm the clingy one.
All right.
Okay, I'll be leaving first.
You guys go ahead.
Enjoy your weekend.
-Enjoy your weekend.
-Bye.
Countless girls in our company have tried
to get his contact information.
But I've never even seen him waver once.
Also, he always
talks about his girlfriend.
Now I'm really curious
about how his girlfriend looks.
Given Zhang Lurang's personality,
his girlfriend should be
gentle and generous.
Kind and understanding.
Fair and quiet.
Rangrang!
Guess who I ran into.
I passed by the China World Trade Center.
There is an event going on.
The guest is the star in the movie
we watched a few days ago.
Do you remember?
The actor that I said
looks a lot like Guan Fang.
He is even taller in person.
Did you get a photo with him?
No, I was in a hurry.
By the way, Rangrang,
if I open the curtains,
I can see the sea from my hotel room.
The view is spectacular.
Let's stay in this hotel if we come here.
Sure.
There's also
a really good rice noodle shop downstairs.
How does it compare to the place
we frequented in university?
The one near the university is better.
Rangrang,
it's almost time
for my appointment with the client.
I'm kind of nervous.
Is it because
it is your first time meeting a client?
I'm afraid I'll say
the wrong thing when I get nervous.
You'll be fine.
Think about
your first autonomous admission interview,
your debate
in your third year of university,
and your interview with the company.
You were nervous,
but you did well.
You're amazing, Zaizai.
It's amazing that suddenly,
I'm not so nervous anymore.
But I'm a little hungry.
Hungry?
Yes.
We're having dinner
with the partner company.
I heard we'll be having local delicacies,
so I didn't eat much for lunch.
Zaizai, it's time to go.
I'm coming.
Rangrang, I'm hanging up.
Okay, bye. You've got this.
I didn't expect it
to go so smoothly.
I've been working
with this British company
for so many years.
This is the first time
the contract signing went so quickly.
Yes.
It's all thanks
to your connections, Mr. Wei.
Otherwise, negotiations
would have lasted for months.
Here, let me give you a toast, Mr. Wei.
There is no rush.
What you said is not entirely correct.
I think
Ms. Su's fluent translation
was a great help.
Ms. Su is so young
and beautiful.
I didn't expect her professionalism
to be at such a high level.
I just graduated.
It's all thanks to Mr. Chen's guidance.
Isn't it a little cold in here?
I don't think so.
I might be more sensitive to the cold.
Ms. Su,
the wine here is very nice.
Would you like to try some?
How can anyone leave wine in their glass?
Mr. Wei, I'm not good
at holding my liquor.
I ramble when I get drunk.
I wouldn't want
to say something inappropriate
in front of everyone.
But I appreciate your recognition.
Why don't I toast you with tea instead?
No, don't.
You make it seem
as if I'm imposing on you.
Hurry up
and thank Mr. Wei for understanding.
Thank you for your understanding.
Ms. Su,
you don't have to drink the wine,
but the food here
is delicious.
Here.
Thank you, Mr. Wei. I'm not hungry.
She's not hungry.
Ms. Su, since you aren't hungry,
you can go outside and enjoy the view
while we finish our meal.
The view here is wonderful.
-Here.
-Yes.
On this night with an empty stomach,
how I wish someone could come
and take me away from here.