Three, two, one!
-Cheese!
ADAPTED FROM ZHU YI'S NOVEL,
SHE'S A LITTLE CRAZY, ON JJWXC.NET
-Kiss!
You Have Always Been My Favorite.
I should have eaten more at lunch.
Hello.
Can I order food by myself?
Sorry, you have to book a table first.
Do you have a reservation?
Never mind. Thank you.
Zaizai?
Is it over?
No.
Mr. Wei drinks a lot.
I bet it will go on for quite a while.
You must be starving.
I brought a few buns for you.
But they have gone cold.
Thank you.
It's just bad luck
that this happened to you.
Mr. Chen told me you could go home.
If Mr. Wei sees you when he comes out
and starts a drunken rant,
you will be in trouble.
I've been outside for a while.
I should get back inside.
Stay safe.
Okay. Don't worry.
Is it over?
Did everything go well?
Let me guess.
Are you having a celebration party?
Rangrang.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Did you have dinner?
Dinner was extravagant.
We had roasted duck, brined chicken,
candied apple fritters,
and spicy boiled meat slices.
They were all delicious.
If that's the case,
why are you crying?
I saw a bus stop just now
called "Jiangyi Road."
I got homesick all of a sudden.
I'll go to you.
It's late.
Rangrang,
I'll buy a ticket
for the earliest trip home tomorrow.
Rangrang,
I didn't make a mistake, right?
No, you didn't.
It's all right.
I will be all right soon.
My phone is out of battery.
I'll talk to you later.
Rest early.
WHEN YOU ARE LOST,
WHERE YOU STAND IS THE RIGHT DIRECTION
Do you want to get on?
This is the last bus.
If you miss it, you won't get home.
My home isn't around here.
Go home soon.
How I wish
Doraemon's Anywhere Door actually exists.
You are in the wrong in this too.
You have been working for so long.
Can't you handle such social gatherings?
Reflect on it.
Why are you here?
I know you have been mistreated.
So I came to bring you home.
Is it good?
Yes.
Rangrang,
you drove for three hours.
Aren't you tired?
I am.
Do you find me
a lot of trouble?
If I didn't go there,
I wouldn't have slept soundly tonight.
Zaizai,
not everything should be weighed
for its worth in the world.
If it's possible,
I would like you to trouble me more often.
What's wrong?
My mom always says
that words fall on my deaf ears,
going through one ear and out the other.
If I cover my ears,
I can keep your words in mind.
Dig in.
Okay.
I haven't cooked in a while.
Is it too salty?
No, it's even a little sweet.
Maybe the cook
was overloaded with sweetness.
VIP DINING VOUCHER
Tonight?
A friend of mine opened a restaurant.
It's a new restaurant in town.
He wants me to try it out.
I thought it would be boring to eat alone,
so I wanted to see if you are free.
But I have plans tonight
that I can't turn down.
It's all right.
We'll go there another time.
Sure. You can try it out first.
I should hang up now. Bye.
VIP DINING VOUCHER
Hello, Lurang.
Is this the important matter
you mentioned?
For me, eating is a priority in life.
Besides, this is a romantic restaurant
with good online ratings.
It's a romantic restaurant,
but we are here for one thing only.
The food.
Sit down.
Guan Fang?
Gu Ran?
Is this the restaurant you mentioned?
-I came with a friend...
-Jiang Jia!
I have things to discuss. I have to go.
Sure. We'll talk another time.
Was there traffic?
This is rare.
Jiang Jia came to a romantic restaurant
with a guy.
They don't look like a couple.
I have no idea.
Are you done? I need the menu.
Why haven't you confessed to Jiang Jia?
Is it that obvious?
It is very obvious.
Everyone can tell.
Right?
Yes, it's obvious.
I knew it all along.
It's not so easy to tell someone
that you like them.
The type that Jiang Jia likes
is someone like Qianyu.
Kind and thoughtful.
I'm afraid to ask her if she likes me.
I'm even more afraid
to tell her I like her.
Being her good friend
sounds like a nice excuse.
I can turn my heartfelt words into jokes
and give a gift that I bought on a whim
on the pretense that it was a free sample.
But if the confession fails,
things will get awkward between us.
She might ignore me for good.
I'm afraid to even imagine that.
It's good enough
to be good friends.
At least fights and arguments
won't tear us apart that easily.
So...
It's good that you're not confessing.
I'll confess to Jiang Jia.
-What?
That is the right thing to do.
If you never make an impulsive move,
you will always regret it.
Go, do it now.
Hold on.
This...
You need to be properly prepared
before winning a girl's heart.
So I need your advice on this.
I need your experience.
I have no such experience.
You get it.
I've been in a dozen relationships.
But they all failed.
Do you still want my advice?
I knew I couldn't count on you guys.
I must rely on myself.
What is your plan?
Jiang Jia loves hot pot,
crayfish, noodles with soybean paste,
and ice cream.
These are foolproof topics.
Gu Ran?
Did you just happen
to come here after a walk again?
Yes.
Did you just have dinner?
What did you have?
Dumplings.
Dumplings?
Freshly made or frozen?
Freshly made.
Good. That is good.
Good.
Well, don't stay up too late.
I should get going.
Gu Ran.
Are you...
It's nothing. I'm heading inside.
Good night.
I think
my effort wasn't entirely fruitless.
She said good night to me.
She said good night!
Don't you think that is a hint?
Not at all.
It's your wishful thinking.
Fine.
Have you read the messages
in the high school group chat?
Those from Year One and Year Two
are throwing an alumni gathering.
It's this weekend.
Are you guys going?
My project is wrapping up.
I'll be a bit busy.
Zaizai might be working overtime.
We'll pass this time.
I'm not going either.
I'm grabbing drinks with friends.
But I think Zaizai said
Jiang Jia would be there.
Hello? I won't be there this weekend.
Yes, I quit drinking.
Are you free?
Pick an outfit for me.
Am I seeing this right?
It's Gu Ran.
I ran into him
in the hospital not long ago.
He looks the same
as he did back in high school.
I wish I could talk to him.
But he has been frowning at his phone.
It must be something important.
My right side looks better.
They will come in from the front door
and see my perfect side profile.
They will be stunned by my good looks.
What are you staring at?
You look different tonight.
Do I look good?
I bought this dress this afternoon.
But then again,
I've never tried this style.
Does it look strange?
Not at all.
You look great.
Should we...
Jiang Jia.
May I have a dance with you?
I can't really dance.
Yes, she doesn't dance well.
It's all right. I can show you the steps.
I'm a slow learner.
Slower than anyone you know.
Give it a try.
-She...
-Okay.
Buddy,
do you know Jiang Jia well?
What is it?
My friend, Sun Yuan,
has liked Jiang Jia for over half a year
and works at the same television station.
He recently decided
to take the initiative.
As his friend, I came to ask you
about Jiang Jia's hobbies and interests.
You must know.
You know her so well.
Do your old schoolmate a favor.
I think
I may not know her very well.
Gu Ran?
Did Jiang Jia leave?
Why didn't you leave with her?
What kind of boyfriend are you?
What?
Aren't you two together?
No.
That can't be right.
Jiang Jia has liked you for ages.
Hasn't she confessed?
Hold on.
What do you mean by she likes me?
When we went to that summer market
after the NCEE ended,
she said...
I won't date a close friend either.
I think it's not easy being friends.
What if something happens
after we start dating?
It'll be awkward
if we can't be friends anymore.
You are right.
But if it's Gu Ran,
that would be nice.
You have a crush on Gu Ran.
No, not at all.
You heard it wrong.
That's why she headed straight for you
when she arrived today.
I thought you two were seeing each other.
How could I be wrong?
Thank you!
I just got off a conference call.
What's up?
The night before we watched
the sunrise together,
I didn't finish what I said.
After I left the country,
I wrote it on paper.
I wanted to give it to you
countless times.
When the weather was nice,
when it was raining,
and when I looked up at the stars.
Time and time again,
I failed to give it to you.
I've kept this love letter for five years.
Now,
can I read it out loud to you?
"Jiang Jia,
I've wanted
to tell you this for a long time.
I like you.
I like you a lot.
When I wrote these words down,
I couldn't help but smile.
My roommate told me
I was hopeless.
I didn't tell him
that I didn't want to be cured.
During my first semester abroad,
I audited a Chinese elective class
in my free time.
The professor taught us some proverbs.
The hardest of them all
is 'knowing oneself.'
I used to say
that if I ever fell in love,
I would show it openly
and let everyone know about it.
Only later did I discover
that I am timid when I like someone
and afraid to let her know.
I said, 'Jiang Jia is so careless.
Who would fall for her?'
But I secretly kept your discarded photo
in my wallet for five years."
I even said
that it would be nice to be just friends.
But when I saw you dance with another man,
I could only leave out of jealousy.
A friend wouldn't do that.
What would a friend do?
A good friend
won't see you every night
when he closes his eyes.
He wouldn't feel more upset than you
when you are upset.
He wouldn't say so many irrelevant things
just to tell you,
"I like you."
It seems
I didn't take you as a friend either.
A friend wouldn't do that.
Why do I feel like
I dug myself into a hole?
Gu Ran,
you said you would give me
your game console.
Don't forget that.
I have to be happy
even when you guys are not with me.
I can give you the console,
but I won't play with you.
You promised me before.
That was before.
She's in charge of me now.
Who cares about you?
Let's go, Zaizai. Let's ignore them.
How did he confess his love to you?
Tell me in detail.
I'll whisper it to you.
It's about time
for you to get married, right?
I even have your wedding gift money ready.
I've just started dating.
Lurang is first.
Soon.
I'm going to propose to Zaizai.
When?
As soon as I finish my current project.
I would like
to be better prepared.
LUMING TECHNOLOGY, DRONE SEMINAR
Take it easy.
You are the main person
in charge of this drone.
No one knows it better than you.
LUMING TECHNOLOGY, DRONE SEMINAR
Rangrang, I can't leave the office yet.
I don't think I can make it
to the seminar.
It's okay.
It's just a talk about a new product.
There will be a recording.
You can watch it later.
You don't necessarily have to be here.
But it's your first product.
It's not the last one.
Rangrang, you've got this!
It's about time. Let's go in.
Come on.
Let's go.
The wide range of applications
of industrial drones
makes them
unlike consumer and military drones,
which have clear usage scenarios
and functions.
So now, the conflict is the gap
between the users' higher demands
and the product's performance
and service.
Today,
Luming is not just launching a new drone,
but also an all-new system
that can be used in various fields.
The launch of the CW-003
will open up a whole new world of demand
in the market.
Thank you.
INTELLIGENCE IN AN INSTANT
LUMING TECHNOLOGY, DRONE SEMINAR
All technical questions about drones
have been asked already.
May I ask you a personal question?
Sure.
We all know
that there were many difficulties
in the research process for this drone.
As the youngest
aircraft manufacturing engineer
at Luming,
what are the convictions
that sustained you
to complete this project?
I used to be
a person with no self-confidence.
Even before high school,
I had low self-esteem.
I always thought
I would live out my life in mediocrity.
That was until I met someone.
Every time I look at her,
I see myself in her eyes.
I have always wondered
why someone like her,
who is as bright as the sun, exists.
When I failed,
when I ran into difficulties,
when I wanted to give up,
she would tell me,
"It's okay.
To me, you are the best."
I don't think
anyone can resist such favoritism.
Not to mention me,
who has never received
such partiality before.
Because of her unreserved faith in me,
I believe
I should continue to persevere for her.
I have made her cry again.
I'll have to cheer her up when I get home.
We should all
receive the same amount of love.
We should all receive so much love.