Three, two, one!
-Cheese!
ADAPTED FROM ZHU YI'S NOVEL,
SHE'S A LITTLE CRAZY, ON JJWXC.NET
-Kiss!
From Now On,
Someone Will Share Your Happiness.
Don't forget the gathering
we mentioned before.
See you guys
at Jifeng Restaurant at 7 p.m.
My department has a gathering tonight.
I won't be going with you guys.
I suddenly remembered something.
Xie Linnan is the president
of your department, right?
Yes. Why?
Didn't you post
on your Moments a few days ago
that you had a sore throat?
I saw him on my way to class.
He gave me some medicine to give to you.
Wasn't the medicine on the desk yours?
No.
I forgot to tell you about it.
I just remembered when he was brought up.
Your department's president
is so nice to members.
That's quite rare.
-Cheers!
Welcome, everyone!
Welcome!
Welcome to the new members
who have joined the New Media Department!
From now on, we are one big family.
Welcome!
We were supposed
to have this gathering long ago,
but I didn't expect us to be so busy.
But luckily, we have good news.
The promotional video
we made for the school
has already been shared over 10,000 times.
Not only that,
the school leaders even praised us.
I think our budget for next semester
will be very generous.
You can all drink, right?
This will make things more lively.
Here, I'll pour a glass for you, Zaizai.
Here you go. Yours.
Where is mine?
Seniors can wait.
Let the junior drink first.
It's better for girls not to drink.
There are other drinks here.
Just eating and drinking is boring.
-How about we play a game?
-Drink this instead.
How about truth or dare?
-Okay.
-Why not?
What are the rules?
-Hold on.
-Here.
-Make some room.
-Okay.
The tip of the pen shall pick the player.
-Pick one.
-Come on!
-Pick one!
-Truth.
Truth?
Then let's have the freshmen
ask the question.
I'm sure you're curious
about our president.
Is there a girl you like?
What is your type?
Do you have any?
Well...
Yes.
Yes?
-Who is it?
I don't know if I have a chance.
-A chance?
-Who is it?
-Is she in our department?
-Which college is she in?
Only one question. Let's move on.
-It's okay.
-I won't be so unlucky.
-Fine.
-We'll get you next time.
Rangrang, I'm done.
Come and get your girlfriend.
I'm going out for a bit.
Is he going out to pick up takeout?
Have you ever seen anyone
dressed in advance to pick up takeout?
Linnan, we'll get going then.
Be careful. Text us when you arrive.
-Bye.
-Bye, guys.
I'll walk you back.
It's okay.
My boyfriend is coming to get me soon.
I see.
It's already late.
I'll go after your boyfriend gets here.
Okay.
Is your boyfriend the one
who helped you answer the roll call?
Yes.
When school started,
I remember you asked me
where the College of Engineering dorm was.
I guess you were looking for him.
I can tell you really like him.
He is the person
I fell in love with at first sight
and he is the best person in the world.
Hearing your high praise for him,
I suddenly feel
there is nothing to regret.
Su Zaizai.
Rangrang.
Go on. I'm leaving too.
Bye.
Bye, Linnan.
What were you two talking about?
We were talking
about my boyfriend.
I told our president
that my boyfriend
is the best person in the world.
I like him the most.
So? Are you happy?
Rangrang, you're quiet again.
Look, you're such a dull person.
Yet I've let you stay in my heart
for so many years.
I'm truly the most generous landlady.
What are you doing?
Paying my rent.
Then you owe me a lot of rent.
Then I'll pay you slowly.
But I'll need to charge you interest.
That's about it for the weekly meeting.
There is nothing else to discuss.
That's right.
I nearly forgot.
New Year's Day is coming soon.
The school is planning
a New Year's Eve party.
Usually, the Literary Department
is responsible for such events.
But they have fewer members this year.
So our department
will be contributing too.
Zhu Miao.
I remember
from your interview for our department
that you've organized many programs
in high school, right?
How about we leave this task to you?
Will that be okay?
Don't put me in a difficult spot.
I only took part
in a few dance competitions
in high school.
It was nothing substantial.
How is that not substantial?
Stop being modest.
I'm really not confident.
When I was searching
for content materials online,
I remember seeing a video of Zhang Lurang
in a high school drama performance.
Does that count as experience
in organizing programs?
How about you let Zhang Lurang help me?
Okay, you two can work together.
Zhang Lurang, is that all right?
Okay.
Zhang Lurang.
I'm sorry for dragging you into this.
It's okay.
We're in the same department.
Why don't I buy you lunch today?
Afterward, we can find an empty classroom
and gather reference materials.
I'll pass on lunch.
Let me know
if you need specific materials.
I can search in advance.
If we need to discuss face-to-face,
we can schedule another time.
I'll get going now.
Zaizai,
you've been spending a lot of time
in the dorm lately.
Where is your boyfriend?
His department assigned him a task.
He has been busy
with his college's New Year's event.
I'll ask him if he's free.
Ding!
Your gentle, lovely,
and understanding girlfriend
is asking you if you want
to have dinner with her tonight.
Please reply upon receiving this message.
Copy that.
I'll come and find you later.
Once the program is finalized,
we can arrange rehearsals
based on everyone's availability, okay?
Okay.
Since it's late, that's all for today.
Zhang Lurang,
I'm a bit undecided
about the format of the program.
I want to hear your opinion.
Can I take up some of your time?
Yes, both of you should discuss it.
Let me know
once the program is confirmed. Okay?
-Okay.
-Thank you for your hard work.
-Bye.
Bye.
Okay, take a look at these options.
If we choose this dance,
it requires a higher level of skill.
What do you think
about a recitation of poetry?
The Publicity Department
is already doing that.
We can't do that then.
How about a choir performance?
A choir performance is less challenging
and has a higher possibility.
Why don't we go with that?
-Okay.
-Great.
Let me see.
What song should we pick
for the choir performance?
Should we do a mashup or...
I'm really sorry.
I lost track of time.
I think your girlfriend
must be getting impatient.
It's okay. You can come in.
You're not disturbing us.
Well, I'm sorry
for taking up your boyfriend lately.
After the program is over,
I'll treat you guys to a meal.
It's okay.
I won't be in your way then.
I'll get going.
Bye.
Let's go.
What do you want to eat?
Grilled fish.
It's over.
If I didn't have class,
I would come and see it.
Goodness.
What is this?
No way.
What is it?
It's nothing.
Let us look into it first.
We'll tell you later.
Don't ask us yet.
Does it have to do with me?
No!
Zaizai, we'll tell you tonight, okay?
Okay.
What is this?
I follow a lot of our schoolmates
on Weibo.
I don't know
when I started following Zhu Miao.
I just happened to check my Weibo today.
Then I saw her post this picture.
Zaizai, did you know about this?
No, I didn't know.
But this photo is different
from the original photo that I saw.
See? I knew it.
Zhang Lurang doesn't look like a cheater.
Why would Zhu Miao do this?
But this can easily mislead others.
What is her Weibo username?
-Let me check.
-I'll send it to you.
ZHU MIAO
When I'm with someone interesting,
I'm happy no matter what I'm doing.
Gosh. Is this your boyfriend?
He's very good-looking.
WE'VE GOTTEN A LITTLE CLOSER
Zaizai.
Check your phone.
ZHU MIAO: THE SUNLIGHT
SEEMS MUCH DIMMER AT THIS MOMENT
HE'S SO ADORABLE
WHEN HE'S SPACING OUT!
She's getting more outrageous.
Does she have some kind of delusion?
She made it up quite convincingly.
I know, right?
If I didn't know you,
even I would believe it.
Su Zaizai, you need to stay calm.
Patience.
No, I can't be patient.
I have to confront her about this.
She made another post.
Look. Is that her?
Hi.
It's you.
What's the matter?
Something has been bothering me lately.
I'm deeply perplexed.
If you don't mind,
can you tell me about it?
Well, I saw a girl on Weibo
who keeps posting photos of my boyfriend
with very misleading captions.
Many people think they are a couple.
But she never clears the air.
Anyway, I don't think it's right.
What do you think?
I'm sorry.
I usually like
to casually document my life.
But I didn't expect you to misunderstand.
As for this matter,
I don't want to tell Zhang Lurang
and bother him with it.
So please delete all your Weibo posts
related to him.
If my boyfriend appears
in someone else's Weibo posts
for no reason,
I wouldn't be happy about it, right?
I understand. Don't worry.
I'll delete them.
Why isn't Zhu Miao here yet?
It's weird.
She's usually punctual for the meetings.
Sorry, everyone. I'm late.
What's wrong?
Why are your eyes red?
Were you crying?
It's a personal matter.
I don't want to trouble everyone.
Don't worry.
You're too nice,
so others take advantage of you.
Tell us.
We might be able to help you.
-Yes, tell us.
-That's right.
Yes, we're all friends.
He's right.
I'm really fine.
Let's start the meeting.
Are you Zhang Lurang?
I'm Zhu Miao's roommate.
I'm here to ask you something.
Do you know what your girlfriend did?
What's wrong
with Miaomiao posting pictures
on her Weibo account?
Why is your girlfriend upset?
She even made Miaomiao
delete the pictures.
What a bully!
Miaomiao cried silently under her blanket
even when she felt wronged.
She only told us after we hounded her.
So did she delete them?
Did she delete the photos
that my girlfriend doesn't like?
Hold on.
If you don't know,
I'll ask her myself.
What kind of attitude is this?
What the heck?
What's wrong?
Someone in the Organization Department
posted about the love-hate relationship
between a beauty and a hunk
in the College of Engineering.
Zaizai, is Zhang Lurang
in the Organization Department?
It also says
that Zhu Miao cried
during yesterday's department meeting
while looking at Zhang Lurang.
It was clear what was going on.
I'm going to reply
and ask what is so clear.
They're spouting nonsense.
I suppose I have to use my last resort.
Give me the dorm key.
I need to head back first.
Why are you going back to the dorm?
I have to get changed.
Zhang Lurang,
did my roommate say something
to you just now?
Don't misunderstand.
It's not what you think.
It has nothing to do with Zaizai.
I didn't
consider your girlfriend's feelings
when I posted the pictures.
I'm sorry.
Rangrang!
What a coincidence.
I was just explaining the photos
to Zhang Lurang.
Zaizai, I didn't expect you
to mind so much.
If any conflicts arise
between you two because of me,
I'll feel really guilty.
It's okay.
I'll explain it to my boyfriend myself.
Are you going to the cafeteria too?
Why don't we go together?
Sure. Let's go.
My leg.
It hurts!
Does it still hurt?
I'm so clumsy
that I sprain my foot just by walking.
I just remembered
that I still have something to do.
I'll get going first.
Zhu Miao, aren't you going to eat?
Maybe next time.
Let's eat together next time.
Bye!
Zhang Lurang,
can I ask you something?
Why are you smiling so happily?
It's because
my girlfriend is so adorable.
You should wear a mask when you go out.
Being so handsome is quite troublesome.
ZHANG LURANG
That's more like it.
You haven't posted in so long.
Is that your girlfriend?
Yes, my girlfriend.
RANGRANG
Rangrang, did you change
your display photo?
Yes.
Won't Susu get jealous
since you removed her photo?
I've discussed this with her.
What did you say?
Susu said
it's better if it's the other Susu.
She thinks she can accept it.
When I go home for winter break,
I'll buy extra jerky to treat her.
That's hilarious.
What is so funny?
Didn't Zhu Miao
delete all of Zhang Lurang's photos
from her Weibo earlier?
Now she's starting to post again
and they are all pictures
featuring our Student Union's president.
Even the captions are the same as before.
Does that mean she has changed her target?
Probably.
Anyway, it has nothing to do with me.
I'm just looking forward to going home
for the New Year.
Zaizai,
are you also going home today?
Alone?
Obviously not.
Why would she be alone?
We're on winter break now.
It's the first time we've been away
from home for so long.
Now that we're going home,
I realize how much I miss Jiangyi,
Mr. Su Jianhua, and Ms. Zhou Xiaoli.
It feels really great
to go back with Rangrang.
Having him around
makes me feel safe wherever I am.
The journey is a bit long.
Leaning on this will be more comfortable.
Here.
If you get tired, you can lean on me.
Okay.
We're leaving now.
Slow down.
Rangrang, we're finally back in Jiangyi.
Even though it has only been half a year,
everything feels different.
Maybe the air is better
or maybe the roads have become wider.
Even the winter doesn't feel cold anymore.
We're here so soon.
I told you earlier to slow down.
This won't do.
I should tell my parents about us.
Or else, I can't even invite you in.
I told my uncle
on the phone yesterday.
Does Mr. Lin already know?
This is bad.
He must think I have stolen you away.
I shouldn't have slept so much
during his math classes
so he would have
a better impression of me.
Don't worry.
My uncle has always had
a good impression of you.
Really?
When you get home,
talk nicely to your child.
Don't start quarreling again
because you disagree.
All right. That's all then.
I'm hanging up now.
Honey,
do you remember my coworker
who went on a business trip with me?
I think so. What's up?
His son is already in Grade 12.
They argue every day at home.
But his kid refuses
to tell him what is wrong.
Just today,
the homeroom teacher gave them a call.
Only then did he find out
that his kid
has been skipping school every day
to go out to play games.
How could he not be livid?
No wonder he said he envies me.
Having a daughter is truly heaven.
Especially our daughter, Zaizai.
She's obedient and sensible.
She has never made me worry at all.
Indeed.
I'm not trying to brag here.
Ever since Zaizai was a child,
she has never hidden anything from me.
What did she write
in her elementary school essays?
"My best friend is my dad."
Stop kidding me.
She's obviously closer to me.
So explain this to me.
Whenever I went on a business trip,
she would call me over ten times a day.
Zaizai is coming home today.
She has probably arrived.
Why are you still standing here?
That's why I bought fish.
I'll make fish soup. Let's go.
So are you going home now?
Head inside first.
What is it?
It's nothing.
Then I'll go inside.
Good heavens, look at them.
It's normal for young people to date.
Don't make a fuss about it.
That scared me.
Those look just like Zaizai's clothes.
I almost mistook her for Zaizai.
Su Zaizai!
Don't move.
It's my parents.
How about this?
When I count to three,
you run forward and don't turn back.
Am I that embarrassing?
You're right.
We're adults now.
Neither of you move!
I want to see who has the nerve
to pick on my daughter!
Su Zaizai, aren't you so daring now?
Why didn't you tell us you're dating?
Do you know
what kind of boy you're dating? You...
Xiaozhang?
Mr. and Mrs. Su.
-We meet again.
-Yes.
Zaizai,
I need to seriously criticize you.
Why didn't you tell us you're dating?
Have you not considered
that he might be cold outside?
Get Xiaozhang inside
so he can warm up.
That's right.
-Have you not had dinner yet?
-Dad.
-You must eat.
-Dad!
Next time, just come straight inside.
Xiaozhang,
how long have you two
been dating?
It has been half a year.
Mom, it's too late to tell us
to break up now.
Who made the first step?
Me.
I pursued him.
I knew it.
I knew it was my daughter.
Since you've been dating for so long,
there is nothing more I can say.
But I still have something to tell you.
Please do tell, Mrs. Su.
Mom,
don't scare him.
Our daughter, Zaizai,
can be unreasonable.
If you really can't bear it with her,
be sure to tell me about it.
I'll help you criticize her.
You must never endure it alone.
Also,
she has always been a glutton.
You have to help me
take good care of her.
Sometimes when she's happy,
she will start singing.
But her singing is really...
Even as her mom, I can't stand it.
You have to be patient with her.
She doesn't have any other talents
after all.
She just loves singing.
Mom.
Stop it. I'm still here.
I'm losing face here.
I'm helping you prepare him mentally.
What if you scare him away one day?
Where will you
find someone like him again?
My mom was just kidding.
I'll run away from home if you keep going.
My wife loves to joke around.
Zaizai isn't like that.
At least,
eating a lot is a blessing.
That's right.
Dad!
Did I say something wrong?
Have some water.
Here.
Go and wash an apple.
Go.
If you're not prepared,
we can come next time.
No.
Whether I can salvage the lazy image
that Mr. Lin has of me
depends on today.
Let's go.
No, I can't.
I'm still a bit nervous.
On closer thought,
it's like meeting your parents.
I'm here with you.
It must be cold outside.
Here. Have some water to warm yourself.
Thank you, Uncle.
I mean, thank you, Mr. Lin.
Why are you acting
like a high school student
when you're already in university?
You've already graduated.
I can't use your math papers
to criticize you anymore.
How is your current homeroom class,
Mr. Lin?
The class I'm currently in charge of
is similar to your class.
It's my worst class ever.
I think your water has gone cold.
I'll add some warm water for you.
Uncle, I'll get you a glass too.
Okay.
Lurang is lucky to have met you.
He was always quiet
and not good at expressing himself.
But he has better insight than anyone else
and is far too sensible for his age.
I felt truly sorry for him back then.
But ever since he met you,
he has really changed a lot.
Su Zaizai,
thank you.
My mom always told me
to find a calm and quiet boyfriend.
So this must be fate.
Why do the same words sound so beautiful
when Rangrang says them?