Three, two, one!
-Cheese!
ADAPTED FROM ZHU YI'S NOVEL,
SHE'S A LITTLE CRAZY, ON JJWXC.NET
-Kiss!
When I Fly Towards You.
-Thank you.
-Bye.
-See you next time.
-All right.
-Bye.
LUMING TECHNOLOGY, DRONE SEMINAR
Didn't you say you couldn't make it?
But this is your first product talk.
You must have wanted me to be here.
If you're really touched,
give me a substantial reward.
One more.
It's not a game with extra gameplay
as a prize.
But I've always had good luck.
I win a prize every time.
Let me take you somewhere.
Let's go.
What is this place?
Our home.
I've already bought this house.
I was planning to bring you here tomorrow.
See if there is anything you don't like.
I have dreamed
of this scenario many times.
I want
to place a large sofa here.
And here,
a white television cabinet.
Here,
I'll hang a blue curtain.
It's so beautiful.
Today is December 22nd, 2012.
Doomsday is over.
What are you filming?
Didn't you say
we would be happier
if we record the happy moments?
I'm trying it out.
But you didn't speak
when I asked you to speak earlier.
Rangrang, were you shy?
You can tell me in secret first.
No.
May 26th, 2013.
Mrs. Guan made a new dessert.
Su Zaizai liked it very much
and finished two big bowls.
No, a bowl and a half at most!
August 7th, 2013.
We watched the sunset in Baichuan today.
It was fun.
Today is January 15th, 2014.
It's a beautiful day.
It's easy to get sleepy.
Rangrang, are you filming me?
No.
July 28th, 2015.
We're in a relationship.
Today is October 3rd, 2016.
I'm waiting to have a meal with Zaizai.
Five,
four,
three,
two.
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm on a video call with my uncle.
What?
I'm just kidding.
January 20th, 2017.
Because of the extra boba in her milk tea,
she is overjoyed.
Rangrang!
June 26th, 2020.
After today's seminar,
I want to propose to her.
For the first 17 years of my life,
I worked hard
just to keep the name Zhang Lurang alive.
That was until I met you.
I had more to look forward to.
I looked forward to you
popping up unexpectedly.
I looked forward to sweaty gym classes.
I looked forward to every bus on Route 74.
I began to look forward to tomorrow.
Maybe
I just looked forward to what you said
every night.
"See you tomorrow."
Then
I always wished
I could spend
more and more time
with you.
Later on,
I was no longer satisfied.
I wish
that you are the first person I see
when I wake up in the morning.
I want to watch movies with you
in my free time.
We could go for a walk after dinner.
Perhaps we will
have a child.
I'll teach him math.
You will teach him English.
On his birthday,
we will make a cake for him.
Zaizai,
shall we get married?
I have a bank card.
What? Are you going to provide for me?
All my red packet money
throughout childhood
is inside.
I haven't spent a penny.
I was saving it to buy rings.
I would like to think
that I've been saving money my whole life
just to marry you.
There is no backing out now.
Zaizai.
The station called me in
at the last minute.
-Did you wait long?
-I just arrived too.
Have you finished your work?
Of course.
My best friend is engaged.
Your unmarried days are numbered.
I can't miss this.
Let's check out wedding dresses.
You can try some too.
I don't want to.
He hasn't proposed to me yet.
Hello. What's up?
Are you guys done yet?
I'll come and pick you up.
We haven't even started.
Don't worry about me.
I will go back on my own.
Okay, bye now.
Don't you need someone to carry your bags?
Don't you think I'm a good fit?
We don't need that.
I'm hanging up.
We're in a hurry.
Gu Ran, are you...
Zhang Lurang?
Zaizai is beside me.
Did she not pick up?
Her phone seems to be on silent.
We're not sure when we'll be back yet.
She will contact you then.
Okay, bye.
Let's go.
-Cheers.
Time sure flies.
I remember this stall was here
when we were in junior high.
We used to come here on weekends.
This grilled eggplant is the best.
Zaizai,
I want to ask you something.
People say marriage is the grave of love.
Aren't you afraid
you will regret getting married so early?
Actually,
I regret it already.
What?
I should've proposed to Rangrang earlier.
We could've been celebrating
our wedding anniversary now.
You're kidding again.
I'm not kidding, Jiangjiang.
Do you know how much hassle it is
to plan a wedding?
You have to check the guest list
and be involved in the planning.
You have to take care of everything
from the venue to the desserts.
Rangrang never asked me to do it,
but he worked in secret until midnight.
What makes a marriage worthwhile or not
is your partner's attitude.
I've been in love with Zhang Lurang
for so many years.
If I don't even have
this confidence in him,
then wouldn't I have a bad taste?
I wish you all the happiness in the world
and forever young.
To us.
Cheers.
Hello.
Hello, Zhang Lurang.
You may have to come.
What's wrong?
Rangrang, come and take your baby home!
Zaizai, stay still.
Send me your location. I'm coming now.
All right. We'll get going now.
She didn't drink much.
She should be sober in no time.
Drive safely.
Bye.
How was it?
Did you have a good time today?
Yes. I even bought new clothes.
By the way,
when Zaizai was trying on wedding dresses,
I couldn't resist trying some on.
That shop's wedding dresses
are really pretty.
Jiang Jia.
Why don't we also...
Stop it!
You can't propose so casually.
I'm not dressed up
and my face isn't made up.
No way!
I'll wait for you to be ready.
Gu Ran, you're so annoying!
You're ruining the surprise!
You won me over just like this
All my ways out have been blocked
My...
Something and something
My love and hate are...
Rangrang, am I a good singer?
Yes.
But you don't even applaud.
Rangrang,
your face is so cold.
Are you feeling cold?
Let me warm you up.
Hubby, be good.
What did you call me?
I didn't hear it.
Hubby.
Why can't I warm you up?
Why?
Why are you crying again?
What's wrong?
I can't control myself.
I'm so silly.
Rangrang won't like me anymore.
That's not true.
You don't even kiss me.
You don't love me.
You don't like me anymore.
You don't even kiss, hug,
or lift me up.
Call me hubby again.
Hubby.
Rangrang, I love you so much.
I know.
Next, please welcome
our beautiful and graceful bride!
ZHANG LURANG, SU ZAIZAI
I bet your brother
wasn't this nervous about the NCEE.
I didn't want to cry,
but I couldn't help it.
My makeup is running.
It's okay.
I'm entrusting my daughter
to you.
Bride and groom, do you have anything
you would like to say to each other?
Starting from when I was 16,
my New Year's wish every year
was to marry you.
It seems
that making the same wish many times
will make it come true.
I'm honored.
-Kiss!
June 17th,
early summer.
Today, I finally married Zhang Lurang.
No, it's that he has finally married me.
Today should be my most unforgettable day.
That's not right either.
There were many unforgettable days
in my youth.
The starlight and the cicadas
on the day we stood guard
at the military training base,
the light that fell on us
during the play,
the train that escaped doomsday,
the sunset we watched together
in Baichuan,
partying at a music festival
with a big crowd,
the first snow
that falls every year,
and the goodbyes at sunrise.
We cried,
laughed,
parted,
and met again.
The charm of youth
is never about getting what you want,
but about every unexpected tomorrow
-You're all so fast.
-and every person you meet by chance.
I wonder when this young boy
who exchanged a quick glance with me
under the eaves
began to take place in my world.
And I have become best friends
-with the people I have known
-Three, two,
-since I was young.
-one!
What are you blushing about?
Why are you blushing?
Go!
-Congratulations on your wedding!
-The story began in the summer of 2012,
but it will never end.
Our robust youth
-may make a comeback
-Kiss!
sometime in the future.
Even if we will no longer be young then
and the sun has set,
-our love will remain the same.
-Smile!
-Your heart will still race
-What are you waiting for?
when I fly towards you.
Go to sleep.
Rangrang, what time are you leaving
for your business trip?
Seven in the morning,
so I can't wake you up.
Sleep early.
Come and sleep beside me.
I've got it.
Let's sleep.
Rangrang, I have a question for you.
What?
If one thing is to be taken away from you,
would you choose to keep me
or your handsome face?
You.
What if it is between me and your height?
What if it is between me and money?
Why are you asking me this?
Rangrang, you hesitated.
You wanted to choose money!
You prefer money over me!
I'll give you all my money then.
I will always choose you.
But Rangrang,
you won't be tall, rich,
or handsome anymore.
I might not be fond of you anymore.
Are you afraid of that?
I thought you said
only one thing would be taken.
Who knows what might happen?
I'm not afraid.
Why?
There is no reason.
You're just sure that I love you.
What are you watching?
A fantasy movie.
Hey, Rangrang.
If you could travel back in time,
is there anything
that you really want to do?
I don't know.
How can you not know?
Is there nothing you really want to do?
Only those who have regrets
want to go back in time.
But I don't have any.
I had a good past
and I have a wonderful present.
What about you?
Is there anything you want to do?
I want to kiss.
You don't have to "want."
You can just kiss me.
Rangrang, where are you?
I just got off work.
I'm on my way to your office.
I'm not at my office.
I took this afternoon off.
Can you pick me up
at Changfeng Street near our home?
Sure. I'll be there in five minutes.
Rangrang.
Where did you go with your afternoon off?
The hospital.
The hospital?
What's wrong?
You...
Don't scare me.
What is going on?
I'm pregnant.
I said that we are going to have a baby.
What kind of reaction is this?
I have dreamed about this
so many times.
Thank you.
Rangrang, you are going
to have to make money
to buy milk powder for Youyou.
Youyou?
It's the name I came up with for our baby.
What do you think?
It sounds great.
Zaizai,
I heard you took the afternoon off.
Why? Are you going home
to look after your baby?
Youyou is with my parents.
I'm going back
to my high school for a reunion.
What are you taking with you?
Our school uniform.
We agreed to show up wearing it.
Rangrang.
Are you here already?
I'll come out right away.
I'm leaving. Bye.
-Bye.
Rangrang.
If fate could have told me in advance
that I would meet such a person,
could I have chosen
to meet her a little earlier?
For a long time afterward,
I thought of that scene
over and over again.
She stood under the eaves
with her extraordinarily bright eyes
looking at me through the rain.
That glance
seemed to hint at me
that my light has come.
It was that glance,
just that quick glance,
that brought us together for life
so precisely.