Three, two, one!
-Cheese!
ADAPTED FROM ZHU YI'S NOVEL,
SHE'S A LITTLE CRAZY, ON JJWXC.NET
-Kiss!
If Only Heroes Could Be More Normal.
What a coincidence.
Is this your son?
That's right.
Here, have some water.
And I've also met Jiajia before.
It was that time at the hospital.
Talk about fate.
It's so serendipitous.
Jiajia, when did you go to the hospital?
It was when Zaizai got hurt.
Right.
I think one of their friends got injured.
Jiajia,
no need to be shy.
Just make yourself at home.
Ranran always acts so casually at home.
Yes, he does.
Here you go.
So how was the traffic
on your way here?
It's the holidays.
There weren't many people.
-Yes, fewer cars.
-Fewer people are going to work.
Ranran,
you've been studying the whole morning.
Your friend has come to visit.
You should greet her.
Ranran, you can show Jiajia to your room.
You have a lot of games, right?
Go and play, you guys.
Surely, you will find
the adults' conversation boring.
Yes.
Go on.
Okay.
Jiajia, go on.
Go on.
Feel free to look around.
Is this the homework
you told your mom
that you worked on all morning?
It's normal
for a guy's room to be a little messy.
You were obviously playing games.
This photo.
I know it's hard to believe.
But that was a candid photo.
This is Shen Qianyu, right?
He looks so good in a snapshot.
Do you have games on your computer?
Are you really asking that?
For a guy who's always on trend,
I have all the good games.
Do you have GKART?
Your computer is on.
I was just using it to...
That's better.
GKART
What are you...
I...
Do you see how nice I am?
I found the game for you.
I get it.
What?
It's not very proper
to do it openly in the daytime.
That's much too bold.
But I totally get it.
Just be careful next time.
Wait, no!
Jiang Jia, what were you thinking of?
Who told you these things?
There is no need to be shy.
I'm not some stranger.
Forget about the game.
You should review online classes
to clean your dirty mind.
Wait! I haven't logged in to my account!
What's your problem?
I am a positive young man.
Do you have a problem with that?
I am playing this game today!
My mom is getting better every day.
Her appetite has improved a lot.
She has even gained weight.
Dr. Gu, without your help,
my family wouldn't be celebrating
this new year.
You speak too highly of me.
I was just doing my job
as a doctor.
She recovered quickly
because of her good physique.
That's right.
I wonder if the kids are hungry.
Shall I prepare some fruit for them?
They're having fun.
You shouldn't disturb them.
If they're hungry,
Ranran will take care of it.
Look,
your son is so disciplined,
unlike Jiajia.
She always makes us worry.
Jiajia is a sensible kid.
She's also well-behaved.
As for Ranran,
he's good at taking care of girls.
You don't have to worry
about them hanging out.
You're right.
Otherwise, they wouldn't
have gotten along, right?
-Yes.
-Listen.
Jiajia is a quiet, reserved girl.
She never argues with others.
Right.
Let go of it right now!
You let go of my hair!
Just you wait!
How could you bite me?
I think I should get them fruit.
Yes.
Get some fruit for them.
Where were we?
Well...
What do the elderly
have to pay more attention to?
That's right.
There are some things.
Particularly conditions
related to the respiratory tract.
Good morning.
-Good morning, sir.
It's the first lesson of the semester.
Let's review first.
The flu has been quite bad lately.
We should take more precautions.
Though the weather is warming up...
-We're still acclimatizing
-...make sure to continue layering up.
to the new classroom.
We can't let our guard down.
Class rep,
come get some vinegar during the break
-and fumigate the classroom.
-Okay.
Let's continue.
What is it?
Are you playing charades?
Just spit it out.
Ranran,
the flu season is ramping up.
Your dad and I
plan to go to Huiyuan to help out.
It's not that serious.
We're just going to support them.
Yes.
But it's quite urgent.
We have to leave tomorrow.
How long will you be away?
At most, half a month.
Just over a month if needed.
It sounds pretty cool.
You could be interviewed on television.
If so, let me know.
I'll brag to my friends.
That would be amazing.
See? I told you he would be okay with it.
He can't wait for us to go away
so he can have all the freedom.
Not to that extent.
Maybe just a little.
Okay, eat.
Today's dishes are quite spicy.
Here you go. Eat this.
This isn't spicy.
You're such a picky eater.
HUIYUAN CITY
Honey,
we should pack some warmer clothes.
Yes, it's cold there.
Let's go get them.
999 GANMAOLING COLD REMEDY GRANULES
So are both your parents away?
Yes. They won't be back
for at least half a month.
Won't you feel bored by yourself?
Not at all.
They were often away working overtime.
I'm used to it.
Besides, I get to do whatever I want.
Nobody will nag me
for playing video games.
I'll get to play the new mode
in Crossfire.
Well?
Let's play tonight.
Of course!
No.
I have to help my grandma close up.
Lurang.
What about you? Do you want to come?
I'll pass.
Are you also busy tonight?
I have homework.
It looks like none of you
get to enjoy the freedom.
What are you up to?
Jiang Jia.
Xiaojiang.
Jiajia.
The best Jia.
I'm doing math homework.
I just thought of the answer,
but you disrupted my train of thought.
Can you give it a rest?
Hello? How can I help you, Ms. Chen?
Ranran, are you doing okay by yourself?
I'm as good as I can be.
I just had dinner with friends.
I just got home.
That's good.
There's cash in the drawer in our room.
Take it if you need it.
Buy your friends something to eat.
Don't worry.
I surely will.
Dr. Chen, there's an emergency.
I'm coming.
Ranran, I just called to check on you.
Your dad and I are busy. I have to go.
Don't stay up too late. Sleep early.
Are you...
You're so busy.
Well? Did you manage to get through?
No.
That's odd.
He kept sending me texts
to harass me an hour ago.
Now I can't get in touch with him.
Is he already asleep?
Harass you? Like what?
Maybe something did happen to him.
Did you say
that both his parents are away?
He must not be used to being home alone.
I think you should go check on him.
Grandma,
you worry too much.
He was bragging to us this morning
that he can do whatever he wants
without supervision.
Did you just take his word for that?
No wonder.
No wonder what?
No wonder you couldn't
make any friends before.
Gu Ran's address?
Yes. You went to his house before, right?
Give me his address.
I'll send it to you.
If there's nothing else, I'm hanging up.
Hang on.
You aren't busy right now, are you?
Why?
Stop rushing me. I'm already here.
You're just being paranoid.
He's a grown person. What could happen?
Just get here.
I was halfway through watching a drama.
Gu Ran.
Gu Ran!
So you are home. Why didn't you pick up?
Are you sleeping?
You're burning.
Hello, Guan Fang. Gu Ran has a fever.
Are you almost here?
I'm not sure. There is traffic up ahead.
I'll try to cool him down physically.
There should be fever medication here.
If the fever persists,
we'll take him to the hospital.
Okay.
Normally, you're quite annoying.
But you look pitiful when you're sick.
You're awake.
Do you feel better?
I feel much better.
Why are you here?
Don't you remember letting me in?
My goodness.
Were you sleepwalking just now
and simply opened the door?
Actually, Guan Fang couldn't reach you,
so he got worried
and asked me to check on you.
Thank goodness I live nearby
or else you would've burned to bits
before he got here.
Thank goodness.
Anyway, why isn't Guan Fang here yet?
My legs are numb.
Guan Fang should be here.
I'll go outside to get him.
Okay.
May I ask
what you are doing?
Good question.
Since you will be living alone
for half a month,
the probability
of similar incidents happening again
will be very high.
I know my grandma too well.
She will definitely ask me
to check on you every day.
So for the sake of my own sanity,
I'm going to pack you up
and take you to my house.
What?
But that's not a good idea.
I don't want to trouble your grandma.
-Besides...
-She heard you were coming.
So she has made braised pork knuckles,
fried shrimp,
steamed sea bass,
spiced beef,
and dumplings.
What are we waiting for?
Let's go.
Don't you have a spare room?
This is just fine.
We have enough space on the floor.
And he won't roll off the bed.
I didn't know you were so good to him.
You even brought him home
to look after him.
I just don't want my grandma to nag me.
I'm not that happy to sleep with him.
It's not like I enjoy
looking after a patient.
Where is Gu Ran?
I think he's outside on the phone.
Yes, based on the current situation,
it will be another two weeks
before we can go home.
-Today, I...
-That's right.
If the hospital
or a patient's family calls,
remember to note it down.
Urgent matters cannot be delayed.
I've got it.
Okay.
Don't move.
The view of you seemed to tell a story
before you turned around.
But not if I turn around?
Turned around,
it's "yrots."
Why are you moody again
after only a few minutes?
Even you could tell so easily.
Yet they couldn't.
I often suspect
that patients are more important
to my parents than I am.
Do you know?
When I was little,
they always worked late.
I was alone before I fell asleep.
I was still alone after I woke up.
When I was unhappy,
I would hide in a corner at home,
imagining their frantic looks
when they came home from work
and couldn't find me.
But even after I woke up from my sleep,
they still weren't home yet.
So I could only go back to bed,
hugging my pillow.
Even now, they still have no idea
about the countless hide-and-seek games
that I have played with them.
That's because they have never found me.
Hence, I kept winning again and again.
How I wish I could lose once.
I guess I won today.
I found you.
You should've told me.
I'm an expert at hide-and-seek.
Next time, ask me to play.
But I'm not going to play for nothing.
If you lose, you have to buy me snacks.
You're smiling.
Does that mean...
Thanks to you, I'm feeling better.
Good.
You look better
when you smile.
It's late.
Drink this milk and go to bed.
-Thank you, Mrs. Guan.
-Thank you, Grandma.
Make sure you cover yourself
when you sleep.
You don't want to get a cold.
Okay.
What are you doing?
You're blushing.
Are you still feverish?
No.
My fever is gone.
But your face is really red.
Your heart is beating fast.
It's not normal.
Very abnormal.
I'm really fine.
Go to sleep, okay?
I'm not a stranger. Don't be shy.
Just let me see.
Let me feel you.
Where are you touching?
Go to sleep. Stop touching me!
-Let me touch.
-Stop it. Go to sleep.
Go to sleep.
Stop touching me!
You have a fever!
Let me feel you.
Zhang Lurang, you've known Gu Ran
for a long time.
How do you put up with him?
Lurang, did you know?
Guan Fang snores like a trumpet at night.
Like a trumpet. Do you know?
If Gu Ran wasn't breathing,
I would've thought he became a mutant.
Last night, he kicked me.
My waist is all bruised.
Come and sort him out for me.
I just recovered from being sick.
Aren't you going to visit me?
I really can't handle him by myself.
You have to come and save me.
Mrs. Guan's stewed meat is incredible.
Come and try it.
No.
I woke up with a stuffy nose this morning.
The heater is not working
and even the hot water bottle broke.
I can only wrap myself
in a blanket and shiver.
Get me my nunchucks!
Open the door.
What on earth?
Even Rangrang has learned to play pranks.
999 GANMAOLING COLD REMEDY GRANULES
Hello, Rangrang.
I was going to Guan Fang's home
to bring medicine to Gu Ran.
I bought too much,
so I brought you some on the way.
But Guan Fang's home and mine
are in the opposite direction.
Rangrang, does "on the way"
mean following your own desires?
Your house is on the way
from the pharmacy.
So...
You don't have to explain. I get it.
Rangrang, I like that
you don't say what you mean.
Over there.
One, two.
Do you think Zhang Lurang will come?
He hasn't replied.
I know him. He will come.
Do you want to bet on it?
Sure.
I don't believe he will.
It's almost time.
What do you mean?
Three, two, one.
Who is it?
No way.
I told you.
Lurang just doesn't talk much.
But he's actually lovable.
Take your medicine.
Lurang,
did you buy it just for me?
It's to treat your brain.
I'm not leaving.
So can you let go of me now?
To be honest,
I've never slept
with anyone else since I was five.
I slept with my back against the wall
whenever I felt scared.
I've never felt so secure.
Also,
the hot water bottle you bought for me
is very warm.
I'm quite enjoying being a patient.
Don't get the wrong idea.
I bought an extra one by accident.
You're not worried about getting a cold,
but I don't want to be infected.
Cover yourselves properly.
Smarty-pants like you two
are only good at studying
and can't look after yourselves.
You're not any better.
Did your fairy godmother
pull up your blanket
when you were uncovered last night?
I'm as fit as a fiddle.
I don't get cold easily.
Are you saying I'm weaker than you?
Come on. Let's compare.
Bring it on.
Mine is better. See?
I have to take this call.
We'll compare next time.
Hello, Mom.
Were you sleeping, Ranran?
Not yet.
I have good news.
The flu in Huiyuan is under control.
Your dad hasn't rested much
this whole week.
We received so many pennants
from the patients' families.
At first, the director wanted us
to stay for a few more days.
But your dad was worried
about you being alone at home,
so he insisted on hurrying back.
Why are you talking about that?
Why not?
No need to worry about me.
I'm staying at my friend's house.
His grandma's cooking is exquisite.
I think I've gained weight.
That's great.
When I get home,
I'll make you something delicious.
I want to eat dumplings.
Sure.
I'll get your dad to make them.
He makes great dumplings.
You two stay safe out there too.
I hope to see you soon.
Okay. Don't worry.
You should sleep early.
You have school tomorrow.
Bye.
Do you want to get another fever?
It feels as if the world
always needs heroes.
But
I don't suppose anyone wishes
for their own family members
to be the heroes.
Special treatment for the heroes' child.
You can make use of it tonight.
How is giving me a Walkman
considered special treatment?
Is Guan Fang snoring again?
Let's go.
GUAN FANG
Can you guys really sleep like that?
You won't understand brotherhood.
We don't mind one another.
Gu Ran!
You roll around too much.
-Stop talking.
-Don't steal my blanket.
Stop it. It's mine.
This is the first time
that I've found being sick
to be an enjoyable thing.
A hot water bottle from Rangrang.
Medicine from Rangrang.
The bag that Rangrang used.
And...
Zaizai, whom Rangrang cares about.
Rangrang, are you having trouble sleeping
because you're worried about me?
Have you taken the medicine?
Yes.
The hot water bottle is very warm.
Then
sleep early.
I'm already in bed.
What about you?
I'm about to sleep too.
Although I have a stuffy nose,
my hearing seems
to have become more sensitive.
With his voice
transmitted into my ears so clearly,
nothing seems to scare me now.