Three, two, one!
-Cheese!
ADAPTED FROM ZHU YI'S NOVEL,
SHE'S A LITTLE CRAZY, ON JJWXC.NET
-Kiss!
When Susu Meets Susu.
Do you see my name?
Who is ranked first?
What about over here?
Do you see my name?
No, I don't.
ZHANG LURANG
Zhang Lurang!
Do you know you're awesome?
You scored 101 in English!
And what does that mean?
You've gone up by 20 points
in just two weeks!
It'll be a breeze
to get to 110.
It's lower than last time.
But why are you not surprised
by your score at all?
I checked my paper after the exam.
Doesn't that take away the surprise?
I am surprised.
Really?
You scored well too.
SU ZAIZAI
Rangrang,
I almost passed math.
This is my highest score in math so far.
Wait for me after school today.
I have something for you.
I've just finished my duty.
You must have gotten on the bus already.
It's okay.
I can give it to you tomorrow.
I haven't.
SCHOOL
Rangrang!
Isn't it a coincidence?
It so happens that the bus is late today,
so I got here on time.
This is luck.
I'm so lucky.
Here, your reward.
What reward?
Didn't I tell you?
I would reward you
if you score well this time.
I kept my word.
Thank you.
I think
it has other functions.
I didn't check thoroughly.
You can check when you get home.
Can it speak?
I...
I don't know.
Why isn't the bus here yet?
Rangrang, congratulations
on getting a good score.
I hope
you'll continue to study hard
and keep up the good work.
Ms. Su Zaizai is serious, responsible,
positive, and cute.
A long-term collaboration with her
is the way to go.
Rangrang, congratulations
on getting a good score.
I hope
you'll continue to study hard
and keep up the good work.
Ms. Su Zaizai is serious, responsible,
positive, and cute.
A long-term collaboration with her
is the way to go.
The exams were a bit difficult this time.
Take a closer look after you get home,
especially the tricky questions.
That's right.
One more thing.
Our school's annual autumn sports meet
is about to open for registration.
Be proactive, everyone.
Each event needs at least two contestants.
Wang Nan, get a name list after class.
-Okay.
-Okay, class is dismissed.
I heard a senior say
that registration every year
is like forceful recruitment.
The class reps are the unluckiest ones.
Not only do people hate them
for asking others to join,
but they also have to take on the events
that nobody signs up for.
Why don't you help me and join an event?
I'll run the 1,000 m race.
Ditto.
I don't have stamina.
I'll do the long jump.
Great!
Why don't you girls
join one more?
No way.
This isn't some BOGO deal.
I'm considered nice.
Have you seen the other classes?
Sign-ups are more direct and crude.
How so?
You are to sign up
for whatever lot you draw.
Why not just assign it directly?
Men's 100 m relay. Men's relay.
Men's relay.
What did you get?
100 m relay.
What's wrong?
Ms. Zhang,
I think we should sign up for events
according to their own wishes.
It's unfair to take part in what you draw.
Look at me. My legs are so long.
I'm a better short-distance sprinter.
I drew the shot put.
That's a waste of my talents.
That's why I said
you can swap events.
Does anyone want to swap with Gu Ran?
Ms. Zhang, I do!
What did you draw?
Men's 2,000 m.
Hurry up.
I'm okay with the shot put.
Well, Ms. Zhang,
I suddenly feel
that the shot put is fine.
In the previous meets,
everyone would be reluctant
to do long-distance running and shot put.
Drawing lots is to ensure participants
in every event.
There are still over ten days left.
Get ready.
Class is dismissed.
Am I really going to put a shot?
I'll be lucky
if the shot doesn't put me out.
Let me see.
100 M RELAY
"100 m relay."
Rangrang, I will surpass you this time.
I'm running the 1,000 m race.
I'm not bragging.
Whenever my mom
chased me with her slippers,
she could never catch me.
I have the top three in the bag.
If you cheer me on,
I will try my best to get first place.
Don't push yourself
if it's too difficult.
Don't pretend to be reserved.
You obviously want to cheer for me.
Zaizai,
aren't you afraid you'll get a stomachache
from drinking iced water in the morning?
I am hungry.
Hungry? Great.
Go and buy some Xu's rice noodle rolls.
We're having breakfast soon.
But it's the weekend.
Come on. Get into the mode.
The sports meet is coming up.
Get into the mode.
Quick, go on.
Besides, your mom has been craving this
for a long time.
So that's the main reason, isn't it?
What? Are you going back to sleep?
I'm getting changed.
The money is on the coffee table.
Be quick.
Your mom and I go to work at 9 a.m.
How nice.
I don't have to go myself.
Rangrang?
Can you get up?
It hurts.
That looks serious.
Let's go to the hospital.
You'll have to take me there.
Your golden retriever is a bully.
I'll go with you.
Does your bike still work?
I'll bike you to the hospital.
Is it really okay to leave your dog
in the security room?
It's okay. The security guards know her.
She must be a big deal.
Even the security guards know her.
But does she not like strangers?
Or does she simply hate me?
She doesn't hate you.
But she bit me.
You have to take responsibility.
Sure.
By the way, what is her name?
Susu.
I am here!
Rangrang, my nickname is Susu.
Since she has the same name as me,
I'll keep a dog named Rangrang.
Then we'll be even.
Does it not hurt anymore?
It still hurts!
Hold on tight then.
It will hurt more
if you fall off.
Then I'll hold on tightly.
Endure it for a moment.
Let me handle this briefly.
It seems
to be just an external injury.
Your ankle is sprained.
But we must wait for the CT scan result
to see if your bones are injured.
Thank you, doctor.
Then let's go outside
and wait for the CT scan result.
Remember. Don't let her move too much.
Okay.
Well, it's just a few steps.
I can manage.
So why were you riding a bike
in the morning?
I was going to buy breakfast.
I wanted
Xu's fresh shrimp rice noodle rolls.
I'm actually a little hungry.
Okay, I'll buy it for you.
Are you leaving me here alone?
I'm not hungry anymore.
I mean it.
Okay.
Then let's wait for the CT scan result.
Lurang?
Hi, Mr. Gu.
Who is this?
She's my friend.
She hurt her leg
after being frightened by Susu.
Well, this is Gu Ran's dad.
He's a doctor in this hospital.
Hello, Mr. Gu.
My name is Su Zaizai.
I'm also Gu Ran's friend.
Hello.
Gu Ran is a lively one.
I am already surprised
that he has a quiet friend like Lurang.
I didn't expect this young lady
to be gentle and quiet too.
Zaizai!
Did you fall? Where are you hurt?
Doctor, is my friend okay?
I'm fine.
This is Gu Ran's dad.
Gu Ran's...
Hello, Dad.
Hello, Mr. Gu.
I'm Gu Ran's friend. My name is Jiang Jia.
This girl's personality
is quite similar to that of Gu Ran's.
It's almost time.
Let's go get the CT scan result.
We still have to dress your wound.
Jiangjiang, wait for us here.
Mr. Gu, please excuse us.
Go ahead. Be careful.
Mr. Gu.
Have you had breakfast?
Let's hurry up.
Jiangjiang is afraid
of being alone with elders.
She must be at a loss for words now.
I don't think so.
Why?
Mr. Gu is very talkative.
He usually chats
with Gu Ran's friends.
Does he? What does he chat about?
How do you know I don't like breakfast?
You even know I don't like vegetables.
From my observation,
you have a yellowish complexion.
You did not have breakfast,
but still hiccuped several times.
You probably
have a digestive system problem.
You must've been staying up late recently.
Yes, that's right.
You guys should not harm your bodies
just because you're young.
It's very bad for your health.
If you're lucky,
you'll have minor abdominal pain.
Worse, you'll get stomach problems.
I'll always eat breakfast from now on.
Mr. Gu,
can you cure hair loss?
What?
Hey, Ms. Bai.
Xiaoran, are you here to see Mr. Gu?
I'm bringing him the keys.
Is my dad in his office?
He should be there.
-I'll head there.
-Okay.
Jiang Jia?
Dad?
Why are they together?
Don't be discouraged.
I think you still have hope.
I'm only 17.
Indeed.
It's really rare
among people of your age.
What should I do?
Mr. Gu,
you must keep it a secret for me.
Sure.
Jiang Jia is...
Gu Ran?
Hey, Xiaoran.
Did your mom ask you to bring me the keys?
I left early in the morning and...
Dad, be quiet.
I was ignorant and often made you angry.
I apologize to you.
Actually,
I stole the snacks you bought last time.
I also broke your new water glass.
I was also the one
who threw the basketball
that hit you during gym class.
I'm sorry.
I was wondering why I've been so unlucky.
-So it was you.
-How long has it been?
What do you mean?
I heard everything you two just said.
Why were you eavesdropping?
If I hadn't done so,
were you planning
on hiding it from me forever?
Why would I tell you this?
You're sick. It's a big deal.
What if I don't see you in the future?
What are you talking about?
I'm not sick.
Don't hide it. I know everything.
Zaizai fell from her bike.
I just came to see her.
Su Zaizai?
Don't use her as an excuse.
Gu Ran?
I just hurt my leg.
Why is everyone here?
Are you not sick?
What were you two talking about just now?
Why do you always have so many questions?
Dad, why were you talking about hope?
Hope!
What hope?
I said you guys are
the hope of the motherland.
Zaizai, are you done? Let's go.
-Bye, Mr. Gu.
-Wait!
The keys.
Dad, let's talk at home.
Mr. Gu, I trust you.
Okay.
Mr. Gu, we're leaving first.
Be careful on the way home.
Okay. Bye, Mr. Gu.
-Bye.
Do you really not need me to see you home?
No, I'm fine.
Zhang Lurang will see me home.
I will see her home.
Okay. I have something to do,
so I'll leave first.
I'll visit you tomorrow.
It's just a little hair loss.
It's not obvious, right?
EXIT
Has Jiang Jia been
having headaches lately?
Headaches?
I don't think so.
If he finds out,
he will definitely laugh at me.
It's Qianyu.
Where?
What are you doing?
Are you really not sick?
You are the one who is sick.
Didn't I tell you already?
I was there to check on Zaizai
and ran into your dad by chance.
-We were just casually chatting.
-That's a relief.
It's great that you're not sick.
You don't have to say anything else.
Are you going
to ask your dad at home tonight?
You're being paranoid.
I'll be asleep
by the time my parents get home.
We have no time to chat.
Are they that busy?
Doesn't that mean you'll be home alone?
And no one will boss me around.
Envious?
Who would be envious of that?
Were you planning
to get a false medical note
to get out of the 1,000 m race?
Only you would do
this kind of thing, okay?
The 1,000 m is nothing to me.
What are you laughing at?
Don't you believe me?
I didn't say that.
Which floor do you live on?
The third floor.
It's the first unit
on the right of the elevator.
Do you want to come in for a bit?
But if you don't pick up Susu,
she may think you are abandoning her.
You should go.
I can go upstairs by myself.
Okay. Remember to apply the ointment.
And you really left this Susu behind.
Are they back so soon?
I'm coming.
This is for you.
Did you buy rice noodle rolls for me?
Yes.
I'm leaving now.
Hey, wait a minute.
I'll give you my favorite jelly.
Do you like eating jelly?
When I'm unhappy, I'll feel better
after eating some jelly.
Why?
I don't know either.
I'm asking why you're unhappy.
Rangrang,
I never knew
you cared about me so much.
What time are you going
to school tomorrow?
I'll take you to and from school
until you are healed.
It was Susu's fault after all.
You offered.
Do you want to eat it?
But you made a mistake today.
So your punishment is no snacks today.
Hand.
Good night.
-I'm so jealous.
-Me too.
Please take care of her
when she is in class.
No problem.
Well,
I'm leaving then.
See you after school.
Zaizai,
what is going on between you two?
It's obvious.
I am his creditor.
In short,
Su Zaizai hurt her leg
because of Zhang Lurang.
Then are you backing out
of the sports meet?
Can't you read the room?
Who cares about the sports meet?
It's a miracle
that she could come to class.
I'm jealous.
Although I can't join the competition,
I can still contribute.
Aren't you worried
that we have no photographer?
Give me the camera.
Leave it to me to take the pictures.
Have you ever used a camera?
Don't underestimate me.
I was born
to be a photographer.
I'm a natural at taking photos.
I'm hungry.
I want to eat spare ribs, braised pork,
and pork trotters.
WHAT ELSE DO YOU WANT?
I want you
to bring them to me.
This is quite different from my camera.
Today is October 12th.
The weather is sunny
with a slight breeze.
It's a great pleasure to meet you
at the Voice of the Campus.
There is a quote
from Han Han's A Fortress.
"This is the way things work.
It takes only a moment
for you to fall in love with something.
You then spend years
asking yourself
why you like it."
Does it still hurt to walk?
Yes, it hurts so much.
Jiangjiang, I'm leaving first.
Is her leg
all better now?
Zhang Lurang.
Youngsters nowadays.
Zaizai, how is your leg?
I'll pick you up from school
for the next few days.
It's out of your way to work.
The road I used to take
is under maintenance.
My detour passes by your school.
By the way,
when I passed by their school today,
I saw a boy carrying a girl on a bicycle.
They were in school uniforms.
They are so young.
Zaizai, don't be like them.
Boys nowadays are sweet-talkers.
But it doesn't mean anything
to carry a person on a bike.
Maybe the girl was injured
and couldn't walk.
Besides, you shouldn't
call someone a sweet-talker
just because they are handsome.
That makes sense too.
How do you know what that boy looked like?
I was just guessing.
Our school has
quite a lot of handsome guys.
The sports meet is tomorrow.
I'm going to rest.
The annual school sports meet has begun.
The magnificence of soldiers
on the battlefield
returns to our gym once again.
The pursuit of speed makes us faster.
The pursuit of strength
makes us go higher and stronger.
We put our will to the test
to challenge our limits.
All the best to all the athletes
in the sports meet.
Ignite your passion.
GRADE 10, CLASS 9, GRADE 10, CLASS 1
I drank hot water. I feel much better now.
But I probably
won't be able to run 1,000 m.
If my leg was fully healed,
one of us could have joined the event.
You should feel fortunate.
Why?
Have you seen
the photos of the sports meet
in the school newspaper every year?
Come, I'll show you.
-Go for it!
Get set!
Yes!
Awesome!
We won!
-Go for it!
Get set.
This sports meet
is basically a major disaster.
I suddenly feel so lucky.
-You can do this!
-You've got this!
-Nice job!
-Go for it!
What are they doing over there?
-Go!
The faculty competition, I think.
I think Mr. Lin is participating too.
-Let's go.
-Let's go take a look.
-Go!
-Mr. Lin, go for it!
Mr. Lin.
What a good figure you have!
I usually...
Mr. Chang is even fitter.
I bet you exercise regularly.
You have muscles all over.
It's pinching my hand.
Your legs are so long!
Your legs are twice as long as mine!
How can we compete with you?
Who can outrun you?
I just like exercising.
-I love playing ball.
-Really?
I like playing ball too.
What kind of ball do you usually play?
Yo-yo.
My son loves to play it.
So I play with him.
It's a tough workout.
This...
Get set.
It's starting.
-Go!
Ready.
Go for it!
Do your best!
-Go for it!
-Go, Mr. Lin!
-Yes!
He won!
Look at you guys.
You don't work out, don't you?
It's not that we don't work out.
You were running too fast!
Look how tired Mr. Lin is.
He almost couldn't breathe.
I mean, almost fainted.
That's true.
-I'm totally spent.
-Look at him.
Almost fainted?
-Just don't be faint-hearted.
-Indeed.
Xiaoxiao.
It's normal that you couldn't catch up.
Last year, I got first place.
Yes, indeed.
In the future,
you guys need to exercise more.
Of course.
Let's go.
Goodbye, Mr. Chang!
Goodness. I'm exhausted.
Su Zaizai,
isn't the tug of war about to start?
-Did you bring the camera?
-Yes.
Good. Take more pictures.
It's about to start. Let's hurry there.
-Mr. Lin, we'll be going first.
-Okay.
-Go for it!
How is it going?
Handsome just defeated Class 3.
Now they are going against Class 4.
-Go for it!
-Go for it, Handsome!
-Go for it, Handsome.
-Go for it!
Su Zaizai, keep cheering.
Why are you getting quieter?
-Go for it!
Well, my voice is a little hoarse.
Participants in the men's 100 m relay,
please come to the check-in area.
Rangrang, are you about to run
the 100 m race?
Then I'll cheer you on.
If you don't say anything,
I'll take that as a yes.
But there are so many people.
You might not hear my voice.
Maybe I can borrow
the referee's loudspeaker.
Weren't you cheering loudly
during the tug-of-war match?
That was for our class rep.
His name is Wang Nan.
We usually call him Handsome.
It's his nickname.
Are you
jealous?
No.
If not, why would you remember it?
I was just asking.
After pretending all day,
I can finally walk normally.
I almost got caught today.
Luckily, I realized it in time.
It's such a headache
that my leg is healed.
I wonder how much longer
I can sit on the back of Rangrang's bike.
Whatever.
I will delay it as long as I can.
Su Zaizai.
I'm sorry.
Today was another day of being Pinocchio.
My nose had better not grow longer.
What if I won't look cute anymore?