Three, two, one!
-Cheese!
ADAPTED FROM ZHU YI'S NOVEL,
SHE'S A LITTLE CRAZY, ON JJWXC.NET
-Kiss!
When We Started Getting Closer.
GRADE 10, CLASS 9
After you get your exam papers back,
check your mistakes.
Thank goodness I passed!
Do you all have your papers?
Let me start
with a summary of your performance.
Excuse me, Ms. Zhang.
What is the matter?
I didn't get my exam paper.
What is your name?
Su Zaizai.
Right.
Su Zaizai,
in the assessment exam taken
by two classes,
you got the highest score, 138.
So I circulated your paper
among the students in Class 1.
You may take it back after class.
Share your classmate's exam for now.
Class 1?
Okay.
HIGH SCHOOL ENGLISH ASSESSMENT
I'm surprised.
Su Zaizai is so good at English.
Why doesn't she usually speak English?
Well, if you put it that way,
you should speak classical Chinese
if you do well in Chinese.
Good point!
Is it Su Zaizai's paper?
Yes.
ZHANG LURANG,
HIGH SCHOOL ENGLISH ASSESSMENT
Don't get me wrong.
I'm not following you.
I put a tracker
on my English exam paper.
It brought me here.
All right.
I went to your class to get my paper.
Gu Ran told me that it was with you
and that you were in the reading room,
so I came here.
Sorry.
I mistakenly took it with me.
It's no big deal.
You didn't mean to. I get it.
Are you still doing
the fill-in-the-blanks?
Did you fall asleep too?
It's time for class. Let's go back.
Rangrang,
you're too slow at fill-in-the-blanks.
You spent almost half an hour.
It's a waste of time.
When I don't understand something,
I don't want to move on.
Did you really understand it?
But you only answered
three problems correctly.
Do you really understand it?
Do you really understand
how to calculate acceleration?
That's because
I don't pay attention to physics.
It's okay that you're not good at English.
Listen, my scores
in physics and chemistry combined
don't even add up to 100.
I still don't have
the periodic table of elements memorized.
And I really don't know
the unit of acceleration.
What are you trying to say?
Do you still not understand?
I was emphasizing your excellence.
I almost made myself sound super stupid
and you still don't get it.
Zhang Lurang.
Don't blindly do exercises.
Reciting vocabulary is more useful.
Hey, Rangrang,
do you know your mom is here?
Who called her here?
Don't you know?
I just saw them talking in the office.
I thought I was wrong.
Yes, I'm not usually here.
I'm on a business trip
and wanted to stop by.
How is Zhang Lurang doing recently?
His grades are among the best
in our school.
He is outstanding,
especially in science.
However,
he's not that good in English.
He didn't pass the latest exam.
It would be a pity
if English dragged him down.
I see.
Actually, my other son,
who is younger than Lurang,
is excellent in all subjects.
He has skipped grades to Grade 11.
I never have to worry about him.
If only Lurang
could be half as excellent as him.
Mrs. Zhang, don't say that.
Zhang Lurang is also excellent.
We shouldn't deny his strong points
just because of a small flaw.
Yes, you are right.
Ms. Zhang.
Come here, Zhang Lurang.
I'll let you talk. I'm going back to work.
Don't be late for the next class.
Please help my son improve.
-Thank you.
-Yes.
Did you have an English exam?
Why didn't you mention it?
I just got the exam result.
I heard that you didn't pass it.
Never mind.
I don't expect you to be like Luli.
Go back to your class.
I'll think of a way
to improve your English.
Did you teach a top student
how to do exercises?
I don't think
he is a top student in English.
Even with a poor English score,
he ranked in the top 50
in the entrance exam.
I have a feeling
that he doesn't memorize vocabulary.
The fill-in-the-blank exercise
only had Unit 1 vocabulary.
Even without new words,
he didn't know them.
Even a top student has limitations.
I know it was ridiculous
for me to remind him that way,
but he seemed frustrated with it.
I said that directly
without considering his feelings.
Would he be mad?
Why wasn't I more tactful about it?
That's how it feels to be affected
by someone she cares about.
TEACHING BUILDING B
Excuse me.
Come in.
Ms. Zhang,
I don't understand some tenses.
How diligent of you to study after school.
I suppose so.
If you can figure out English,
you will definitely be in the top five.
What don't you understand?
Here.
-And this one.
-Okay.
Look here.
You should fill in
"said"
because the "that" clause in the sentence
is in the past perfect tense.
Ms. Zhang, we're heading to the meeting.
Okay.
I'll come soon.
Look.
According to the word "did"
in the first part of the sentence,
we know we should use simple past tense.
Excuse me.
Likewise,
it should be the same tense here.
Ms. Zhang,
the classwork for today is all here.
Okay.
By the way,
you came at the right moment.
This is Su Zaizai,
Class 9's English representative.
She's excellent in English.
I have to go to a meeting.
You may ask her if you have any questions.
Are you in a hurry to go home?
No, I'm in no rush.
Okay, Su Zaizai,
please help Zhang Lurang.
I'm going to a meeting.
-Thank you, Ms. Zhang.
-No problem.
Since Ms. Zhang said so,
don't worry.
I will be responsible for you.
Sit.
Thank you.
You made so many mistakes.
No worries.
This means
you have a lot of room for improvement.
Well,
did you memorize vocabulary today?
What stupid question are you asking?
I did.
Zhang Lurang, let's get started.
This one...
That rules out A and B,
so the answer is C.
Is that clear to you?
Yes.
Repeat it to me.
You can't?
Then I'll tell you again.
The sentence begins with "not only,"
so the sentence
has to be partially inverted.
Do you know what inversion is?
Yes.
Really?
Tell me about it.
I'll tell you one more time.
Listen...
The sentence begins with "not only,"
so the sentence
has to be partially inverted.
And from the following "went,"
we know it's in the past tense,
so the answer is C.
Didn't I explain it really well?
Concisely and explicitly.
Yes, I think you did well.
Mr. Lin.
You did explain it well
with very clear logic.
Zhang Lurang,
I suggest that you ask Su Zaizai
to help you with English.
-I agree...
-No need.
It would take up her time.
Not at all.
How about this?
You can tutor me too.
We can take up each other's time.
It's called mutual improvement.
You're right.
Mutual improvement.
I'll tutor you in English on Saturday.
You can tutor me in math on Sunday.
Is there anything else
you don't understand?
No, there isn't.
Thank you.
That's great.
Su Zaizai.
Zhang Lurang and you.
Are you two...
Not even close.
What?
No, I meant
the tutoring.
It hasn't been decided yet.
Well, Mr. Lin,
I'll be leaving now.
Goodbye, Mr. Lin.
Goodbye.
"Not even close"?
GRADE 10 ENGLISH TEST
It seems
that Rangrang understood
the points I told him.
Am I able to help him?
You did explain it well
with very clear logic.
Zhang Lurang,
I suggest that you ask Su Zaizai
to help you with English.
If only Rangrang would agree to it.
The answer to the last problem is C.
Many of you made a mistake here.
Does anyone know why the answer is C?
Zhang Lurang,
please tell us.
It's because...
The sentence begins with "not only,"
so the sentence
has to be partially inverted.
The sentence begins with "not only,"
so the sentence
has to be partially inverted.
And from the following "went,"
we know it's in the past tense,
so the answer is C.
Well done. Please sit.
It looks like Su Zaizai teaches you
better than I do.
Su Zaizai? The student in Class 9?
A student in a normal class?
Although she's not an honors student,
her English score is in the top three
in your grade.
She's still in a normal class.
She's jealous.
Rangrang,
why are you reading while walking?
It's dangerous.
Watch out!
Rangrang, guess what is in my bag?
Books.
All right.
A book, yes.
But it's not an ordinary book.
I made this complete collection of English
with great effort.
Even a hopeless student
can be enlightened.
Of course, if you join my tutoring class,
with my detailed instructions,
you will definitely pass.
Even moving up ten ranks
will be a piece of cake...
No, thank you.
Rangrang,
please think it through.
My tutoring fee is inexpensive.
SHINY SCIENCE AWARDS
SU ZAIZAI'S ENGLISH TUTORING CLASS!
REMARKABLE RESULTS! NO LIE!
Zaizai!
You explained
this fill-in-the-blank question so well.
I got it immediately.
Of course.
I'm a professional tutor.
Whose English score is so high?
It's mine.
I'll think about it.
After all, I prioritize high efficiency,
so I have certain requirements
for students.
Yes, of course.
He should be home soon.
Lurang?
Good, he's home.
Come, sit here.
Let me introduce him to you.
This is Zhang Lurang,
Luli's older brother.
Lurang, this is Ms. Chen.
She once tutored Luli
for an English contest.
She's a great teacher.
Very coincidentally,
Ms. Chen has been transferred
to Jiangyi this year.
I made great efforts
to slip you into her tutoring schedule.
You have to study hard, okay?
I used to only teach kids
who were in the top three of their grades.
Take Luli for example.
We got along very well.
Being gifted is essential.
I heard from your mom
that you are very bad at English.
I don't know if you can keep up with me.
I didn't want to take this job.
But your mom said...
I already have a tutor.
Why didn't you tell me this?
Mrs. Zhang,
my time is very precious.
Ms. Chen, please wait.
When did you hire a tutor?
Why didn't I know?
Is this tutor reliable?
At least
she truly wants to help me.
I'm going out to buy something.
Lurang!
I...
Thank you.
Zhang Lurang!
Why are you here?
I...
You are following me.
I'm just passing by. I'm leaving.
Hey!
Well...
The power went out at my house.
I couldn't cook.
I had to eat out.
I'm having oden here alone.
It's really pitiful.
I get the feeling
that people are giving me weird looks.
Zhang Lurang,
can you sit with me for a while?
Just for a while.
Rangrang, would you like to eat some?
No, I've already eaten.
But I bought a lot.
Are you sure you won't have some?
I'm not hungry.
I know you are not hungry.
I'm forcing you to eat it.
Try it.
Isn't it good?
Yes.
There are also these.
This one is also good. Try it.
Rangrang, I have to learn from you.
Learn from me?
You didn't waste any of it.
Look, it's empty.
Shall I buy some more for you?
No need.
How much
did these cost?
It's on me.
If you feel bad about it,
then let's say you owe me one.
You can treat me to a meal later.
Thank you.
Here.
Are you treating me already?
It's the tutoring fee.
Tutoring fee?
I'm...
applying for your tutoring class.
The one you mentioned this afternoon.
Is the class full already?
No!
Besides, you're an honors class student.
I'll give you one-on-one tutoring.
There's no class size limit.
I promise
to be serious, conscientious, and patient.
Is this enough?
Yes!
If not, I'll give you English lessons
and you'll give me
math and physics lessons.
Like Mr. Lin said,
mutual improvement.
Rangrang, you smiled.
You actually smiled!
Thank you for your oden. I'm leaving now.
Rangrang!
Do you have WeChat?
Given our relationship,
isn't it only right
to add each other on WeChat?
-What relationship?
-That's...
A teacher-student relationship.
If I don't have your WeChat,
how will I contact you tomorrow?
See you tomorrow, Rangrang.
See you tomorrow.
Zhang Lurang!
It's nothing.
I just want to inform you.
I don't give returns or refunds
for my tutoring.
So we will have
to work this out together.
Am I dreaming?
This is a milestone for me!
CONTACTS, DETAILED INFORMATION
It's so cute.
It must be Rangrang's dog.
Nobody else could raise such a cute dog.
CONTACTS, DETAILED INFORMATION
MOMENTS, ZHANG LURANG
Why aren't there any Moments updates?
That's how it should be.
Not everything should be posted online.
What if bad people see them?
Rangrang, what time do you want
to start the lesson tomorrow?
Is he busy?
RANGRANG, WHAT TIME DO YOU WANT
TO START THE LESSON TOMORROW?
Is he asleep?
No, I can't send him any more messages.
What if he finds me annoying?
I'll see you
at the intersection at 10 a.m.
I'll pick you up
since we live so close.
No need.
Then you can pick me up.
I'm just joking.
I'll be there tomorrow on time.
Good night, Rangrang.
Good night.
Did you wait for a long time?
No.
I also just got here.
Do I look different today?
Did you not sleep well last night?
What?
You have dark circles.
Are they that obvious?
Let's go.
I look so different today
and he only noticed my dark circles.
You're the reason
that I didn't sleep well.
Rangrang, wait for me!
Su Zaizai.
Where
do we start?
There is no rush.
We can start
by changing how we address each other.
Look, I'm tutoring you now.
Shouldn't you call me Ms. Su?
Or just omit my surname
and call me Zaizai.
Su Zaizai also works.
I like you calling my name.
Look, this is the lesson plan
I've made for you.
You have a weak foundation in English
and a limited vocabulary.
I'm going to send you 50 words every day.
Memorize and write them down
and then I'll teach you
phrases and collocations.
Okay.
I'll pay you
part of the tutoring fee tomorrow.
Didn't I say yesterday
that I don't need money?
I'll tutor you in English.
You can tutor me in math and physics.
We can help each other.
You don't have to feel bad about it.
After all, your only weakness is English.
But I'm weak in more than one subject.
I actually get the better end of the deal.
Okay,
Ms. Su.
Then let's get started, Zhang Lurang.
Let's go.
It has been a long time, Zhang Lurang.
Do you have PE class now too?
What a coincidence.
See you later. Let's go.
It must be hard to teach her.
It's easier than teaching you.
You've changed, Lurang.
Lurang.
GYM
Gather up!
Next class,
we'll have a test on the three-step layup.
I just took a look.
Some of you are rather uncoordinated.
The test will be tough for you.
I've made a list.
If I call your name,
you are to stay after class.
I'll leave two balls here.
Keep practicing.
Chen Pengpeng.
Wang Yue.
Su Zaizai.
Lin Si.
Jiang Jia.
Xiong Keke.
Don't laugh.
You're the same too.
I'll call some names.
Hu Hong.
Liang Meng.
Ye Zhenxin.
Li Jiayun.
Jiang Ranran.
These students must stay and practice.
Everyone else is dismissed.
Go.
Do you want to play some more?
Leave the ball at the door.
Let's buy some water first.
Okay.
I've barely talked with him.
Now I have to practice
the three-step layup.
I'm so upset.
Let's practice, Zaizai.
I can at least take three steps.
You can't even take one step.
Here.
Ye Zhenxin.
We do so much better than them.
Why are we wasting time here?
That girl with the basketball
seems to be Su Zaizai.
When I passed by
the reading room yesterday,
I saw her tutoring Zhang Lurang.
How do they know each other?
She has been in hot pursuit.
Excuse me.
Can you throw the ball over?
-Let's get some ice cream later.
-You're kidding.
Did you see her attitude?
How could she kick it even farther?
Forget it. Let's get it ourselves.
I think this is yours.
You kicked it to us. Was it intentional?
What is going on?
Is it necessary to make such a scene?
That's our ball.
Thank you.
Are you all freshmen?
Can you play basketball?
Shall we teach you?
No, we're just playing around.
Hey, look over there.
Aren't you practicing
to get better at basketball?
We're offering to teach you.
Why aren't you happy?
What?
You're playing hard to get.
I can see through it.
Even if we are to be taught,
it should be by a good player.
But you guys?
I don't think we need it.
What do you mean?
She wants you to shut up.
Do you think it's cool to bully girls?
It's none of your business.
Do you want a fight?
We're not interested in fighting.
This is the basketball court.
So let's have a game.
Your ball looks nice.
The girls need a ball to practice.
If you lose,
give them the ball.
Okay!
Let's do it.
But I have one condition.
If you lose,
you will apologize to us.
-I think...
-Okay.
How about a three-on-three?
We're on.
By comparison,
Zhang Lurang is so handsome.
Even Gu Ran pleases the eye.
Come on.
Come on!
They must have seen
how the boys bullied you,
so they came to lend you a hand.
We are classmates.
We help each other, of course.
By the way,
Zhang Lurang was looking at you
when he accepted the challenge.
Yes, I saw it too.
Really?
I didn't notice it.
Classmates help each other.
They are not our classmates.
Why are they so excited?
Who knows?
They keep pestering Zhang Lurang
and the guys.
He is so awesome!
Zhang Lurang is so good at everything!
Desperate fools.
Nice block!
-Come on!
Awesome!
It's 21 to 9!
He's so handsome!
Do we still need to continue?
We didn't take the game seriously.
Let's go.
Wait.
Did you forget something?
Leave your ball here.
Give us the ball faster.
The class will be over soon.
No, not them.
It's the two girls next to them.
Zhenxin!
Why are they helping
students from another class?
Exactly.
Where are you two going?
Tutoring lesson.
Are you coming too?
Go.
I don't want to torture myself.
I'll just keep playing.
It's unbelievable.
The top English student here
is reading basic English.
I want to figure out
why Rangrang's English is weak.
Well, have you figured it out?
Not yet
because I can answer
these questions right away.
Zaizai, having good grades
doesn't make you a good teacher.
You are right.
Should I practice with you first?
Jiangjiang, give me your test paper.
Don't hide.
Hurry up.
Do you know why you got this wrong?
If only my English score
could be sold to Rangrang.
I don't think he got a bad deal.
That's because I'm the tutor.