Three, two, one!
-Cheese!
ADAPTED FROM ZHU YI'S NOVEL,
SHE'S A LITTLE CRAZY, ON JJWXC.NET
-Kiss!
Good Job, I'll Reward You With Ten Points.
Where is Zaizai?
Qianyu?
Who are you peeking at?
What are you doing?
Are you too shy
to go talk to Qianyu?
As if! It's nothing to be shy about.
Go on then.
You're always at my heels
and questioning me,
but you're such a coward in front of him.
Why didn't I realize
how two-faced you are, Jiang Jia?
It's none of your business.
It's absolutely my business.
Look.
We are so close.
I should deliver your feelings to him.
Just wait. I'll tell him.
Qianyu!
Gu Ran, how dare you!
Jiang Jia, are you afraid of this?
Fine, I won't tell him.
Well, it depends on your performance.
What?
I'm a little thirsty.
Please drink it.
I just finished doing the shot put.
My arms are sore.
I'll do it.
It feels refreshing.
All right. That's it then.
I'll call you again if I need you.
You may go.
Gu Ran, this is considered blackmail!
Sue me.
I...
Zhang Lurang!
You have a medal!
That's amazing.
I'm only the runner-up.
"Only"?
Being the runner-up is amazing.
Why are you looking down on second place?
I don't.
It's only meaningful if I win.
Why?
First and second place
are both meaningful.
If I get to compete,
I'll feel great even if I get last place.
So you are very amazing already.
However,
this silver medal
looks like it's tied to a red scarf.
It looks quite nice.
If you like it,
I'll give it to you.
Su Zaizai!
It's time to take group photos! Come here!
I'm coming!
I have to go.
Wait for me tonight.
Make sure to wait for me.
Isn't that Zhang Lurang's medal?
Yes.
Zhang Lurang.
Why did you give your medal
to someone else?
She likes it.
Rangrang,
you should
keep this medal.
Why?
This is the first medal you got
while I was watching.
It is very meaningful.
I'm just joking.
I think being a runner-up
is also meaningful to you.
You don't need to give it to me
just because I like it.
Besides,
it's not the medal itself that I like.
-I...
-You like...
No.
I have never. I swear!
I swear.
I'm only 16 years old this year.
I...
Did he ask you so suddenly?
Yes.
It was very sudden.
What did you say?
I told him
that I'm only 16 years old
and have never given it much thought.
You are 16 years old.
Is Zhang Lurang 60 years old?
Stop laughing at me.
Help me analyze it.
Why did he ask me that?
Be prepared.
With my years of experience
consuming novels and dramas,
most people who ask that question
either want to say
they like you
or they don't like you.
Whatever.
He didn't say he liked me or hated me.
At least we are still friends.
That's enough for me.
Rangrang, congratulations
on getting a good score.
I hope
you'll continue to study hard
and keep up the good work.
Ms. Su Zaizai is serious, responsible,
positive, and cute.
A long-term collaboration with her
is the way to go.
THE FIRST HIGH SCHOOL
Judging from the last examination's data,
we can see
that the students of Grade 10
show very different studying capabilities.
AVERAGE SCORES OF EACH CLASS
The honors classes, Classes 1 and 2,
have a much higher academic performance
than the normal classes.
I hope they can keep up
the good work.
Of course,
the homeroom teachers of normal classes
shouldn't be dejected.
There are special cases too.
Take Zhang Yan's two classes, for example.
Although Class 1's average result
is in the lead by a lot,
their English results alone
is not as good as that of Class 9.
Class 9 does have students
who are very good at English.
I never have to push them to learn.
I think this is good.
We should let excellent students
set an example for others
so that they can improve together.
If possible,
we can send excellent students
to other classes
to share their ways of studying.
I think this is a good idea.
Some students aren't bad at studying
or unwilling to study.
They just aren't using the right method.
That was why they wasted their time
without improving their results.
With other students' help,
that can change.
For example, Su Zaizai from our class
didn't pass the math subject
in her entrance exam.
However, ever since
she formed a study group
with Class 1's Zhang Lurang,
her math scores
have improved significantly.
Let me give you an example
of a study experience sharing session.
Ever since our class's Zhang Lurang
received Su Zaizai's help,
his English score has improved
from 80 to 100.
Quiet.
So I've discussed it with Mr. Lin.
We won't give lectures
in the last two classes.
The highest scorers of a single subject
in the last monthly exam from both classes
will go to the other class
for the study experience sharing session.
Do you all understand?
-Yes.
Good.
How is it? Is it messy?
How long have you been doing your hair?
Jiangjiang,
I'm a little nervous.
What is there to be nervous about?
You have given Zhang Lurang
so many tutoring lessons.
This is different.
It was one-on-one with Zhang Lurang.
This time, I'll face the whole class.
Besides,
if I don't nail it,
the students from his class
will laugh at me
for daring to teach Zhang Lurang.
I can't let that happen.
You're right.
That's all for my experience.
If there is anything you don't understand,
you can go to Class 9 and ask me.
-Su Zaizai, I have a question.
-Su Zaizai.
I have a question.
Can you explain this to me?
-Can you help me?
-Ask me one by one, please.
I'll answer you one by one.
They're not usually this serious
when Ms. Zhang is teaching.
Is it too late to ask Su Zaizai
to give me English lessons?
Yes.
Why?
When she taught me,
it was one-on-one.
Su Zaizai.
What?
It's time to go home.
I'm coming.
Well, I'll explain it to you
when I get a chance.
I'm leaving. Bye.
Wait for me!
Rangrang, did you leave so quickly
because you were afraid
that I would ignore you
if I tutored all of them?
No.
It's okay if you did.
Don't worry.
I will be responsible for you
until the end.
Did the school release an announcement?
Zaizai.
Didn't you leave with Gu Ran?
Hearing his name makes me angry.
Don't mention him.
Are you reading this too?
I haven't read it yet.
Don't bother.
No one knows about it better than I do.
The school anniversary
is happening soon.
The school requests all student clubs
to prepare a performance,
including the Drama Club.
What is our show then?
I knew you would be curious.
I have asked around.
It will be Cinderella for now.
The actors of the main roles
will be chosen among the new students.
If Zhang Lurang is the prince,
I'll audition for the role of Cinderella.
What? Have you changed your mind again?
I heard the prince will be played
by Shen Qianyu.
It's not Rangrang, so I'm not interested.
I think it's fine being an elf.
I heard Ye Zhenxin
will be auditioning too.
If we apply together,
our chances of winning
will be much higher.
I'll be mad
if Ye Zhenxin gets the role of Cinderella.
But...
Think about it.
Cinderella's dress is the prettiest.
Don't you want Zhang Lurang
to see you at your prettiest?
I do.
That's right.
Don't worry.
This audition is fair and just.
If we prepare well,
the role will surely be ours.
Zhang Lurang,
you know the audition for Cinderella
is today, right?
I want to audition for Cinderella.
We are from the same class.
Please vote for me.
I have cookies for everyone.
What an impressive way to get votes.
How unfortunate.
It's too bad I've been having a toothache.
I'm avoiding sweets.
I'm sure you know
that toothaches are contagious.
Zhang Lurang, what about you?
The choice should be made
after I watch
all the candidates' performances
in the audition.
That's right.
I'm well-prepared,
so I believe I'll win.
I have a feeling
that she is a competent rival.
"Ye Zhenxin."
SU ZAIZAI, YE ZHENXIN, JIANG JIA
SU ZAIZAI, YE ZHENXIN,
JIANG JIA, WANG LINLIN, CHEN MENG
"Ye Zhenxin."
"Su Zaizai."
"Jiang Jia."
Students,
this is the final vote.
"Su Zaizai!"
Yes!
I'm not convinced.
Either Su Zaizai solicited votes in secret
or the audition was rigged.
Otherwise, how could she win
by just one vote?
A professional actor won't complain,
regardless of the role she gets.
This was decided by a vote.
I hope you can accept it
with an open mind.
If you still don't believe it,
I can show you the votes.
There's no need.
Goodbye, Qianyu.
Qianyu, I have a request.
I want to see the votes.
Why does the winner
want to see them as well?
"As well"?
Never mind.
These are all the votes.
Here you go.
Thank you, Qianyu.
Lurang,
your ballot has a stain.
Do you want a new one?
It's fine. It can still be used.
SU ZAIZAI
In the Cinderella audition,
you voted for me.
I didn't.
Don't tell me you are feeling shy.
No.
Did you really do that?
I don't remember.
Because you would back me up.
I wouldn't.
Zhang Lurang,
thank you.
He touches his neck when he lies.
Rangrang is cute even when he lies.
SU ZAIZAI
Actually, your vote is all I need.
Rangrang,
I got the script for Cinderella today.
There are so many lines
and they're difficult to memorize.
Take your time memorizing then.
Rangrang, when you are free,
can you help me with my lines?
Why are you asking for my help?
That's because you have a good memory.
If you help me rehearse my lines,
I'll surely improve quickly.
It will only take
a little of your time every day.
Just a little.
If you can score 90 points
on the exam I give you
during our tutoring session in two days,
I'll think about it.
Ninety points?
Is there a problem?
Ninety points is great.
It's an auspicious number.
I can do it if I work hard.
Ninety points?
I don't even dare to dream about it.
No, I must do it no matter what!
I must get 90 points.
Rangrang,
you are here so early.
NO. 9 WANGRONG ROAD
Why didn't you go in?
We can't go in today.
CLOSED TODAY
Why are they closed?
We can take a break for today.
No!
We agreed
to have a tutoring session today.
We can't waste time.
Besides,
I must do your exam today.
Come in. No one is home.
Sorry for disturbing you.
Susu.
Rangrang, she still remembers me.
She seems to like you.
Well, she must take after her owner.
It was just a joke.
How do you know
I like watching television while studying?
It's not for you.
Then who is it for?
Is it for you?
Be good and watch television.
I'm going to study.
Rangrang,
is Susu usually the only one
with you at home?
My uncle also lives here.
Your uncle?
They say nephews and uncles look alike.
Is your uncle as handsome as you?
What does he do?
He's a math teacher.
Math teacher?
He's knowledgeable.
No wonder you are so good at math.
Do the exam first.
You wrote it by hand.
Did you make it just for me?
It's 4:30 p.m. now.
I'll grade your paper at 6:40 p.m.
It's so formal.
An exam should be formal.
According to the latest census,
one-third of people over 18 years old
are single.
That means
one in three people in the country
is single.
50,9% of people
believe a small social circle
is the reason for singlehood.
24,5% of people...
Ninety points.
I'm done.
I'm five points short.
Rangrang, my answer for this one
was initially correct,
but I later changed it.
Can you grade it
based on my previous answer?
No.
My calculation method
is correct for this question.
I gave you points for the method.
Why is it so difficult
to get five more points?
My uncle is back.
Lurang, you're home.
Hello, sir.
Su Zaizai?
Are you having a tutoring session?
Yes.
Lin...
Mr. Lin?
Given your reaction,
Zhang Lurang didn't tell you
I'm his uncle, did he?
He didn't.
You didn't ask.
Mr. Lin,
we are having an exam here.
It's finished.
Although I didn't get good results,
I intruded for too long.
-I should go.
-Hey, wait.
Su Zaizai, are you leaving like this?
This is unacceptable.
Mr. Lin,
we couldn't find a place
for the tutoring session,
so we came to your home.
This is not Zhang Lurang's fault.
How could you do this?
She came here to study.
How could you chase her away
because she didn't do well?
It's still early anyway.
Well, you can explain the problems
that she didn't understand.
What?
Stop asking.
Being passionate
about your studies is good.
It's all right.
If it gets too late,
I'll have Lurang see you home.
All right? Continue.
I'll be grading homework in the study.
I'll start with the second problem.
No wonder.
Now that I look at you closely,
you have Mr. Lin's eyebrows.
Am I the last to know?
I don't normally tell people.
That's great.
I'm the first person to know your secret.
I'll keep this a secret,
so add a few extra points
to my math paper.
This is not a secret.
There's no need to keep it.
Watch your step.
My main problem
is no one is rehearsing the lines with me.
I can only think about it while walking.
Perhaps
I will think about it while I'm eating,
sleeping,
and attending classes.
What should I do if this goes on?
I think...
You have been doing well
in the tutoring sessions.
You didn't skip any lessons
and you have been serious.
I can reward you with ten points.
Ten points?
I have 95 points then.
Rangrang,
do you agree to rehearse my lines with me?
Rangrang, you are so nice.
I'm just helping out.
Exactly.
Handsome and kind. You're so wonderful.
Is it your first time in my room?
Don't be so reserved.
Be casual.
Make yourselves at home.
Guan Fang,
I think you're the most reserved one.
Am I?
I don't think so.
No other classmates have ever been here.
I'm not used to it.
Where is your grandma? I didn't see her.
She hasn't come back yet.
I saw a balcony when I was outside.
We can rehearse our play there.
Why are we using your room?
Only my room is soundproof.
I'm afraid people will complain
if we do it out there.
You must be exaggerating.
Memorize the lines first.
We can rehearse together later.
Sure.
Let me give you the scripts.
I only have two copies.
I have a copy of my own.
Here it is.
Why don't you read the highlight scene
where the prince
asks Cinderella for a dance?
We will help you with this.
Sure.
Let me...
"Pretty lady,
may I invite you to a dance?"
Rangrang, show some emotion.
You need to put in some emotion.
Wasn't that enough?
You sound shy.
Think of her
as someone you just fell in love with
and were intimate with for the first time.
Don't you feel happy?
Don't you feel excited?
Pretty lady,
may I invite you to a dance?
Not bad.
This is good. Keep it up.
Why me?
Because I only have eyes for you
in the ball.
You are so beautiful.
-He only has eyes for you.
It's time to dance.
I think it's good to add a hug here.
I think it works.
I don't think that's good.
-Why?
-Have you memorized your lines?
Lines? I have memorized them.
She is your maid!
Sister!
She can help you
clean...
Do your laundry and cook.
Did they clean by hand in that era?
Guan Fang, you have so many questions.
Why don't you go out
and practice on your own?
Come back later.
It's just memorizing lines.
I can do it in a few minutes.
Let's put on some music.
Cinderella,
is this your dress?
Look at you.
No, I think
I need to be more evil.
Xiaofang, give me a hand.
What rubbish do you have in your hands?
These are fresh vegetables.
They are not rubbish.
You...
Xiaofang, I told you many times.
I told you to arrange your shoes neatly
when you come home.
Look at you.
Tell me.
Am I your maid or your grandma?
You are my maid, of course.
How dare a maid
have such fantasies?
You!
You're getting worse as you grow older.
What did you call me? A maid?
-How dare you!
-Grandma, what are you doing?
Seriously!
What? What did I do?
What did you do?
Tell me!
-You tell me!
-What have I done, Grandma?
-You!
-Stop hitting me!
-You tell me what is wrong with you!
-Grandma!
You!
It hurts!
Hello, Mrs. Guan.
Are you beating up your grandson?
Please continue.
We are just watching. Don't mind us.
Grandma!
Is it a play?
Yes, Grandma.
Think about it.
How would I dare to scold you?
We will also be performing this play
on a big stage later.
Is Xiaofang going to perform too?
With my ears now,
I don't even need props to play an elf.
Grandma,
do you want to see our performance first?
Yes. We don't have any audience.
Sure.
I've never watched a play before.
Come on.
Come.
Once upon a time,
there was a beautiful princess.
Her name was Cinderella.
Although her father had left her
when she was very young,
her mother loved her dearly.
One day, her mother
found her
a stepfather.
This is
your sister.
She can do your laundry, mop the floor,
and cook.
Everyone, come and bully her!
This is not your part yet.
Wait for a while.
Go and mop the floor!
Who do you think you are?
It's fine.
Here, turn.
Come.
Hurry up.
Your Highness, you are such a fool!
You missed Cinderella again!
What are you doing, Rangrang?
I'm reading the script.
Familiarize yourself with it then.
Help me record a video.
I'm afraid I'll forget
when I rehearse alone.
I want to see
what still needs improvement.
Sure.
Thank you, Rangrang.
Look. She is your sister.
But there is no need to worry.
She can do your laundry and cook.
Why?
From today onward, you are our maid.
I had a very long dream that night.
The fairy tale in my dream
had a perfect ending.
I HAD A VERY LONG DREAM THAT NIGHT
THE FAIRY TALE IN MY DREAM
HAD A PERFECT ENDING.