Three, two, one!
-Cheese!
ADAPTED FROM ZHU YI'S NOVEL,
SHE'S A LITTLE CRAZY, ON JJWXC.NET
-Kiss!
Those Moments I Have Never Regretted.
Bye.
How was it?
Wasn't I cool?
Yes.
Did you hear that?
Cool!
-Nice!
-Let's take a break.
Why is she still here?
I shouldn't have been so charismatic.
What did you say?
Come here.
Look.
She's looking this way again.
There are so many people here.
This is embarrassing.
Why do I feel
like she's not looking at you?
Impossible.
Shen Qianyu, go for it!
Go, Shen Qianyu!
The person you like is Shen Qianyu?
Yes. Why?
Then...
Then why did you...
Why did you keep smiling at me?
Who was looking at you?
I was looking at Qianyu.
But you kept blocking my view
and spouting nonsense.
You praised me during military training.
You have some nerves to mention that.
If you hadn't posed as Zhang Lurang,
would we have got your names wrong?
You got our names wrong?
Yes.
How could you get our names wrong?
One has two characters.
The other has three.
One is Zhang. The other is Gu.
One is
handsome.
And the other is even more so!
How could you get our names wrong?
Are you asking me?
This is a huge misunderstanding.
So were you praising Zhang Lurang?
Of course. Would I praise you?
Did he wake up
on the wrong side of the bed?
So that's the truth.
Only an instant cardio-reliever pill
can save him now.
No wonder.
I wondered why you were always around
when I played basketball with Qianyu.
You do have ulterior motives.
Watch what you say.
What do you mean by...
Did you call him Qianyu?
Do you know him?
Yes. Our dads are colleagues.
We play basketball together a lot.
What?
You had such a long game just now.
Are you tired? Are you thirsty?
Do you have enough milk tea?
Would you like me to buy you another cup?
Hey, Gu Ran.
Don't go!
You said Qianyu likes the color white.
What kind of white?
Off-white? Ivory? Cream?
Gu Ran, don't be so petty!
We could talk about something else,
such as what Qianyu likes to eat,
drink, or read.
You should know all that, right?
Can you stop following me?
Gu Ran, don't run!
Why are you still here?
It's none of your business.
Gu Ran.
My dad is working overtime today.
So are your parents.
Why don't we dine out together?
Sure.
You can bring your friend if you want.
-I don't...
-Me!
I want to come too.
Are we friends?
Of course not.
Our relationship exceeds friendship.
We were late and got punished together.
We've been through thick and thin.
Our friendship is more precious than gold.
Don't force me to tell people
that you were locked in.
She is absolutely right.
We...
We're really good friends.
-Let's go then.
-Let's go!
DRAMA CLUB
I forgot.
I have to help Ms. Zhang
tabulate the scores for the midterms.
You guys should leave first.
Are you doing it alone?
Yes. I just have a little left.
Do you think I'm capable?
Are you a little impressed?
You sure aren't humble.
We'll get going then.
-Bye.
Why is it suddenly raining?
It doesn't look like
it will stop anytime soon.
I guess I'll wait.
Rangrang,
I read my horoscope the other day.
The book said my lucky element is water.
I didn't believe it at first,
but now I think it's pretty accurate.
Why?
Because good things happen when it rains.
I first met you
at a corner store in the rain.
I learned your name
in a field in the rain.
All rainy days
seem connected to you.
It rained three times last week
and twice this week.
In that case,
only rainy days connected to you
are meaningful to me.
Rangrang, surely you didn't come back
just for me today?
I forgot my notes.
I see.
If it rains next time
and you don't bring an umbrella,
you can check in the teacher's office.
They might have a spare umbrella.
But if you tell me in advance
that you will be coming,
I don't mind being in the rain again.
Here.
Your house is up ahead.
You can take the umbrella.
Rangrang!
See you tomorrow!
Did you win the lottery?
Why are you suddenly treating me?
You're so cheerful too.
The food in the canteen
was delicious today.
Can't I be happy about it?
Hurry up and choose.
You said it's your treat.
I won't hold back.
A treat?
Who is treating?
Me! I'm feeling happy today.
I'm treating everyone.
Then I won't hold back either.
Hurry.
-Get more.
-Why is it them again?
They sure like the attention.
Let's go.
Zaizai, do you have enough pocket money?
Rest assured.
My dad gave me money this morning.
What should I get for Rangrang?
Did they all go out for lunch?
Keep it up!
A REWARD FROM FAIRY ZAI!
Su Zaizai?
Why are you here?
Of course I have something going on.
Don't you have your own classroom?
Why do you keep visiting our class?
Is English the first class after lunch?
What's wrong?
I'm doomed.
There's dictation. I'm doomed.
I forgot to memorize them!
Has anyone seen an envelope?
-An envelope?
-Yes.
Is it a love letter?
What love letter? It's our class fund!
Is the class fund missing?
Yes, I just went out to get newspapers.
It was gone when I came back.
Don't panic. Look for it again.
-You should tell the teacher quickly.
-That shouldn't be.
Okay.
Ms. Zhang!
Ye Zhenxin, why are you panicking?
Our class fund seems to have been stolen!
I can't find it anywhere.
Don't jump to conclusions.
It's serious if it involves theft.
That's right.
Have you searched thoroughly?
I was counting the money
in the classroom during lunch.
Midway through,
I went to the mart to buy a pen.
Then I went to get newspapers
at the Office of Academic Affairs.
The money was gone when I returned.
How long were you away?
Was there no one in the classroom?
I was away for about ten minutes.
When I returned,
I only saw
one person, Su Zaizai.
Stop crying.
-Let's go check the security footage.
-Okay.
Mr. Chang, calm down first.
Ye Zhenxin might have
accidentally left the money somewhere.
Let's look for it again.
The security camera caught everything.
Ye Zhenxin has always been
an exemplary student.
Why would she lie?
Mr. Chang.
Mr. Chang,
you wanted to see me?
Su Zaizai,
during the break,
did you visit Class 1?
I did.
Why did you go there?
Did you go to see a teacher?
Did something happen?
Class 1's class fund is missing.
When we checked the security footage,
you were the only one in Class 1
during the break.
So
are you suspecting me
of stealing the money?
I didn't steal anything.
Mr. Chang.
I believe Su Zaizai wouldn't steal.
She has always been a good student.
She's also very helpful. She...
We'll just talk about the facts today.
Tell us.
Why did you go
to Class 1?
I went to see my friend,
but he wasn't there.
Su Zaizai,
during the break,
didn't you treat several classmates
to snacks
in the mart today?
Where did that money come from?
What are you implying?
That was my own money.
I went to the mart
before visiting your class.
Is there any relation between the two?
I just want
to clear up the misunderstanding.
In that case,
you went there after me as well.
Doesn't that also make you a suspect?
What nonsense is that?
That's impossible.
Ye Zhenxin went back to her own classroom.
Mr. Chang,
I don't think my class has any relevance.
If you suspect me of taking the money,
Ye Zhenxin should prove it with evidence.
The burden of proof shouldn't be mine.
Su Zaizai.
We are all willing
to believe you.
But you have to give us
a reasonable explanation.
You're from Class 9.
Why weren't you in your classroom
instead of visiting Class 1?
She was there to see me.
Sometimes, falling for a person
can happen in an instant.
I remember that moment clearly.
It was a rainy day.
It was the moment he glanced over.
It was the moment our eyes met.
But I never understood
the reason I fell for him.
But the lucky thing is
I've never regretted it.
I've never regretted going to the mart
when it was raining.
I've never regretted
scolding him for no reason.
I've never regretted meeting him
and then falling for him.
She knew you were not in the classroom,
but she still entered your class.
Why is that?
She was there to bring me notes.
Notes?
Su Zaizai explained a problem to me once.
I know about that.
I asked her to do it.
I thought she explained it well,
so I asked her to tutor me.
She was there today to give me notes.
Here are the notes.
CLASSIFICATION OF VERBS
AUXILIARY VERBS, MODAL VERBS
Students helping each other out
is a good thing.
You should've told us from the start.
But Mr. Chang,
we still haven't found the class fund.
Besides,
during that period,
Su Zaizai was indeed the only one
in our classroom.
And after I left,
you were also alone in the classroom.
I discovered that the money was missing
after I returned.
Also, if you weren't feeling guilty,
why didn't you explain things
before Zhang Lurang got here?
I asked her to keep it a secret.
Because I don't want others to know
that my English scores are so bad
and I need to be tutored
by a student from a regular class.
That's not a good way to think.
What's wrong with a regular class?
Everyone has their strengths.
Su Zaizai was kind enough
to tutor you
and she even got misunderstood.
It might not be a misunderstanding.
Ye Zhenxin,
we do not have sufficient evidence
to prove that Su Zaizai took the money.
Before the truth comes to light,
if we spread baseless rumors
based on our speculations,
that would hurt other students too.
Don't you think so?
That's right, Mr. Chang.
I feel
we should investigate this properly.
You're right.
How about this, Ms. Zhang?
Return to the classroom first
and search the classroom thoroughly.
Before we have any concrete clues,
let's not suspect any student.
Okay, Mr. Chang.
I will investigate this properly.
Okay. Leave this matter to the teachers.
Head back first.
Let's go.
Wait. Your notes.
They're pretty good.
Keep it up.
Thank you, Ms. Zhang.
Su Zaizai.
You...
Why didn't you tell them just now?
Why didn't you say
that you came to see me?
Didn't you say
that you don't want others to know
you're bad at English
and need to be tutored
by a student from a regular class?
I feel the same way.
I'm worried you might feel embarrassed.
That's not it.
I don't find it embarrassing.
I also don't want the teachers
to misunderstand you.
However, I really didn't know
your class collected class funds today.
And I don't know where Ye Zhenxin sits.
I just wanted to put the notes
on your table
along with the snacks and cola.
Su Zaizai.
I believe you.
The more I think about it,
the angrier I feel.
How could they interrogate you
without any evidence?
I just hope they find the money quickly.
Otherwise, even without evidence,
they will still suspect me.
What if they really can't find it?
Shouldn't the person
who lost it be held responsible?
That makes sense.
Ye Zhenxin is not a kid.
How could she lose the funds like that?
Or is it that no matter what happens,
you can act sorry
and cry your way out of it?
Why don't you cry too?
You should act pitiful too.
Anyone can do that!
That's right. You should cry too.
Cry.
Like this?
No, that's not real enough.
GRADE 10, CLASS 1
Who stole it?
I heard it was Su Zaizai from Class 9.
So she stole it?
I think so.
Didn't you see her steal it that day?
What are you talking about?
The tri-city joint exam
is right around the corner.
Must you talk during class?
Regarding the class fund,
please refrain from discussing it.
Let's all look for it after class.
Even if we can't find it,
the teachers will handle it.
Just focus on your studies.
Help me pass it.
What is this?
I knew it.
-Pass it back.
-Okay.
I THINK IT WAS HER!
WE SHOULD GET IT BACK FROM HER.
HAVE YOU HEARD?
WE LOST OUR CLASS FUNDS.
WHAT? IT'S OVER 2,000 YUAN!
FOR SOME REASON,
A GIRL FROM CLASS 9
WAS IN OUR CLASSROOM.
Jiangjiang.
Are you going straight home after school?
-If you have time...
-You go first.
I have plans. Be careful on your way home.
Ma'am, where is
Class 1's trash from today?
We have so much trash every day.
How would I remember?
We dump them all together.
But all the trash from Grade 10 is here.
There's another heap there too.
Thank you, ma'am.
No problem.
I don't see it here either.
Search more thoroughly!
Zhang Lurang, take that one.
Su Zaizai.
What do you mean by Su Zaizai?
That sundae was quite yummy.
-Let's go after class.
-Sure.
We'll go after class.
Ye Zhenxin, have you found the class fund?
No.
I thought you found it
since you seem so relaxed.
That's right.
You're acting
like we're the ones who lost it.
I helped collect the class funds.
Am I to blame for it being missing?
Ye Zhenxin.
Why don't you think it over again?
Could it be that you misplaced it?
I don't understand.
Why do you guys trust someone
from another class so much?
Okay. Do you guys not believe me?
Here. Search for yourselves.
You had better find it.
Otherwise, I...
What?
What will you do?
What is in the book?
-It really is her.
-It's her.
She put it in her book.
Is that the class fund?
Do you really want us
to see it for ourselves?
She really had it.
-Did she hide it herself?
-She must've hid it, right?
Don't malign me!
I really couldn't find it yesterday!
Who knows
if Su Zaizai put it back here?
Ye Zhenxin.
Rumors can do a lot of damage.
Haven't you realized that by now?
I'm sorry, Zhang Lurang.
I dragged you into this by accident.
I'm really sorry.
You don't have to apologize to me.
You owe Su Zaizai an apology.
It has been found!
What has been found?
That thing. Class 1's class fund.
They found it in their own classroom!
That's great.
Your innocence has been proven.
How did they find it?
I was just getting there.
It's so dramatic!
The money
was right inside their class rep's bag.
They found it on the spot!
She totally made a fool of herself.
Why didn't they find it before?
She never searched properly.
This is outrageous.
The money was with her all along.
How could she accuse you so confidently?
That's right.
I'm going out for a bit.
Where are you going?
Are you skipping your break?
I need an apology.
I'll go with you!
What's going on?
I don't know. Let's see.
Look.
Do you need this many people to watch?
It's break time.
There are people everywhere.
If you prefer,
we could go to the teacher's office
and talk in private.
We'll do it here then.
I'm sorry. All right?
Do you call that an apology?
You didn't even look into my eyes.
Okay, I'll say it again.
I am sorry.
Surely you've heard it now?
I heard it.
But
I don't accept it.
What do you mean?
"I'm sorry" and "It's fine"
are sincere words
spoken to correct mistakes and hurt.
They are not words spoken carelessly
as you just did
to pretend that mistakes didn't occur.
If that's the case,
I don't accept this apology.
-Su Zaizai!
-That girl is pretty cool.
What is her name?
I don't know.
Zhang Lurang, have dinner at my place.
My grandma has been talking
about letting you guys try her new dish.
Tonight?
Come on. It's the weekend tomorrow anyway.
I've told Su Zaizai and the others too.
Okay.
Actually, I really have to thank
Guan Fang and the guys.
No matter how other people suspected me,
they always believed me.
They even helped me find the money
in the end.
I am very grateful to them.
Boys this age are like that.
They look childish,
but instead of speaking nice words,
they prefer to show it with their actions.
Here.
Take your time eating, all right?
I'm going to the other street
for some ingredients.
Grandma, I'll go with you.
No, I can go by myself.
Just keep your friends company.
Take whatever you need.
Okay.
What were you guys talking about?
Nothing.
Here. Cheers.
I'll treat everyone
to the amusement park tomorrow.
-Cheers!
-Bottoms up!
By the way,
who asked Ye Zhenxin to check her bag?
Didn't she insist that she didn't have it?
I think it was...
The two of them.
Was it us?
I don't really remember.
No matter who it was,
I'm really grateful.
I am actually pretty touched.
We usually fool around.
Being so serious feels so weird.
And don't people usually cry
during such touching moments in dramas?
You didn't cry at all.
No problem.
Zaizai, cry.
Listen, Zaizai is really good
at pretending to cry.
She trembles and her shoulders shake.
She can also...
That's hard to believe.
Is it that realistic?
It is.
Have you seen it?
Are you angry because I pretended to cry?
No.
What is on your mind then?
In the teacher's office,
Ye Zhenxin cried,
so the teachers all sided with her.
Since you're so good at pretending to cry,
why did you only fume?
Why should I cry?
Only those who made mistakes cry.
I wasn't in the wrong.
I'll head back first then.
Zhang Lurang.
Guan Fang secretly told me this.
You demanded an apology
from Ye Zhenxin for me.
-I...
-Thank you.
I just wanted to say thank you.
Good night. See you tomorrow.
Zaizai!
It's not our meet-up time yet.
Why are you guys so early?
How can we not be enthusiastic
about going to the amusement park?
Everybody is here now. Let's go.
Let's go!
I want this one!
Only girls would like that.
What do you think? Is it cute?
Ours is a pair.
Here, I'll get the same one for you.
You must wear it.
Otherwise, people might think
we're excluding you.
Are you happy now?
Let's go!
Hey.
Can I ask you for a favor?
Look.
Why are you wearing the same one as mine?
It's not like I want to.
It's because...
Well, it's because
my head is too big.
And it happened
that Su Zaizai's headband was bigger,
so we swapped.
Don't forget the comics you promised me.
You have my word.
I haven't been
to an amusement park in ages!
I want to ride that! Come on!
Hurry up!
Come on!
I'm spent!
We've taken the pendulum three times.
I'll never take my feet
off the ground again.
I'm never going
on such a thrilling ride again.
We can't waste the ticket!
Why are you guys sitting down?
Won't you consider
going on the Ferris Wheel?
Zaizai,
you don't need to count me in.
I've also reached my limit.
I don't mind sitting in the breeze here.
Then what about you, Zhang Lurang?
Sure.
It's beautiful.
Make a wish.
Make a wish?
Don't you watch dramas?
A wish made
at the Ferris Wheel's highest point
has the greatest chance of coming true.
I don't have any wishes.
I'll make two wishes then.
I won't wish for things
like suddenly becoming smart
or winning the lottery.
I'll make the simplest wishes.
My first wish is that we all did well
in the exam we just finished.
My second wish
is that Rangrang will smile more.
I noticed that he has dimples
when he smiles.
It looks so nice.
Rangrang.
You smiled, didn't you?
I didn't.
You clearly did.
Today, let me introduce my best friends.
Be clear. Who is the best?
Jiang Jia, why are you so competitive?
So what if I am? So what?
-Childish.
-You're the childish one!
All right. Ignore them.
Why don't I go first?
What's with that?
Okay, I'll start over.
Let me introduce my best friends.
Zhang Lurang, come closer.
They are Zhang Lurang...
Su Zaizai, I should come first!
Okay.
They are Jiang Jia,
Zhang Lurang,
Gu Ran,
and Guan Fang.
Why did I come last? Start over.
Hey, you pressed the wrong button!
If I could stop time,
I would never let our friendship fade.
I wouldn't let any of them slip away.
IF I COULD STOP TIME,
I WOULD NEVER LET OUR FRIENDSHIP FADE.
I WOULDN'T LET ANY OF THEM SLIP AWAY.