Three, two, one!
-Cheese!
ADAPTED FROM ZHU YI'S NOVEL,
SHE'S A LITTLE CRAZY, ON JJWXC.NET
-Kiss!
Hey, My Prince.
Mr. Lin, did you ask to see me?
Su Zaizai.
You can tell me
if I've done anything wrong.
I'll do better.
Has Rangrang caused you any trouble
while you were tutoring him?
No, he hasn't.
He has also tutored me.
I'm the one that troubles him.
To be honest,
English has always been his weakness.
He has scored poorly in it
since middle school.
His parents have always been worried
about this.
Your tutoring
has been quite effective for him.
There has been a marked improvement
in his grades lately.
Thank you.
It was Rangrang...
Zhang Lurang is smart.
He's a quick learner.
I'm saying this as Lurang's uncle.
I have to thank you.
By the way,
if you have any math questions,
you can ask me at any time.
Of course, you can ask Lurang too.
Okay.
I'll definitely ask you
if I have any questions.
Thank you, Mr. Lin.
GRADE 10, CLASS 9
-Let's go. Bye.
-Bye.
Hey, Zaizai.
Why did Mr. Lin
want to see you during the break?
It was about tutoring Zhang Lurang.
I thought he was going to scold us
for messing around.
But instead,
he thanked me.
He is quite happy
about Zhang Lurang's improved English.
Mr. Lin is really good to Zhang Lurang.
He does.
It would be great
if I had an uncle like that.
Jiangjiang,
I'm not leaving with you today.
-I still...
-I know.
Tutoring.
Your joy is all over your face.
-Go quickly.
-You can leave with Gu Ran.
No, thank you.
Go on now.
There is something on your skirt.
Hey.
Do you have any?
I only have this.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Why are there still so many people around?
Gu Ran!
What's up?
Just say it. Don't be awkward.
Are you about to head home?
Can you give me a ride?
No, I'm going to play basketball.
Wait here for me for a bit.
It'll be late when he's done playing.
Forget it. What do I expect from him?
Jiang Jia?
Qianyu?
What's wrong?
I...
Well...
I have a leg cramp.
No, it's my stomach.
What am I saying?
Where do you live?
I'll give you a ride home.
Qianyu,
will it be too much trouble
for you to give me a ride home?
It's okay. I live in that area too.
It's on the way.
Tomorrow is
the school anniversary performance.
Will you be okay to do it?
Yes.
I'm feeling a lot better now.
Then do your best tomorrow.
Okay, let's both do our best.
Are you taking pictures of the sunset?
Yes.
Today's sunset is beautiful.
What's the matter?
It's okay.
You can finish taking pictures.
This is the most beautiful sunset
I've ever seen.
THE FIRST HIGH SCHOOL
AFFILIATED TO JIANGYI UNIVERSITY
Today, we gather here
to celebrate the 60th anniversary
of The First High School.
Today, with great excitement,
we reminisce about the fast growth
of The First High School.
What's our queue number?
The fifth.
Be quiet. I'm going through my lines.
Where is Su Zaizai?
She just went to get changed.
Her hairstyle is a little complicated.
But she should be...
Gosh.
It looks so real.
You do look like Cinderella.
Stop talking nonsense.
Next time, I'll let you play Cinderella.
Actually, I think it looks pretty.
-It is pretty.
-Let Qianyu see it too.
Where is Qianyu?
I don't know.
I don't think I have seen him today.
We're about to go on.
Don't tell me he's not here yet.
Don't worry. I'll look for him.
Relax.
Recite your lines in your head.
Come on, everyone.
Is Qianyu injured?
What exactly happened?
I searched everywhere
but couldn't find him.
I finally reached him
after several phone calls.
Qianyu fell off his bike
on his way to school.
He's at the hospital now.
-He probably can't make it.
-Is it serious?
Don't worry.
He's fine.
Now we should be worried
about our performance.
What should we do?
Coming next is the fashion show,
Era of Painted Impressions.
Please get ready.
We didn't pick a backup prince.
Even if we manage to find someone,
he won't have time to memorize the lines.
Zhang Lurang,
can you go on stage?
-Me?
-That's right.
Why didn't I think of it?
Lurang knows the lines.
Lurang,
you must not back down.
You must go on stage.
I have confidence in you.
You can do it.
Lurang,
I told my grandma.
I don't want
to miss the chance to go on stage.
That's right.
We've practiced for so long.
Help us out, please.
Help me out too, please.
Okay.
I'll try.
Rangrang, don't be nervous.
Just do as we usually rehearsed.
Are you nervous?
No, I'm not.
Just admit that you're nervous.
What's the big deal anyway?
I won't laugh at you.
Actually,
I'm a little nervous.
Are you really nervous?
I guarantee you won't be nervous
with my method.
When you go on stage later,
just imagine the audience as cabbages.
Cabbages?
Yes.
What is there to be nervous about
in front of cabbages?
Am I right?
And even if you make a mistake,
what does it matter
when it's for cabbages?
But you still have to be a little nervous.
After all,
a handsome cabbage like me
is sitting in the audience.
You're too self-absorbed.
Are you still nervous now?
Well, not really.
The fashion show segment
showcasing the characteristics of the era
was truly memorable.
But the excitement doesn't end here.
It's our turn to go on stage.
Break a leg.
All the best.
Let's do this.
Coming up next,
please enjoy
the classic theater adaptation
of Cinderella
presented by the Drama Club.
A long time ago,
there lived a beautiful girl
named Cinderella.
Although her father had left her,
her mother loved her dearly.
Until one day,
her mother married
a selfish and narrow-minded man.
Father, who is she?
She's so filthy.
She's your stepsister.
Don't worry, my little princesses.
She can do
the laundry
and cook for you.
Why?
From today onwards,
you will be our servant!
We have a professional videographer.
I know.
I'm filming it for Guan Fang's grandma.
She will love this.
Your Highness, no girl in this house
can fit into the glass slipper.
May I try it?
Didn't you say
you only have two daughters?
Your Excellency,
I indeed only have two daughters.
This filthy girl is just our servant.
She's dirty
and will ruin this beautiful shoe.
Take her up to the attic now!
The evil stepsister in the green dress
isn't hateful at all.
She's quite cute.
Cute?
Yes. Why?
How is she cute?
She even stumbles while walking.
She's as stubborn as a donkey.
How is she cute?
Do you know her?
Then introduce her to me.
We are not close.
My dear prince,
you're like the moon high above
casting a gentle light on the sea.
I gaze from afar
and everything seems so beautiful to me.
But the moon doesn't belong to me
and neither do you.
I used to think
that it was the fairy's magic
that turned me into a princess.
But now that you are standing before me,
I realize
that every girl is a princess
in front of the one that she loves.
When I fly toward the moon,
the moon
is also learning to run forward for me.
It's a reward for your good performance.
Thank you.
Rangrang,
why do you keep avoiding looking at me?
I won't charge you for looking at me.
Rangrang,
do I look pretty today?
So-so.
You clearly think I look pretty.
I'll go and get changed first.
Hey, wait.
We just finished taking photos.
There's still film left.
Shall I take a photo of you two?
Yes, since you haven't changed yet.
It will be so memorable.
And they look like the real deal.
What's going on?
Well,
a prince and a princess.
What else could it be?
Hurry, the auditorium is closing soon.
How about that spot?
Ready.
Is there a wall between you two?
Get closer.
Okay, look at the camera. One.
Two.
Three.
Grandma.
You've watched it so many times.
Aren't you tired of it?
Of course not.
Look at how well you acted.
I can't have enough of this.
Grandma, look closely.
I'm not even on stage yet at this point.
Who says you're not?
The one who is sneaking a peek
from behind the red curtain.
Isn't this you?
Your eyesight
is even worse than an old lady like me.
I can't believe you spotted that.
You first performed on stage
when you were in kindergarten.
At that time,
among the 20 children
who were wearing identical clothes,
I spotted you at one glance.
Don't you think it's strange?
They tried to find you but couldn't.
But how did I manage to do it right away?
That's because you have sharp eyes.
Next time,
I'll strive to get the lead role
and stand right in the middle of the stage
to save you the trouble.
Do you want to be the lead?
To be honest,
it would be a lot of work.
Then don't be the lead.
It's so tiring to be the lead.
They have to shine brightly
and make sure everyone can see them.
You don't necessarily
have to become the sun.
If you're willing to,
you could be a star,
a streetlight,
or a firefly.
They are all capable of shining.
When they want to shine, they shine.
When they don't feel like shining,
they can slack off.
Even if you never shine,
some people
could still spot you at a glance.
Grandma, where did you learn
such a grand speech?
Who recorded this video?
Gu Ran.
You've met him several times.
Did he record it for someone else?
Why weren't you
in the video after this part?
Really?
Let me see.
I guess she does look cute.
Why am I watching her?
Are you going?
Yes.
What a surprise.
Su Zaizai
is so popular.
They must be asking
for her contact information.
After the anniversary celebration,
many boys gathered
at our classroom door to look at her.
Your Cinderella might be taken away.
Are you jealous?
Why would I be jealous?
That guy asked me for my WeChat today.
I don't plan to give it to him.
Why are you suddenly bringing this up?
I want you to trust me.
So I have to let you know.
After all, I am...
your student.
Students should listen to their teachers.
You told me to study hard
and I will.
If you stay silent,
that means you agree with me.
But as your English teacher,
I'm not very satisfied
with your performance.
Why?
It's dangerous
when a stranger offers drinks.
What if they're a bad person?
What should I do then?
You should yell my name,
"Su Zaizai!"
Then I'll appear
to get you out of trouble.
Do you remember that?
Then I'll see you tomorrow.
Su Zaizai.
I...
I'll try.
See you tomorrow.
Rangrang is becoming more adorable.
Lurang, I heard
you're close with Su Zaizai from Class 9.
Do you have her contact information?
I want to be friends with her.
I'll treat you to a meal tomorrow.
Contact information?
Then do you want to give it to him?
I'll answer on your behalf.
No.
Rangrang, you must keep the good things
for yourself.
What are you doing?
Passersby would think
you're going in for a fight.
I thought you were fearless.
What is so hard about entering a ward?
I think it's better
for us to go in together.
Are Zhang Lurang and the others
arriving soon?
We should wait for them.
A car hit me
when I was riding my bike.
I just need to wear a cast for a while.
It's nothing serious.
You guys are too generous.
These are all from Jiang Jia.
I told her you can't finish all of this.
I'll share it with you.
Thank you.
My grandma made this pig's trotter soup.
She said it's good for bone injuries.
-Okay.
-That's right.
Qianyu, take good care of your injury.
You must've been panicking at that time.
Luckily, you saved the day.
You guys even won first prize.
Thank you.
No problem.
That's right, Gu Ran.
I might need your help with something.
What is it?
We need to return several props
to the rental place.
Do you have time to go tomorrow?
We agreed on the return time
when we rented them.
Okay, I'll go tomorrow.
Thank you.
Let me serve you a bowl.
All right.
Do you want to go too?
There are quite a lot of props.
I'm afraid you might lose them
and we'll have to pay compensation.
So I'll go with you despite the trouble.
Thank you for earlier.
So this is why you're going with me.
Why do you talk so much?
If I don't have to go, then forget it.
It's good to have an extra pair of hands.
Don't leave.
What time tomorrow?
Where should we meet?
I'm almost there. Where are you?
I think I lost my way.
I'll be there soon. One more block.
I wonder who is the one helping out.
Isn't that the guy from before?
If Shen Qianyu were the one waiting here,
she would have probably come running.
Are you waiting for someone?
Do you know me?
Really? How forgetful of you.
You beat us by one point
on the basketball court
and embarrassed us in front of everyone.
Have you forgotten so quickly?
I remember it now.
My friend said the ball was really good.
Thank you. I'm busy.
I have to go.
Did I say you can go?
We've been wanting
to reclaim that ball for a long time.
Sorry, I don't want to play today.
Hold on.
Who asked for your opinion?
I said that I'm not playing.
Are you deaf?
Say that again.
Gu Ran.
Stand behind me.
Are you protecting me?
Stop talking. Just watch.
Are you protecting him?
Who are you?
Really?
Are you letting a girl fight for you?
You're just jealous.
Me? Jealous?
Fine.
Let's do this.
I just got my blue belt
and haven't had a chance to practice.
Officer, they're the ones!
Hey!
Stop right there!
What's a blue belt?
It's the rank below a black belt.
They wouldn't believe I'm a black belt.
What do you think? Wasn't I convincing?
Actually,
that would be a red belt.
Mr. Lin,
you're early.
I went to buy some fruit.
By the way, Mr. Lin,
will Lurang also be competing
in a few days?
Yes, he has been studying every day.
He even studies on the weekends.
Your nephew is the most disciplined person
in this area.
Are you going to study this early?
No, I'm going to the aquarium.
It's a good work-life balance.
He also likes
to go out with friends to relax.
Boys tend to be more lively.
Yes, you're right.
-Right.
-Are you going out with Gu Ran?
Don't come back too late, okay?
Zhang Lurang.
Hello, Mr. Lin.
Su Zaizai?
We won't take up your time, Mr. Lin.
We'll get going then.
Why is there a girl?
Listen, kids these days
get close far too easily.
Mr. Lin is going to get upset now.
You said you're going to the aquarium.
You don't have to hurry home.
It's okay if you come home late.
But you must see her home first.
By the way,
the weather is getting cold.
When you buy drinks, get something hot.
Do you have money? I'll give you some.
It's okay.
Uncle, I'll get going then.
Okay. Go on.
Bye, Mr. Lin.
Okay, bye.
These all seem to be tropical fish.
-Really?
-That one is so colorful.
-Rangrang.
-Yes, it's pretty.
Have you never been
to the Jiangyi Aquarium before?
It's okay. I'm familiar with this place.
I can be your tour guide for free.
Look at that.
It's called
a doll fish.
It looks like a doll.
It's so cute.
Children, look at this.
This bright orange fish
with two white stripes
on its body
is called a clownfish.
Despite its name,
it doesn't look like a clown at all.
It's actually very cute.
Well,
I wasn't entirely wrong.
It does look cute.
I was half right.
Look at that long one over there.
It doesn't look like a fish at all,
but it's also a fish.
It's called a stingray.
That one is called a stingray
and looks like a devil.
Rangrang, look at that fish.
It's so pretty and cute.
Children, we should learn
from this young lady
and love marine life.
It's getting more attractive.
It's so fleshy.
It would be delicious
as Sichuan boiled fish.
The size is just right.
My pot at home is exactly this big.
Miss, this young lady wants to eat it!
Don't!
I don't plan to eat it right now.
She's joking with you. She can't eat it.
She can't eat it.
The young lady won't actually eat it.
She said that because she finds it cute
and really likes it.
Really?
You're very cute too.
Rangrang,
I didn't know
you were so good at coaxing kids.
I'm not.
I was forced to.
Well,
can you coax a 200-month-old kid?
You don't have to.
Kids who are 200 months old are sensible.
Rangrang!
Su Zaizai.
Hello.
We're currently rehearsing our lines.
Beside me is my male lead,
Prince Rangrang.
Su Zaizai,
have you memorized
the final paragraph of your lines?
I used to think
that it was the fairy's magic
that turned me into a princess.
It wasn't until the clock struck midnight
that I was brought back to reality.
How can I be good enough for you?
Have you forgotten your lines?
Rangrang,
I think I've found the reason
I always get stuck here.
What is it?
It's because I can't accept it.
I think
Cinderella thinks too little of herself.
Why isn't shegood enough for the prince?
Does only a princess deserve a prince?
I don't think so.
I want to ask Mr. Xiao
to change the script.
Rangrang, how should we change it?
Maybe we can change it to this.
Perhaps every girl
can become a princess
in front of the one that she loves.
Sixteen-year-old girls seem to be able
to constantly immerse themselves
in novels and movies,
making it their sweet and lovely secret.