Three, two, one!
-Cheese!
ADAPTED FROM ZHU YI'S NOVEL,
SHE'S A LITTLE CRAZY, ON JJWXC.NET
-Kiss!
Go and See a Brighter Light.
A summer market?
Yes.
Rangrang said there will be a market
at Haiyue Square tomorrow.
He said we should go together.
Do you think I should
use this chance
to confess my feelings to him?
Would it be proper?
Why wouldn't it be?
I think so too.
But Zaizai,
say you confess now.
What if you and Zhang Lurang
don't go to the same university?
It will be four years.
Whatever.
Any place can be reached
by train or plane.
We will see each other.
I envy your courage.
Zaizai,
I've always had a question for you.
Why are you so sure
that you like Zhang Lurang?
Shouldn't I know best who I like?
When he is happy,
I'm happier than he is.
When he is upset, I'm also upset.
With him around,
even math problems don't seem hard.
Once he is not around,
even a holiday feels too long.
Liking someone means caring about them.
Jiangjiang,
have you felt this before?
No.
Not even with Qianyu.
I only thought he was amazing.
No matter what troubles he encounters,
he can solve them well.
He is nothing like someone clumsy like me,
so I idolized him.
However,
sometimes, you might not know it
when you like someone.
I read on the Internet
that your subconscious
won't lie to you.
Jiangjiang,
when was the last time
you felt your heart racing?
You thought of someone, didn't you?
Who is it? Do I know him?
I didn't.
Don't you plan to confess?
Do you know what you will say?
Not yet.
Help me pick out an outfit first.
There's no rush in deciding your outfit.
I think we need to create a detailed plan
to make sure everything goes well.
My many years of watching idol dramas
are finally coming to use.
Jiangjiang, I think I'm a little nervous.
Don't be.
Remember the points I told you.
You will succeed.
He's here. I'm going.
First,
step one.
Change the way you speak.
Speak softly and coquettishly.
Act cute.
Most importantly,
call him "dear."
Many guys
like that.
Rangrang, over here.
Have you been waiting for a long time?
No, I also just arrived.
Dear Rangrang, let's go.
Su Zaizai.
Act normal.
My throat was not feeling well just now.
It's much better now.
Let's go.
SUMMER MARKET
Step two.
Create physical contact opportunities.
For example,
you can accidentally touch his arm
or fall into his embrace.
Then you will feel
your heart racing.
That was close, Rangrang.
I'm glad you are around.
Are you all right?
How?
Thankfully, I reacted quickly.
Look at how skinny you are.
You could have broken something.
Sorry.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Let's walk on the side.
Okay.
The most important third step.
Signaling.
Even a confession requires a lead-up.
You need to let him know what you think.
Confessing after that
greatly increases your success rate.
What's wrong?
Rangrang.
I've been very stressed recently.
My parents want me
to get married before I'm 30.
That means I have to get engaged at 29
and meet my partner's parents at 28.
I think dating for ten years is perfect.
It means I'll need to start dating at 18.
You'll be 19 in a few months.
Can you make it?
Well...
I think
I can accept dating for nine years.
Rangrang, are you an Aries?
The horoscope book I read yesterday said
that Aries and Sagittarius
are the most compatible.
Coincidentally, I am a Sagittarius.
My birthday
is based on the lunar calendar.
On the Gregorian calendar,
I'm a Pisces.
I don't think
horoscopes are that accurate.
If none of these work,
you will have to use the ultimate move.
A distant relative lost his job
a few days ago.
He'll be at the market today,
manning a tarot stall for a side gig.
I already filled him in.
Bring Zhang Lurang over.
You will definitely succeed
with his help.
The horoscope is not accurate,
but I know someone who is really good
at tarot card reading.
Since the fireworks won't start yet,
let's go there first.
Really good at it?
That's right. He is very reliable.
Coming to me was the right choice.
I'm famous in my village
for tarot card reading.
Just last month,
my neighbor, Erniu, had the flu.
I told him he would recover within a week.
Do you know what happened next?
He recovered
in less than a week.
Those who have seen my ability
will always say
that I'm very accurate.
What is your name?
My name is
Very Accurate.
Since we met here,
it means we are fated.
How about this?
I'll do a simple reading for you.
Here.
Pick a card from here
based on your feelings.
This one?
This is an amazing card.
Looking at this card, I can see
that you are a very lucky person.
You will also bring your luck
to the people around you,
especially those who are close.
Whoever becomes your boyfriend
will be very fortunate.
Buddy,
pick a card too.
This one.
This is amazing.
It's great.
Let me tell you.
From this card,
I can see
what your future girlfriend looks like.
She...
She has
bangs and big eyes
and wears pink.
Are you able to find out
what her name is?
Of course.
What is your name?
Su Zaizai.
Louder. I can't hear you.
Why are you looking at me?
Her name couldn't be Su Zaizai, could it?
Yes! Her name is Su Zaizai!
It's too obvious.
I think it's okay.
I've tried my best. It's up to fate.
Jiang Jia?
Why are you here too?
I'm meeting He Yu and the others here.
Gu Ran,
is this your friend?
She is my mom's colleague's daughter.
They were eating around here
and asked me to show her around.
We are childhood friends.
We only met last year.
Has it been so long already?
Miss,
since you are Gu Ran's friend,
do you know if he has anyone he likes?
He wouldn't tell me when I asked him.
-He...
-I do.
I have someone I like.
She is the person I like.
You can't simply say that.
I didn't.
She might not be the most outstanding
and likes to hop around
while singing out-of-tune.
She would become too sad to eat
because of a novel's bad ending.
When she is angry, even I can't stand her.
However,
when she smiles,
she is the only person I see.
I've made it clear to you.
Can I go now?
TAROT CARD READING
Are you going to reward me
for using me as a shield?
That was an emergency.
Fine.
What do you want? I'll give it to you.
I'm not that petty.
My friend just helped me.
Can you help patronize his business?
Your friend?
Who? Where did you meet him?
Do you know him?
It's a distant relative.
It's fine then.
Let me see.
This...
The two of you
have a deep fate.
Look.
This card is The Lovers.
It represents a choice in love.
That means one of you
is troubled by love.
Do you ever stop the nonsense?
You even lied to me.
I didn't.
Buddy,
be honest with me.
Did Jiang Jia bribe you?
You're taking advantage of me.
I'm getting the short end of the stick!
I can't see that.
That's because you are blind!
My admirers
will be lining up in university!
Can any of them compare to me?
He Yu and the others are here. I'm going.
Buddy, was what you said about fate true?
Do you want it to be true or not?
Never mind. Forget it.
I shouldn't have taken it seriously.
I wish you good business.
Thank you.
Why did that sound like a curse?
Really?
What if he confesses to you?
I don't think I will accept it.
What about you?
If a close friend confesses to you,
what would you do?
I won't date a close friend either.
I think it's not easy being friends.
What if something happens
after we start dating?
It'll be awkward
if we can't be friends anymore.
You are right.
Gu Ran.
What a coincidence.
You can buy us ice cream.
Let me say this first.
I'm only treating Fu Yao and the others.
You got lucky to be here.
You're so petty.
There are no clouds tonight.
I'm sure the fireworks will be pretty.
It should be a while
until the fireworks display.
Let's play a game.
Sure.
There's a game going viral online.
Let me give you a test.
The rule is simple.
Use three words to form a sentence.
All right.
First challenge.
"Su Zaizai,"
"Susu," and "cute."
"Su Zaizai
is jealous that Susu is cuter than her."
What?
It should obviously be,
"Su Zaizai is cuter than Susu."
You could also say,
"Su Zaizai is
just as cute as Susu."
Second challenge.
"Every day," "see," and "cake."
"If you eat cake every day,
you will see the doctor."
You are not wrong.
But the first sentence I think of is,
"Seeing you every day
is as sweet as eating cake."
Third challenge.
"Susu," "jelly," and "angry."
"Susu
ate my jelly,
so I'm angry."
You are so petty.
Wait, I keep making the challenges.
You should come up with one.
But let me warn you.
I'm really good at this game.
You can give me a difficult one.
"Zhang Lurang,"
"like,"
"Su Zaizai."
Do you think
I have always been confident
in everything I do?
Yes.
That's not entirely true.
For example,
when I confess this to you.
Confess what?
I like you.
I think we can check our scores tomorrow.
Are you nervous?
Nervous?
What is there to be nervous about?
It's just dating.
I'm talking about
checking our scores.
I don't think there should be a problem.
Don't you usually have a lot to say?
Why are you
so quiet today?
I usually don't speak much.
I remember there is a food street
behind East China University
that is quite famous.
It's worth checking out.
Let's go together.
I'm in a relationship with Rangrang!
I'm not dreaming, am I?
Calm down, Su Zaizai.
Isn't this normal?
Don't be so excited.
I'm sure Rangrang is incredibly calm.
Rangrang, are you asleep?
Lurang, pour me a glass too.
Lurang.
Lurang!
Why are you so happy?
Did something happy happen to you?
Water!
Rangrang, are you asleep?
I don't think
I can sleep.
What time is it?
There are ten seconds to go.
Seven, six,
five, four,
three, two, one.
-You can check it now. Hurry.
-Hurry.
SU ZAIZAI'S TOTAL SCORE, 586
I got 586!
Dad, I've never scored so high!
Mom, pinch me! Quickly!
No need for pinching.
My daughter is the best!
I must call your homeroom teacher.
He asked about your results this morning.
I'll buy groceries.
We'll celebrate tonight.
Rangrang, I can go
to East China University!
Did Rangrang get a bad score?
I'm downstairs.
Rangrang!
Did you check your results too?
I thought about it.
Which university we go to
isn't that important.
The distance is not a problem.
I can...
I think the boys' dorm and girls' dorm
aren't that far apart.
Rangrang!
Your four years at university
are all mine.
Zhang Lurang,
what do you think about that?
I'm honored.
Before school starts, I'll write down
all the things I want to do with you
and complete them one by one.
What is the first thing?
Watch the sunrise.
We don't have to wait for school to start.
Let's go together.
Watch the sunrise.
No.
A date between two people.
This is the perfect time.
We might even be able to rent a good tent.
Let's go.
Well...
What's wrong?
Hurry!
Help me put together the lamp.
How can you camp without this?
Gu...
Gu Ran?
When did you develop a stutter?
He happened to come to my house
and saw me packing.
I knew you wanted to give us a surprise,
but advance notice is better
when it comes to camping,
so we can prepare properly.
Did you say "us"?
Zaizai!
When Gu Ran told me,
I knew he would spoil your plan.
It's okay. I'm here. I'll get rid of him.
What a relief.
Let's go then.
Hold on. We're waiting on someone.
If I hadn't come,
all of you would have suffered.
Don't move.
-What are you looking at?
-Be still.
Tell me.
How can anyone be so blind?
Here you go.
Gu Ran.
I need help here. Come and help me.
As expected,
with great power
comes great responsibility.
I'm going there.
Call me if you need me.
I'm not in a bad mood.
I just want to make you happy.
Are we going to look at the stars tonight?
Sure.
I didn't expect the stars here
to be so pretty.
Why didn't I ever realize
the stars were so big?
Gu Ran.
Jiang Jia? Are you here to stargaze too?
You look like a star yourself.
I just realized my lamp is broken.
I'm sure you can fix it
since you are so great.
You have a good taste.
Lead the way,
Xiaojiazi.
It's my first time
finding Gu Ran so annoying.
I'm surprised. You can actually fix it.
There is plenty that you don't know.
Well?
Don't you find me handsome now?
How narcissistic.
Give me that.
Your hair is messy.
When I'm not around in the future,
who will help you when you're so clumsy?
You won't be going too far anyway.
I'm going abroad.
Even if you are going abroad...
Is this another joke?
This is not funny.
No.
I discussed it with my parents
for a long time.
This foreign exchange opportunity
is very important.
I want to check it out.
Then
that's great.
have you told Zhang Lurang and the others?
Not yet.
Maybe in a few days.
I'm sure they will be shocked
when they find out.
Slow down.
What's up?
I'm so happy.
It feels a bit unreal.
You can't escape if I hold your hand.
This is more reassuring.
Don't.
Aren't you cold?
This development is too fast.
It's like a dream.
Su Zaizai.
I know you want me to act normal again.
Come inside.
My Rangrang is so smart.
I don't feel cold like this.
Is the toilet over here?
After I go abroad,
I don't know when we will meet again.
-I...
-Gu Ran!
Were you talking in secret?
What is it? Let me hear it too.
It's nothing.
Gu Ran was helping me fix the lamp.
What's up?
What did I want to tell you?
That's right!
Let me tell you.
Something is wrong with this place.
I just saw two people hugging outside.
When I looked more closely,
it looked like a person with two heads.
That's so scary.
Something is wrong indeed.
Something is wrong with you here.
Do you not believe me?
I saw it clearly.
That person
was wearing a black jacket.
It was like this one.
The other head
was a female
with very long hair,
about as long as hers.
I made a mistake.
I saw nothing.
I didn't see anything.
I made a mistake.
Well, it's late. Go back to sleep.
We need to watch the sunrise tomorrow.
-Yes, let's go.
-Let's go.
Then
I'm going back too.
Okay.
What's wrong with them?
They suffered a shock.
Don't you have anything to say?
When did it happen?
You even hid it
from me.
Did I?
You...
Not really.
You can date,
but you must promise me one thing.
You must never tell my grandma this.
I can foresee
how hard it will be for me to date.
If my grandma
finds out you have a girlfriend now,
she will be disappointed with me
and torture me more.
I'm serious about this.
Why are you playing on your phone?
I'm telling her good night.
I can't continue this conversation
for a second more.
I'm going abroad.
Is this another joke?
This is not funny.
No.
I discussed it with my parents
for a long time.
This foreign exchange opportunity
is very important.
I want to check it out.
It's my first time waking up so early
just to watch the sunrise.
I suddenly realized
that we've seen many sunsets before.
Now we've watched the sunrise today.
Are we ending what we started?
Touch wood.
We still have a long way to go.
This is not the end.
You are right.
It's not over yet.
The exam results are out.
Have you decided on your schools?
Both of us applied
for East China University.
So you've been planning it.
What about you?
Me?
Do you remember Yong'an?
We visited before.
I'll be there for four years.
Way to go.
Yong'an University is famous
for its economics program.
Of course. Who do you think I am?
Seriously!
The sun is coming out.
This is great.
We all have our own goals
and directions to work hard toward.
I hope the next time
we watch the sunrise together,
we will have become better people.
We will.
The next time we meet,
we'll say, "It has been a long time!"
Go farther
and see a brighter light!
The sunrise is so beautiful!
TO JIANG JIA
You didn't expect me
to write you a letter, did you?
I'm surprised too.
It's obvious
how difficult it is for someone
who is bad at literature to write this,
so don't laugh at me.
Let me guess.
When you are reading this,
you should be preparing
your dorm living necessities.
As for me,
I should be at the airport already.
I didn't tell any of you
because I was afraid that when I saw you...
I was afraid that when I saw you guys,
I would be reluctant to leave.
But you're different.
You are so smart.
When they get mad,
you can help me calm them down.
I picked up a quote from a movie
a few days ago.
"All encounters in life
are reunions after a long time apart.
To put it simply,
when I first met you guys,
I knew we would get along well.
My intuition has been proven
to be spot-on.
I remember when we got punished together
during military training,
the trash that we searched together,
the sunrises, sunsets, fireworks, and snow
that we watched together,
and three years of wishing each other
a Happy New Year.
I'm happy that all of you
were part of my youth,
but there is a saying.
"Life is like a train journey.
Someone will get off at the station."
Guan Fang chose economics.
You're determined to study journalism.
Su Zaizai and Lurang are finally together.
It's so great.
I believe everyone will one day
meet somewhere higher in the future.
I'm not worried about everyone else.
I just think
that you may look fearless,
but you are quite timid sometimes.
I'm sure you're very nervous
now that you're alone.
Do you still remember what I said?
Just go.
It's pretty dark up ahead.
If you are afraid, you can call my name.
My name will give you power.
I hope my best friends
will be safe and happy,
eat well, drink well,
always get a good night's sleep,
have plenty of choices,
and meet friendly people.
Even if we are miles apart,
we will still shine brightly
when we don't see each other.
TO JIANG JIA
Writing so much is not easy for me.
That's all.
If I write more,
I might not bring myself to leave.
Finally, let me confirm this again.
No matter where I am,
we will always be
each other's most important person, right?
Are you taking it back?
No, it just needs an update.
After all,
I'm no longer your teacher, Ms. Su Zaizai.
Congratulations to Rangrang
on having a girlfriend.
I hope you'll cherish her
and keep up the good work.
Su Zaizai is pretty, generous,
positive, and cute.
She is the one and only
for Zhang Lurang.
Rangrang, you are blushing.
I'm not.
You clearly are.
No, I'm not.
See for yourself.
You are blushing.
Blushing.
Look at you.
You are blushing.
You're blushing.
I really envy Rangrang
for having such a great girlfriend.
Of course, it's all thanks to me.