Three, two, one!
-Cheese!
ADAPTED FROM ZHU YI'S NOVEL,
SHE'S A LITTLE CRAZY, ON JJWXC.NET
-Kiss!
A Mutual Idol.
Is Zhang Lurang going to transfer?
Why so suddenly?
I heard this from my mom.
Perhaps it's due to his enrollment status.
I don't think Lurang wants to leave.
He hasn't been like himself recently.
He hasn't told us about it either.
Does Su Zaizai know about it?
She must.
She seemed upset recently.
I thought she had a fight with someone.
I'm sure
it's because of Zhang Lurang's transfer.
You are right.
I'm sure Zhang Lurang told her first.
Zaizai must be sad right now.
I need to figure out how to comfort her.
Comfort her?
Won't she add fuel to the fire instead?
That's hard to say.
Have you been upset recently
because of Zhang Lurang?
Have you noticed?
It's too obvious.
You two haven't
gone home together in days.
But I can relate.
I've experienced it before after all.
Was it because of Qianyu?
It is hard to accept at first,
but you need to go with the flow.
Just accept the truth.
But I just can't accept it.
I don't think it's that bad.
Even if he is transferring schools,
you can still call him.
Suyang isn't far.
You can go see him during the holidays.
Transfer schools?
Aren't you upset
because of Zhang Lurang's transfer?
Is he going to transfer?
Didn't you know about it?
When is he leaving?
I don't know.
Do you want me to ask Gu Ran?
All of you knew.
Only I didn't know.
Zaizai.
Go home first.
I'm going to ask him.
What's the matter?
Are you going to transfer schools?
Actually,
I wanted to turn around and run
a few times on my way here.
I was afraid of hearing your answer.
But if I don't ask you now,
I'm not sure
if I'll still have the courage
to ask you again tomorrow.
I thought...
I thought you only found me annoying
and that we are at least still friends.
I would just stop pestering you.
But everyone knew about your transfer
except me.
What you did
makes me think I'm not important at all.
I'm sorry.
It's getting late. I'm leaving.
Su Zaizai.
I SAW A BOY OUTSIDE THE STORE.
HE LOOKS SO HANDSOME!
Zaizai, are you not sitting here?
I don't want to be a nuisance.
Where is Su Zaizai?
Zaizai is on duty. She went to get water.
By herself?
She has me.
Gu Ran, are you willing to stay back
and complete this honorable mission
with us?
No.
Lurang, what about you?
Sure.
I knew you would say yes.
Lurang.
I'm touched.
I'll go and get water.
DRAMA CLUB
I can do it myself.
Su Zaizai.
Don't you think
Su Zaizai has been acting weird recently?
When she told us she was leaving first,
she said bye to all of us
except you.
What did you do
to make her hate you so much?
Zaizai?
Who is that person?
I don't know.
You two are so close.
What a useless friend you are.
Zhang Lurang is clearly closer to her.
ALL VISITORS MUST REGISTER TO ENTER
That's not necessarily true now.
The guy is quite handsome.
How ignorant can you be?
How is he handsome?
It's not the weekend,
but he's not wearing a school uniform.
He's obviously a shady guy.
I heard girls in our class say
that boys from other schools
have been waiting outside
to seek out girls.
They even whistle like hooligans.
Is he one of them?
This isn't good. I must ask her tonight.
I heard girls in our class say
that boys from other schools
have been waiting outside
to seek out girls.
They even whistle like hooligans.
Is he one of them?
Lurang.
Lurang!
Uncle, I'm going to the store.
Bring your wallet.
My wallet.
Why is he so absent-minded?
This is not bad. Why aren't you eating?
Eat more if you like it.
Right.
When you transferred,
did you tell your friends
from your previous school?
Of course. We are friends after all.
Was there anyone you didn't tell?
There was one.
A girl from the neighboring class
used to bother me all the time,
so I didn't tell her about the transfer.
If I had told her,
she would've asked me so many questions.
It would be annoying if she showed up
during the holidays.
Sometimes,
when someone is too enthusiastic,
it is actually a burden for others.
You should eat air instead.
What are you doing?
Is this how you treat your brother?
Mind your words.
You are my cousin.
It belongs to the one who paid.
-No, it's mine.
-Give it to me.
Let go.
I don't care. It's mine.
-It's mine.
-You cannot eat anymore.
-Stop eating.
-I'm going to eat.
There are also these.
This one is also good. Try it.
Did you eat it?
I'll choke you.
Su Zaizai.
What are you doing?
What am I doing? Buddy.
She's the one beating me up.
I'll walk you home.
No.
Su Zaizai.
You can say that I'm annoying.
I don't mean to be around you anyway.
Let's go.
Say something.
Who was that person?
Just an ordinary classmate.
An ordinary classmate?
Did you forget the look on his face
when he thought I was bullying you?
There is no way he's just a classmate.
He has a sense of justice.
Aren't all guys like that?
You don't know guys at all.
At the convenience store just now,
why did you...
Forget it. I'm not thinking about it.
SU ZAIZAI
ARE YOU NOT AT THE BUS STOP YET?
I'LL WAIT FOR YOU
I NEED TO SEE YOU,
I'M OUTSIDE YOUR HOUSE
Where is Su Zaizai?
Zaizai's cousin is here.
She is showing him around the school
during the lunch break.
I can buy a bottle of milk for her.
Cousin?
Why did her cousin come to our school?
I think he's transferring here
next semester.
He is the guy we saw yesterday
at the school entrance.
I thought he was someone else.
What are you laughing at?
It's nothing.
What do you want to eat?
JIANGYI UNIVERSITY
Su Zaizai.
I'm sorry.
What for?
I made you angry.
I just think
that if you really do find me annoying,
I can...
I've never found you annoying.
Then why did you tell everyone
about your school transfer
except me?
I never told them about it.
I wanted...
I wanted to tell you first.
But I thought about it for a long time
and didn't know how to tell you.
Why?
Because you are
a special friend to me.
When are you going back to Suyang?
Next semester.
There are a few months left.
Are you
still angry?
Yes.
I'm a little angry.
Actually, it's not just a little.
I've been so angry
that I couldn't eat lunch for a few days.
Make your choice.
Pick between comforting me or losing me.
If you don't pick,
I'll really get angry.
How do I comfort you?
Just act cute.
It's easy.
Let me teach you.
I'm Zaizai.
Try it.
I'm...
Rangrang.
Are you mad?
No.
Give me a smile.
I can't.
I don't feel like it.
Then you are angry.
Why would I be angry?
I don't want to be angry.
Smile.
I don't want to.
GRADE 11, CLASS 1
There will be
a prefectural academic competition
held in our school next Tuesday.
It will be on this floor,
so in the next few days,
you need to take all of your things home.
Clean off all the doodles and stickers
on your tables.
Empty the classroom by Tuesday.
Got it?
-Yes.
So now,
we're making space
for those good kids to fight.
But you look happy today.
Do you not plan to tell us
about your transfer?
Don't all of you already know about it?
I'll be the only one left in this class
starting next semester.
I'm bored just thinking about it.
Yes, Luli wanted to come here on his own,
but his exam is important,
so his dad and I came together
because we were worried.
It's not my first time traveling alone.
You have the cheek to be saying that.
Who almost got lost
at the bus station last time?
Exactly.
You are only good at studying.
Lurang.
You're back, Lurang.
Dad. Mom.
Lurang.
Luli has an exam next week at our school.
For the next few days,
he and other students
will come to our school
to sit in on Grade 12 lessons.
He will be staying here.
Sure.
Will there be a problem
if you two share a room?
Why would there be a problem?
Luli loved sleeping with Lurang
when he was young.
Right?
You are right.
I'll get a bigger blanket
for you two later.
Lurang, take this opportunity
to ask Luli if you have any questions.
When he was in Grade 11,
he was already studying a semester ahead.
Lurang,
do you have a lot of homework today?
It's manageable.
Lurang,
are you not happy
that I'm here?
Don't imagine things.
Class dismissed.
-Goodbye, sir!
Jiang Jia, aren't you going?
I'm not.
You fooled me into going last period
and there was no one there.
I would rather take a nap.
-We'll go without you. Let's go.
-See you.
What are you talking about?
Who are you going to see?
We have students from other schools coming
to sit in on lessons today.
I heard there is a genius
who is in Grade 12 at the age of 16.
He skipped two grades.
Most importantly, he is quite handsome.
That's rarer than an endangered species.
All of them are going to see him.
There is no need to go.
There are posts of him on the forum.
Here it is. High-definition photos.
Let me see.
Why does he look familiar?
He looks
like Zhang Lurang.
A little.
The class ended a few minutes ago.
What is taking them so long?
The mart will have no more food left.
Ms. Zhang was teaching this period.
No wonder.
Zaizai, look. It's that genius.
Why is he here?
Who is he waiting for?
Hurry up. I'm starving.
Lurang.
Lurang?
Luli.
Lurang,
Mom is waiting for us at the entrance,
so I came to find you.
She is here for you.
I still have evening self-study.
Leave without me.
I didn't know you came.
Let's play basketball tomorrow.
Gu Ran.
I have to go.
Let's go.
Rangrang, are you also an only child?
I have a younger brother.
Younger brother?
Do you two look alike?
Probably, yes.
Do you have similar personalities?
No.
He is nice.
You are nice too.
I mean, you're nicer.
Which one of you is better looking?
My brother.
No.
You are the most handsome.
You're probably
the only one that says so.
Zhang Lurang.
I heard the genius in Grade 12's auditors
is your little brother.
Is that true?
If you had the same curiosity in studying,
Ms. Zhang would wake up every morning
in laughter.
My grades are average.
I really envy Zhang Lurang.
He doesn't have
to tutor his little brother.
He can be the one being tutored instead.
These people have too much free time.
Gossip spreads like wildfire.
Their names are so similar.
It turns out they really are siblings.
How do you get the news so quickly?
It's all over the forum.
Everyone already knows about it.
I'm really envious of his family's genes.
How can both their children
be so excellent?
Why is the little brother
already in Grade 12
and has gotten so many awards,
while Zhang Lurang is only in Grade 11?
His little brother outshines him.
What do you mean by "only"?
All of us are only in Grade 11 too.
Everyone is different.
You can't keep comparing them.
They are brothers.
It's normal to compare them.
I'm just saying.
You're so petty.
Yes, I am petty.
Are you not eating at the canteen either?
It's too crowded.
All the noise hurts my ears.
We're about to head to your place.
You have good taste.
RESULTS BOARD
GRADE 11 STUDENT RANKINGS
What is it?
Rangrang,
you scored 110 in English
in the last monthly exam!
Which teacher is so good at teaching you?
Aren't you ashamed of praising yourself?
Why should I
be ashamed?
Guan Fang,
what is that on your lips?
Lip balm.
Jiang Jia gave it to me.
How do you know I used lip balm?
Isn't it transparent?
Sorry, I didn't know this lip balm
could change color.
Jiang Jia.
If you have guts, don't run!
I don't have guts!
Today,
I'm going to kill you.
You...
Lurang,
it's the weekend tomorrow.
Why don't we go to the amusement park?
Isn't Jiangyi Amusement Park said
to be a lot of fun?
I have homework to do.
What about the day after tomorrow?
Where do you want to go? We can...
We'll see.
Okay.
I won't disturb you anymore.
Lurang.
Are you done with your homework?
Yes.
Do you want to play games?
I made sure to bring it from Suyang.
I'm stuck at this level.
I'm sure you can pass it immediately.
Play on your own.
I'll play for only half an hour.
Lurang, you're cheating!
I'll go easy on you in the next round.
You said so.
Be quiet. The kids are studying.
Lurang.
How could you make your brother play games
at a time like this?
It wasn't Lurang...
I don't even know what to say.
Luli never plays games back at home.
You're already a bad influence on him.
Games erode your ambition.
Lurang,
can you put yourself in our shoes?
If you could be
as diligent as your brother...
Mom!
Can you please stop it?
Did I say anything wrong?
What is with that attitude?
Stop it!
I asked Lurang to play with me.
But you didn't even ask.
I'm serious.
Can you stop doing this?
I'm coming.
-Mom, is Luli in your room?
-What is it?
No.
Isn't he in your room?
No. I called him and he didn't pick up.
Luli.
Lin Mao, is Luli in your room?
No.
What's wrong?
Our son is missing.
Luli?
What's going on?
-Luli?
-What's going on?
Luli?
Why didn't you know when he left
when you two were in the same room?
Enough. It's no use talking about this.
Let's go out and find him.
Luli is not familiar with Jiangyi.
He can't be far.
-Yes, let's go find him.
-Let's go.
Do you want
the Superb-brand mosquito coil?
All right, I know.
I'll head home after I buy it.
Aren't all these brands
pretty much the same?
Have you seen
a 16-year-old student around here?
Rangrang?
Why do you look so worried?
Did something happen?
My brother went missing.
He is
probably quite emotional.
It's a boy
who is wearing a gray short-sleeve shirt.
I don't think I've seen him.
Okay, thank you.
I have to go.
Rangrang.
You're not as familiar
with Jiangyi as I am.
Why don't I help you find him?
-Sure.
-Let's go.
Luli!
Sorry.
-Luli!
-The subscriber you dialed
-He is not picking up his phone.
-isn't picking up.
Please try again later.
Is he still not picking up?
Let's look over there.
Zhang Luli!
Luli!
CHENYANG NEIGHBORHOOD
-Did you find him?
-No. What about you?
No.
We even went to the school
and didn't see him.
He's not at the bus station either.
We could report it to the police.
The police have more resources.
Yes, let's go to the police.
Let's go right now. Come on.
Lurang,
go home to rest.
We don't need so many people to go.
How can he rest at a time like this?
Zhang Lurang, I don't mean to nag.
You were with your brother,
but you didn't even know when he left.
That's enough.
Would he have done this
if you hadn't scolded him?
-What did I say?
-You...
What did I say?
Why are you talking about this?
The most important thing is to find Luli.
I'll look for him in other places.
I'll go to the police.
Search for him. Quick!
Let's go.
You don't know me,
but I know you.
Zhang Luli, right?
My name is Su Zaizai.
I'm your brother's friend.
Are you the one
who gave him that talking toy?
Toy?
That one?
Did he tell you about that?
I saw it myself.
He never tells me about these things.
When I knew I would be coming here,
I was very happy
because this place must be great
if my brother likes it.
I have always idolized him.
I couldn't tie my shoelaces
when I was a kid.
Lurang always tied them for me.
I didn't remember the way back home.
Lurang!
He waited for me
outside the school every day.
Sometimes, he bought lollipops for me
with his pocket money.
He is
only a year older than me,
but I already thought
he was amazing.
He is so much more amazing than me.
Perhaps the bias
started with an extra fried egg,
choosing one parent-teacher meeting
over another,
or a pointless comparison.
But once it started,
everything that followed
seemed to be a given.
Even I
became an accomplice.
Luli.
Lurang.
Do you know how to solve this problem?
Yes.
-Then...
-This question is really easy.
Lurang, don't you know how to do it?
I was so happy that time.
My all-mighty brother asked me a question.
I thought I could help him.
However,
I was ignorant back then.
I was
very ignorant.
It was only later that I noticed.
Those people kept saying...
Lurang, your scores
are much lower than Luli's scores.
Did you even study?
Lurang,
I'm tired of lecturing you.
You can ask Luli
if you don't know something.
They never considered Lurang's feelings.
They never considered mine either.
Lurang doesn't speak or smile much.
I always thought
that was just his personality.
That was until I met all of you.
Then I knew it wasn't
that he didn't like to smile.
In a family like this,
he could no longer be happy.
In truth,
everyone is praising me,
but what I want the most
is my brother's praise.
I'm grateful to all of you
for being my brother's friends.
Let me tell you a secret.
I had
to pester Zhang Lurang
for him to become my friend.
Really?
Yes.
He is the kindest person I've ever met.
Rangrang.
Lurang.
I'm sorry.
Let's go home.
Rangrang,
I think your brother and I
get along pretty well.
How so?
That's because we have a mutual idol.
He envies me
because I can go to school with you,
take the bus with you,
and have mutual friends.
And I envy him
for having a good brother like you
who waited to pick him up from school
and tied his shoelaces.
Did Luli tell you that?
Yes.
My impression of him
was always the genius
that everyone said he was,
but I neglected the fact
that he is only 16 years old.
He said the person he admires the most
is his brother.
Rangrang, I think he has great taste.
EXAM ADMISSION TICKET, ZHANG LULI
Keep looking for it.
If you left it at home,
call your parents and have them bring it.
It'll likely take them
half an hour though.
Sir, can you let me in
to take the exam first?
I want to let you in,
but this is the rule.
I can't help it.
There is an exam at the school ahead,
so traffic has been restricted.
I think it'll take some time to get there.
Sir, keep the change.
Keep looking for it.
Your admission ticket.
EXAM ADMISSION TICKET
What are you waiting for? Hurry inside!
Do your best in the exam.
I will.
Go in quickly.
Hurry!
Susu, do you still remember me?
Where is Lili?
Lili?
Yes.
Isn't Lili your brother?
I'm extending my love to him.
He already went back.
What?
I wanted to have a fan meetup with him.
An old fan like him
and a new fan like me.
I wanted to learn more about you.
I won't get a chance now.
There will be a chance.
What?
You two will meet again.
It's a promise then.
Susu.
Let's go.
Today, I suddenly realized
that having an idol who spoils his fans
is such a happy thing.
TODAY, I FINALLY REALIZED
THAT HAVING AN IDOL WHO SPOILS HIS FANS
IS SUCH A HAPPY THING.