Three, two, one!
-Cheese!
ADAPTED FROM ZHU YI'S NOVEL,
SHE'S A LITTLE CRAZY, ON JJWXC.NET
-Kiss!
Happy New Year, Rangrang.
Dad.
You're putting up decorations
so early this year.
Your grandma made the decorations early
and sent them over,
so I thought I would put all of them up.
Help me see if it is okay here.
Move it a bit to the left.
To the left?
Like this?
Yes.
Okay, good. I'm pasting it now.
I'll go out
to buy Lunar New Year items later.
Tell me what else we need.
Mom, I need a pair of shoes.
Didn't you buy
a pair of snow boots last year?
You haven't worn them much.
Mom, I need a new look for the new year.
It's for good luck.
Okay then.
Go and pick one for yourself,
so you won't complain about my taste.
Thank you, Mom.
Dear, my belt...
Your belt is still in a good state.
The color has come off.
So I'm thinking of getting a new one
for the new year.
It's for good luck.
Okay, I'll get one for you
at the mall later.
Sure.
I'm full of energy now. Let's continue.
Rangrang,
we've begun putting up decorations today.
What are you doing?
I'm doing homework.
Rangrang, I made dumplings today.
For the first time, none broke.
I'm guessing you're good
at making dumplings too.
Is this really a dumpling?
No.
I can't help much.
My parents prefer that I study.
My parents have never thought about that.
They just ordered me
to clean all the glass in the house.
I'm about to develop a phobia of glass.
Rangrang, what are you doing?
I'm reading at the library.
Rangrang,
you should do something fun
during the break.
What things are considered fun?
Everything that makes you happy is fun.
Today, I took Susu out
and watched the sunset.
It was beautiful.
I'm envious.
Envious?
I envy Susu.
Lurang.
Yes?
Lurang, you're on break.
Why don't you go out?
Uncle and his family just left.
I have a lot of homework to do.
Is Jiangyi a fun place?
I have a friend from Jiangyi.
I really want to visit
every time he describes it to me.
Lurang, you're staying at Uncle's house.
If you have time next semester,
shall I stay with you for a few days?
Mom and Dad said
you don't have many friends there yet.
I don't have time.
Is your school schedule that packed?
I've already made plans with friends
for my free time.
-You're home.
-Yes.
I smelled the food as I was coming in.
It smells so good.
Dad, you came back at the perfect time.
Certainly.
Honey,
didn't you go to buy cured meat?
Why are you back empty-handed?
Where is the meat?
I was just about to tell you.
My mom called me
to say that my grandma
is celebrating her birthday this year
and invited us home for the holiday.
So I'm asking for your opinion.
If we're going, we don't need the meat.
So I didn't buy it.
Great-grandma?
Don't you remember her?
She carried you in her arms
when you were little.
Your great-grandma back in our hometown.
But all our preparation will go to waste
if we're not celebrating in Jiangyi.
And if we go,
Uncle and his family will surely go too.
Where will all of us sleep then?
I return to work
on the fifth day after Lunar New Year.
Won't we be spending most of our time
on the road?
Yes, it will be troublesome.
You're right.
Suyang is quite a distance away
from Jiangyi.
Suyang?
Don't hesitate then!
We must go!
Great-grandma used to carry me.
It's her birthday.
How can we not go
when so many others are going?
Reunion is the most important thing
during Lunar New Year.
-You were just...
-I was considering it just now.
Now I've made up my mind.
I don't mind
squeezing in somewhere to sleep.
Attending is the most important.
Look,
our child has suddenly become so sensible.
That's settled then.
We're spending Lunar New Year in Suyang
and coming back the next day, okay?
Okay.
I'm done eating.
I'll pack for the trip to Suyang.
Are you packing right now?
This girl.
Why is she suddenly so excited about it?
The cohesion of the family, I guess.
Rangrang!
Today, I finished
all the Chinese assignments.
Let me test you.
What test?
A word game.
I'll go first.
Beyond your wildest dreams.
A dream come true.
I know what you're implying.
It's my turn.
Time passes slowly.
Slow on the uptake.
Rangrang, are you insulting me?
Do you want to continue?
You can't take advantage of the game
to do that.
I'll forgive you this time.
But I'm starting fresh.
Put into practice.
Practice makes perfect.
Kung Fu Panda.
Tom and Jerry.
Rangrang, don't just give random answers.
That's not the rule.
Well, forget it.
Rangrang, you have a bad temper.
Only I can put up with you.
I'll forgive you
as long as you buy me bubble tea
when I am in Suyang.
Are you coming to Suyang?
Yes.
We're visiting our relatives,
so we'll celebrate Lunar New Year there.
Zhang Lurang, are you very surprised
as well as
a little bit happy?
Don't be shy.
Just say so or I wouldn't know.
Suyang is a boring place.
How can it be boring if you're there?
Good night.
I'm looking forward to Lunar New Year.
I'll get in the car first.
Put it here.
Dad, how long will the drive take?
Four hours if there is no traffic jam.
We'll arrive in the afternoon.
Rangrang, I'm setting off.
I heard
that Luli ranked first
in the final exam this semester again.
He participated in a competition
before the final exams,
so he didn't have much time to revise
and ended up ranking third in the city.
His ranking dropped slightly.
Are you still not satisfied?
Luli excels in his studies
and is obedient.
We would be over the moon
if we were in your shoes.
He's disciplined.
We don't worry much about him.
Luli, tutor your cousin
when you have time.
He even struggles
with the holiday homework.
Okay.
You've always been a good boy.
Where is Lurang?
How did he do in the exams?
Lurang...
Aunt, Uncle.
Hello.
Lurang is still as quiet as before.
It's not good for him.
He should learn from Luli.
Be more cheerful.
That's just how he is.
But he's obedient and sensible.
Isn't he studying in Jiangyi
this semester?
What was his ranking in the final exam?
I heard
that only the top five in his school
have a chance
to enter East China University.
Lurang,
take Luli and your cousins
to the library this afternoon.
Pick out some books for them.
Have Luli take them.
I have plans in the afternoon.
I'm going back to my room.
Lurang hasn't been close to us
since he was little.
It might be hard for him
to get along with his classmates.
He has friends.
He's doing quite well at school.
Mom,
I'll go back to my room and study.
Go ahead.
Enjoy the food.
I've arrived in Suyang.
Now I'm going to take a nap.
I'll see you tonight.
Mom, please let me be.
Your aunt will be back very late tonight.
Your dad and I have to clean up the place.
Just take Xuanxuan to the supermarket
to buy some seeds, nuts, and snacks.
It's not that hard.
But I've changed into my pajamas.
I want to take a nap.
If you nap now,
you won't sleep tonight.
I can go by myself. I know the way.
Come on. Go with him. Hurry up.
Aren't you going to get changed?
It's fine.
No one knows me here anyway.
But...
It's not appropriate, is it?
Why don't you wait for me on the side?
Don't worry. I can handle this myself...
Everyone, are you ready?
The countdown for the big sale starts now.
Ten,
nine,
eight,
seven,
six,
five,
four,
three, two, one.
Begin!
30-SECOND FLASH SALE!
HALF OFF EVERYTHING!
This is nice.
-I grabbed this first.
-What?
-I got it first.
-I grabbed it first.
Let go!
-I got it first.
-It's mine.
-You're being unreasonable, young lady.
-I got it first.
-I took it first.
-I grabbed it first.
-I did.
-I got it first.
-Let go.
Su Zaizai?
-I...
-Will you drop it?
This is not bad.
-I got it this time!
-Who wants this?
Rangrang, please don't get the wrong idea.
I'm not usually dressed like this at home.
I happened to not dress up today
and ran into you.
No, you've always looked like this.
You remembered it wrong.
My cousin has a bad memory.
I planned to study
after taking a nap
and then meet up with you tonight.
I didn't expect to bump into you here.
You haven't started your holiday homework,
let alone study.
Except for math,
I've almost finished everything else.
I'm not as good as you at math,
so I'm slow.
Are you good at math?
I like math too.
But no one in our family is good at it.
Su Zaizai always
barely passes her math exams.
Little brat.
Don't embarrass me.
She never knows the answer
when I ask her math questions.
But she's really good at English.
I always failed my English exams.
And she has been helping me.
Everyone has their own strengths
and weaknesses.
That's normal.
Zaizai, are you that good at English?
Of course.
I just don't brag about it.
Rangrang, my aunt's place is up ahead.
Do you want to come over?
Right now?
Please come.
I need your help with my homework.
Are you in a hurry to go home?
No. Let's go.
Rangrang, look.
We've encountered
the most secretive intelligence community
in the world.
What do you mean?
The literal meaning.
Let's go.
What?
A boy?
And they're on their way here?
Okay, got it.
Thank you so much.
What boy were you talking about?
Zaizai's uncle's
third aunt's sister's neighbor
said she saw Zaizai with a boy
talking and laughing on their way here.
They seemed quite close.
Uncle's third aunt...
Who is that?
That's not the point.
Zaizai is still young.
She's bringing a boy home all of a sudden.
Did she just meet this boy?
How is his character?
How is his family?
Does he have any bad habits?
We're clueless about him.
It's dangerous.
He also got Zaizai to bring him home
right after they met.
This guy can't be good.
That's exactly what I meant.
Unacceptable.
I must teach him a lesson.
I...
We shall see if he can take a beating.
Okay.
Only my parents
should be at home right now.
Don't worry. They are very friendly.
Stop right there.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Su.
I'm Su Zaizai's classmate.
My name is Zhang Lurang.
Zhang Lurang?
He has been tutoring me
in math and physics.
He's very smart.
Is he the classmate you mentioned?
Why didn't you inform us
that your friend was coming over?
I...
Does the lantern look a bit tilted?
Xiaozhang.
Come on in!
Why are you standing outside?
-Come in and take a seat.
-Quickly. Make yourself at home.
Please take a seat.
Make yourself at home.
Take a seat.
Make yourself comfortable.
Xiaozhang,
are you in the same class as Zaizai?
No.
I can tell he's a good boy.
Zaizai is very weak
in science.
I'm grateful to you for tutoring her.
It's nothing.
She helps me too.
Well, they help each other.
Exactly.
Where is Zaizai?
What were you talking about?
I just changed into some casual clothes.
This is the least casual outfit
I have seen you in.
Rangrang, can you come to my room
and help me with my homework?
"Rangrang"?
Yes.
I heard Zaizai calling him Rangrang...
Don't you need to do your homework?
Go ahead. Go now.
Xiaozhang,
since you're here,
please stay for dinner.
You can try Zaizai's dad's cooking.
I won't stay for dinner.
It's getting late.
Yes, stay and have dinner with us.
I'm cooking.
You can try it.
Zaizai,
be my helper.
Okay.
You should stay.
Sit here and entertain your friend.
I'll help him.
Xiaozhang, is there anything
you don't eat?
He can't eat shrimp.
Okay, all right.
How did you know?
Whenever we ate at Mrs. Guan's place,
you never ate the shrimp balls.
So I asked Gu Ran.
Do you suddenly realize
that I'm caring and attentive
aside from being cheerful?
Is that so funny?
Where is Zaizai?
I asked her to see Xiaozhang out.
Someone said
this must be a bad boy
who harbors evil intentions.
Then you kept calling him Xiaozhang.
You changed your attitude quickly enough.
You must take the actual situation
into consideration.
Look at Xiaozhang's appearance,
demeanor, and attitude.
Would he be a bad boy?
Besides,
he's tutoring Zaizai in math.
He's such a kind kid.
Let me tell you.
I wanted a boyfriend like him
when I was Zaizai's age.
And you're so lucky.
You found one.
Rangrang, did my parents
make you uncomfortable during dinner?
That's just how my family is.
They can never stay quiet for a minute.
That's good.
Good?
My family
usually doesn't talk to each other.
We focus on our own things.
Even having meals
feels like completing a daily task.
We gather at a place at fixed times.
So you don't talk to each other.
Isn't that boring?
Yes, it's quite boring.
Rangrang, you get the privilege with me.
You're now my first contact.
You get priority to chat with me.
Call me any time
you want to talk to someone.
Rangrang,
does meeting me in Suyang
count as an interesting event
during your boring holiday?
Yes.
And I bagged it myself.
Right?
Or maybe they couldn't see me.
I was also too rash.
There was a new cat.
I also chipped in.
-Nice!
-And I had an idea.
Mom, your favorite sketch
is about to end.
How is the patient doing now?
Okay.
Okay, I'll be right there.
A patient has had an adverse reaction.
I need to head to the hospital.
Honey, do the dishes.
Be careful on the road.
Okay.
But it's Lunar New Year's Eve today.
The Emergency Department is always busy.
Your mom has no choice.
I meant
that she hasn't tried the dumplings
that I made this afternoon.
She's missing out.
You can save some for her.
Hello.
It's okay. I'm free to talk.
You should pay attention to your sickness.
Don't go out often.
The weather is cold now
and can damage your lungs.
Yes.
One more thing.
Be careful with your diet too.
Avoid overly sweet, spicy,
or salty foods.
Welcome the Lunar New Year
with joyfulness.
May you have a happy Lunar New Year
and a delightful Lunar New Year's Eve.
Your happiness brings me joy.
Your happiness sweetens my days.
Wishing you a Happy Lunar New Year
in the Year of the Dragon.
Hello, Gu Ran.
That's so insincere.
You just forwarded
Lunar New Year's greetings
without revising the zodiac year.
Sorry.
I'm lighting fireworks with others.
What are you doing?
Did you light fireworks?
Fireworks aren't allowed in the city.
You know that.
Then you can listen to them.
Listen. Did you hear it?
Yes.
Why don't you watch
the Lunar New Year's Gala inside?
What are you looking at out here?
Grandma,
I always feel
that every Lunar New Year is the same.
Everyone eats, sets off fireworks,
and watches the Gala.
They don't even change the sequence.
But why do people
still look forward to the Lunar New Year?
That's because today is a day
that everyone chooses to spend
with people who are worth it.
Don't you think
wishing "Happy Lunar New Year"
to the same person every year
is a fortunate thing?
So I'm really fortunate.
Happy Lunar New Year, Grandma.
Happy Lunar New Year.
Hello, Rangrang.
It's time for the countdown.
Five,
four,
three,
two,
one.
Happy Lunar New Year, Rangrang.
Happy Lunar New Year, Su Zaizai.
I wish we could do a video call.
Then you could see it.
Jiang Jia.
Happy Lunar New Year.
-Take this.
-Great-grandma.
-I can't take the red packet.
-Zaizai.
Just take it.
Your great-grandma is so fond of you.
You really don't have to.
These eggs don't cost much.
Just take them.
Otherwise, she won't be able
to sleep tonight.
All right. We'll take them.
-Take it.
-Zaizai, take it.
Thank you, Great-grandma.
It's getting late. We're heading back.
-Sure.
-We'll visit when we have time.
Okay.
See you.
Bye, Aunt. Bye, Great-grandma.
Drive safely.
What's the point
of celebrating Lunar New Year?
It's to bond with people.
Your room is smelly.
What kind of smell?
You haven't moved at all
during the holiday.
So what do you think?
It's a sour smell.
Get up.
Bring the things with you.
We'll pay a Lunar New Year's visit
to Dr. Gu.
He took good care of your grandma
when she was in the hospital.
We should be grateful.
Get up now.
Just say that you want me
to carry things for you.
-Let's go.
-Good. There you go.
You're more sensible after Lunar New Year.
A New Year's visit?
Are you visiting your relatives?
No, it's my grandma's doctor.
My dad said we must express our gratitude.
I can't talk. I'm almost there
and this fruit basket weighs a ton.
Your dad sure knows you well.
What do you mean?
It would be a waste of your brawn
if you didn't carry the fruit basket.
You should be glad
that you're not here right now.
Otherwise, you wouldn't be laughing.
Jiang Jia, come.
Come here. I found it.
I was also too rash.
Ranran, see who it is.
I also chipped in.
Nice!
And I had an idea.
I'll create a club.
What?
Why don't you crawl
out of the screen and hit me?
-Look at this one.
-Okay.
Hello.
I'm looking for Dr. Gu.
No way.
You did crawl out of the screen.
Gu Ran?
Do you know each other?
Rangrang, what are you looking at?
You're completely absorbed.
I just feel
that fireworks are beautiful.
Haven't you played with fireworks
during Lunar New Year before?
No.
So will you think of me
whenever you see fireworks?
This Lunar New Year, my wish
is that fireworks factories don't sell out
before I turn 100.