Three, two, one!
-Cheese!
ADAPTED FROM ZHU YI'S NOVEL,
SHE'S A LITTLE CRAZY, ON JJWXC.NET
-Kiss!
You Are More Charming Than the Scenery.
Sir.
Crybaby.
You're the crybaby.
My name is Doudou.
He strayed away from his teacher.
Let's take him to the broadcast station.
Let's go.
I'll take you to your teacher.
No, I want him to hold my hand.
You're not the only one. I...
I also think
you should let him hold your hand.
Otherwise, we might both get lost.
Let's go.
Welcome to Jiangyi Aquarium.
Please keep your valuable items with you
and keep them safe.
Valuable items,
you must follow me carefully.
Sir.
She looks like she wants to eat you.
What are you saying?
That's how she looked
when she looked at the fish just now.
No.
Didn't he say I acted like that
because I thought it was adorable
and liked it very much?
Come, I'll show you the big turtles.
Do you see that? It's a huge turtle.
Thank you so much.
As soon as I turned around, he was gone.
-Luckily, he met you.
-You're welcome.
We were heading this way anyway.
By the way,
I'll give you
these aquarium souvenir keychains
as a thank you.
Are they exactly the same?
There are also different ones.
No, it's okay.
I want the same ones.
Thank you.
If there's nothing else, we'll get going.
Say goodbye to them.
Bye.
-Bye.
Rangrang,
when you were holding Doudou's hand,
I thought I saw us ten years from now.
Well...
Forget it.
Kids say whatever they want.
Here. We each get one.
Now you've been to Jiangyi Aquarium.
This is proof.
Let's go.
Other than the school uniform,
this is the second item we have in common.
It's incredibly meaningful.
I must make sure
that it can be seen at all times.
THE FIRST HIGH SCHOOL
What doomsday?
It's the 21st.
It's after the academic competition.
People on the forum made it sound so real.
They said it was a Mayan prophecy.
Do you really believe in doomsday?
I didn't believe it at first.
But many people say it's true.
And don't you think
the weather has been a bit weird lately?
They all say this is a sign of doomsday.
Yes, that's right.
The moon was especially huge last night.
The prophecy also says
that the sun won't rise again
after doomsday.
That's so mystical.
Will anyone really believe that?
Don't online forum posters try to come up
with the most convincing stories?
Signs of impending doomsday?
Only fools would believe that.
Why are you looking at me?
I don't believe it.
Says the one who was speaking
so confidently just now.
Me?
I was trying to educate all of you.
I want you to keep up
with this current hot topic.
Got it?
You guys are the noisiest on this floor.
Is this what an honors class is like?
Before we start our lesson,
I want to emphasize
the academic competition.
Half of our class
will participate in this competition.
Though it's not very difficult,
it still tests what we have learned
during this period.
I hope you don't take it too lightly.
Keep your admission tickets safe.
If anything happens while you are there,
contact the teacher in charge immediately.
Do you understand?
-Yes.
The exam is only two days away.
You have no sense of urgency at all.
Every class year gets worse.
Focus on the exercises.
Rangrang,
have you heard about doomsday?
Do you actually believe it?
Everyone is talking about it.
Rangrang,
if it really is true,
what would you find most regrettable?
Not coming to Jiangyi earlier.
Same here.
It would have been great
to have known you earlier.
But it's not too late now.
We still have plenty of time ahead.
So you don't believe in doomsday anymore.
Even if it's true,
I still got to know you.
Come, Zaizai.
Bring some fruit.
I've washed them. Eat them on the way.
Mom, my bag is already full.
If you take out this junk food,
then it will fit.
You're going to a competition,
not an outing.
Let her eat whatever she likes.
She doesn't eat it every day. Right?
You're the one who has spoiled her.
Here, Jiajia.
-Have some fruit.
-Thank you, Mrs. Zhang.
You're welcome.
What time is your train tomorrow?
I'll give you a ride.
It's okay. It's at ten o'clock.
We can get there ourselves in time.
All right then.
Okay. Then let's go.
Sleep early, okay?
-Don't stay up too late.
-Sleep early.
Be at your best.
I know.
Good luck.
Jiangjiang, do you think this counts
as my first trip with Rangrang?
Over 100 others are going with us.
Do they not count as people?
Why aren't you excited at all?
What is exciting about going to an exam?
You're excited
because Zhang Lurang is also going.
Qianyu is not going.
Speaking of which, when do you plan
to give him the jar of stars?
I don't know.
It doesn't feel like the right time yet.
What if he doesn't accept it?
It's simple. Give it to him again.
I wish I had your courage.
If only I were bold.
It's all Rangrang's fault.
He's great.
He has good grades, good looks,
and a great personality.
You're praising him too much.
We always think people we like
are perfect in every way.
So tell me.
Do you think Qianyu has any flaws?
He...
He's too perfect.
Do you see?
You judge me
when you're also completely obsessed.
You're obsessed too.
No, I'm not.
-You are.
-You're the obsessed one!
Why are those two still not here?
Can you not reach them?
Sorry, the subscriber you dialed...
She's not answering.
What time is it?
Zaizai!
What?
-Are we taking the ten o'clock train?
-Yes.
Look at the time now.
What are you waiting for?
Let's hurry to the train station!
Are you planning
to run after the train on foot?
You have a point.
Let's take the bus.
I'll text Gu Ran.
Rangrang, don't worry.
We'll be arriving a little later
than you guys.
Are you taking the bus?
Yes.
Do you know how long it will take?
How long will it take by bus?
Seven hours.
It'll be dark when we arrive.
Just sleep.
We'll be there when we wake up.
I missed my first train trip
with Rangrang.
I will never forget to set the alarm.
Are you going out?
Where are you going?
The bus station.
The bus station?
Has Jiang Jia arrived?
I'll go with you.
Well, if I don't go when you're going,
Jiang Jia will bad-mouth me again.
Come on. Let's go.
Yong'an is colder than Jiangyi.
I'm sure
careless Jiang Jia didn't realize.
Come on.
Rangrang?
Why are you here?
Did you come just to pick me up?
It has been a long time.
You just saw me yesterday.
You're so welcome.
Hold this for me.
Exactly what I need.
I just bought this.
They're still hot. Have a quick bite.
There are other places
to eat near the hotel.
Thank you.
Let's head back.
Why aren't our rooms assigned together?
That's too bad.
I thought I could chat with you tonight.
That's because you arrived late.
Room 413.
Room 412.
Room 411. I'm here.
I'll go inside first. Bye.
-Okay.
-Bye.
Sleep early. Bye.
Bye.
So where is your room?
Room 401. It's up ahead.
It's quite near my room. I'm in Room 407.
The exam is at 9 a.m. tomorrow.
-So you...
-Don't worry about me.
I won't be late.
I mean to say,
don't silence your phone.
I can call you.
Okay.
I'll go inside then.
Bye.
-Bye.
Who's there?
Hello, I'm Su Zaizai.
I'll be sharing the room with you.
Hello, I'm Xia Ning.
Have you had dinner?
I have snacks. Do you want some?
Thank you, but I've already eaten.
Which school are you from?
Suyang No. 1 High School. What about you?
The First High School
Affiliated to Jiangyi University.
Affiliated to Jiangyi University?
Is there a guy named Zhang Lurang
in your school?
He should be quite popular.
Zhang Lurang?
I know him.
Is he also participating
in this competition?
Time sure flies.
It has been almost two years
since we last met.
I wonder if he still remembers me.
Do you two
know each other?
Yes. We went to the same junior high.
My dad was even his physics teacher.
Is he interested in anyone
at your school?
I don't think he has one.
But there are people
who are interested in him.
That's for sure. He's so outstanding.
He probably registered
for physics this time too.
Maybe we'll be
in the same examination hall.
Lurang,
aren't you going to bed?
Sleep first. You can turn off the lights.
I can use the table lamp.
You're making me so stressed.
Even though the exam is tomorrow,
we should take it easy
before the competition.
How about a game?
No.
I'm afraid I might dream of you
doing exercise problems.
Rangrang, are you asleep?
Not yet.
I knew it.
I know you too well.
My roommate is from Suyang.
Her name is Xia Ning.
She said she knows you.
Okay.
What does that mean?
Does he know her?
Are they close or not?
Do you still remember her?
I think so.
He thinks so.
That means they're not close.
We participated in many competitions.
Her results were pretty good.
She's really good at physics.
He remembers her results clearly.
By the way, Zaizai,
what subject are you taking in the exam?
I haven't asked you.
English.
I'm bad at science subjects.
Being good at English
is very impressive too.
Many of those who are good at science
are bad at English.
Zhang Lurang is one of them.
I wonder if he has improved.
Someone is tutoring him,
so he has improved a lot.
His tutor is especially skilled.
She's hardworking and patient.
His grades have improved a lot now.
That's great to hear.
By the way,
there must be many top students
in Suyang, right?
There must've been quite a lot
in junior high, right?
Yes, we do have some,
but not many are well-known.
Was Zhang Lurang famous?
Of course.
Almost every female student
in school knew of him.
Then such a popular guy
must have liked someone, right?
Yes.
Who?
Susu.
Susu?
Susu, I see.
What?
Do you know he has a pet named Susu?
I've seen it once or twice.
I wonder if Rangrang
ran into Xia Ning
during the final physics exam.
Rangrang!
I thought you finished
half an hour earlier than me.
Are you here waiting for me?
I just got out.
That also counts.
Where are Jiangjiang and the others?
Have they left?
It's bad enough that she didn't see us.
She even suspected that we had left.
That's too much.
Well, you may not know
that I've been developing nearsightedness.
Come on. Drinks are on me.
That's more like it.
THE NINTH
HUAYI CUP ACADEMIC COMPETITION
We're leaving in two days.
Let's go and have fun tomorrow.
Sure.
Since we're already here,
it'll be a loss if we don't have fun.
Lurang!
Mr. Xia.
I didn't believe it
when Xiaoning said you were here.
It turns out that she knows you best.
Hello, everyone.
I'm an old friend of Lurang's.
I've been sharing a room with Zaizai
these two days.
"Lurang"?
Are you all done with the exam?
Why aren't you going out
for some fun then?
We were planning to.
Perfect.
Let Xia Ning show you guys around.
She has been to Yong'an many times.
She's familiar with this place.
She can be your tour guide.
Since you haven't
seen each other in a while,
you can catch up.
Now we can consider ourselves acquainted.
Let's hang out together.
She has known him for a long time,
much longer than I have.
They might just be ordinary friends.
We rarely get to travel
and this is a snack street.
Cheer up.
Don't let anything spoil the food.
Jiang Jia, Su Zaizai, do you want to eat?
Come on. Let's go.
It's quite nice, isn't it?
The scenery gets even better up ahead.
So do you come here often?
You can say so. I grew up here.
So I can be your tour guide.
Up ahead
is Yong'an's famous Mount Xiaolan.
Since it's Monday,
it shouldn't be crowded.
Do you want to go up and explore?
Sure.
I heard the entire Yong'an
is visible from the top.
Yes.
That's why visitors always go up.
-Let's go.
-We're already here.
We have to take a look.
You guys go ahead.
My shoes are chafing my heels.
It will be bad
if I can't make it back down.
I'll wait for you here.
I'll stay and keep you company.
It's okay.
You should take photos
to show your parents.
I'll stay here. I won't wander off.
Okay then.
I know a shortcut.
We'll come back as soon as possible.
If you're bored,
you can buy some snacks down there.
Okay.
Lurang, let's go.
I did say I'm not going.
But are you really leaving me here?
Why didn't you go with them?
I'm tired. I don't want to go.
So you went to buy jelly for me.
Didn't you say
eating jelly makes you feel better
when you're in a bad mood?
It'll be an hour or two
before they come down.
Why don't we go and enjoy the view?
Enjoy the view? Where?
If Jiang Jia knew
there was a direct cable car,
she would be so annoyed.
However,
this is really high up.
Are you scared?
What is there to be scared of
when I'm with you?
Rangrang, you seem to enjoy
being in high places.
I noticed it when we were
at the amusement park.
Whenever I was upset in the past,
I liked to go to high places.
It made me feel much better.
Rangrang,
do you have a lot of worries?
Or...
Why don't you try to be like me?
I forget my worries quickly.
What would you do?
I'll eat my favorite snacks.
For example, strawberry jelly,
takoyaki with cheese,
and the first bite of ice cream.
If none of those work,
I would go to the beach
or watch the sunset.
All of these always improve my mood.
And if...
If none of those work,
then just seeing you will be enough.
Rangrang,
every person's existence is meaningful.
Don't easily dismiss yourself.
For some people,
you're their ultimate solution,
a magical remedy
that can cure everything.
They like this world more
because of you.
Every day, I want to strive harder
and put in a little more effort
to become a person like that.
But you already are.
Let me carry it.
So you guys ended up taking the cable car.
That's outrageous.
We went up and down the mountain on foot.
My legs are still sore.
Yet you're occupying my bed
when you rode the cable car.
Move over.
Now!
This is comfortable.
I found the view from the cable car
to be quite beautiful.
Everything looks beautiful to you
so long as you're with Zhang Lurang.
We went hiking earlier today.
I think Xia Ning is pretty nice.
She's pretty, kind, and isn't spoiled.
She helped me several times
when I couldn't hike anymore.
Really?
She even bought us some local specialties.
I think she must be popular at school.
Is he doing okay now?
Yes, one time we went out together
for an exchange.
We...
Su Zaizai.
I left something in Jiang Jia's room.
I was just about to retrieve it.
You guys can carry on.
I came for you.
I texted you, but you didn't reply.
The battery ran out.
Well, I happen to need to go out
to buy something.
It's too cold to chat out here.
Talk inside.
Go inside.
What's the matter?
I'll just stand here.
The heating system isn't working properly.
I thought
you might need this.
Thank you.
Then I'll go back now.
Don't stay up too late.
Rangrang.
Good night.
He's so cute.
Your keychain looks really nice.
Today, I saw that Lurang had the same one.
Are you two...
No.
This is an aquarium souvenir.
They're all the same.
Does Lurang like you?
No.
How could he possibly like me?
He's probably annoyed at me every day.
Why are you nervous?
Then you must like Lurang.
I...
How long have you known him?
Do you know him well?
Do you know what he thinks?
Have I scared you?
I've watched too many television dramas.
So I feel that is what I should say
at a moment like this.
Sorry about that.
But I do think
you don't know him that well.
Let me tell you.
For a guy like him,
it actually takes him a lot of effort
to take every step toward you.
And he usually
won't express his thoughts directly.
Instead,
it's through an action,
a glance,
or even an ordinary sentence
that no one would pay attention to.
He's a guy who excels in academics
and is so popular.
Just so you know,
many people wanted to be friends with him
when we were in junior high.
But he just liked being alone.
In any case,
you'll gradually understand him.
There are many things
you have to experience on your own.
But how do you know all of this?
I'm going to study psychology.
So I already knew it
when I first saw you.
What did you know?
You must be
Lurang's most trusted friend.
Sorry for troubling you
these past few days.
It's nothing.
I heard Jiangyi is a nice place.
If I have time,
I would like to visit.
Also, I would like to see what it is
that makes Lurang like it so much.
Then you'll have to stay longer.
You can't experience all of Jiangyi
in one day.
Okay, I'll definitely visit.
It's almost time.
We should head to the train station.
If he walks too slowly,
you can take the initiative
and walk into his world.
Bye.
See you.
Go on. Bye.
-Bye.
Zaizai, why are you still up?
I'm not sleepy. You can sleep first.
Can you live without sleep now?
I can't seem to fall asleep.
I might as well
sleep on the train tomorrow.
It's my first trip to Yong'an.
I wonder what it will be like.
I should make a plan.
We do have some time after the exam.
Shall I go on a boat ride with Rangrang?
Maybe hike a mountain?
I need to make a proper plan.
Had I known
that staying up late would make me
miss the train the next day,
I would've slept early for a change.