Three, two, one!
-Cheese!
ADAPTED FROM ZHU YI'S NOVEL,
SHE'S A LITTLE CRAZY, ON JJWXC.NET
-Kiss!
So Rangrang Likes Sunflowers.
WHISPERS OF THE MOON
ARE FOUND IN THE STRINGS
-Hello.
-Zhang Lurang said he was on the way.
-Thank you for coming.
Please go on inside.
But their seats are quite far from ours.
Jiang Jia said she was almost here.
Why isn't she...
Who are you?
Give me back Jiang Jia.
Why are you dressed so formally?
Are we dressed too casually?
It will do.
It's almost time.
Let's go inside.
Okay.
You guys go ahead.
I'm going to say hello.
Hurry up.
Gu Ran.
-Hi.
-Hello, Mr. Shen.
-Gu Ran, there you are.
-Qianyu.
JIANGYI CITY MUSIC CONCERT
Gu Ran.
When will it be Qianyu's turn?
What?
Do you know when Qianyu will perform?
I'm curious.
How did you fall for Qianyu?
At first,
I was attracted to the way he looked
as he concentrated on playing the guitar.
Later, after getting to know him,
I found out he has good grades
and an amiable character.
Do you remember that time you played ball
instead of seeing me home?
I noticed for the first time
how long the road home was.
Thankfully, he appeared.
I'll give you a ride home.
I never knew
anyone could be so gentle.
That day we saw the sunset together.
I never saw another sunset
as beautiful again.
Perhaps
only when I'm with Qianyu
will I get butterflies in my stomach.
JIANGYI CITY MUSIC CONCERT
Wait here for me for a bit.
What is he going to buy?
Jiang Jia!
JIANGYI CITY MUSIC CONCERT
Where did they go?
Qianyu.
Thank you. How about a picture together?
Okay, thanks.
Go on.
Do I look good?
Yes.
Jiang Jia.
Qianyu.
Congratulations
on a successful performance.
Thank you.
After you go abroad,
I don't know when we'll meet again.
I'm not good with words.
So...
I wrote something for you.
Thank you.
I have a younger sister.
She also likes to write me letters
about things that interest her.
You remind me of her.
I don't know
when we will meet again.
I hope you do well in your studies,
grow up quickly,
and meet your Mr. Right.
I hope you'll continue to shine.
Besides a bright future,
I would like to wish you
a happy life.
Thank you.
I just remembered.
I haven't fixed the typos
in the letter.
I'll give it to you next time.
Okay.
Sure enough,
if it's not meant to be yours,
you can't force it.
Change into these.
Gu Ran?
Why is it just you? Where are the others?
They're in there talking to Qianyu.
Was it worth it?
You even got blisters
from wearing ill-fitting shoes.
It's the price of beauty.
You know nothing.
Do you know
how many stars there are in the sky?
Stars?
100 million?
At least 200 billion.
But among the billions of stars,
no two are the same.
It's the same when they look at us.
They're probably also wondering.
Out of so many humans,
why are there no two alike?
You're the same.
The Jiang Jia I know is carefree.
She is unabashed
and always stands up for herself
rather than swallowing a grievance.
She's rough around the edges
and inconsiderate.
But
no matter what happens,
she's always cheerful and positive
like an idiot.
Must you list out my flaws like that?
What I mean is
you are you.
Although you're nowhere near perfect,
you're still one of a kind.
You don't have to wear ill-fitting shoes
and pretend to be someone you're not.
You're unique and shining bright.
So one failed confession
is not that big of a deal.
You don't have to be so dejected.
I'm not dejected.
Qianyu said I am like his younger sister.
To think of it,
being his sister isn't that bad.
Things could change in the future.
I have a strong heart.
Don't underestimate me.
Is that so?
Then why did you cry
when you failed the monthly math test?
I guess your heart isn't strong enough
to endure academic failures.
Do you have to bring that up?
Why are you so jolly anyway?
I...
I plan on having snacks later.
I can't wait.
If I remember correctly,
don't you have a class later?
JIANGYI AIRPORT
We just have to get back by 1:30 p.m.
But we would've been distracted in class
if we didn't come.
Where is Jiang Jia?
JIANGYI AIRPORT WELCOMES YOU
The 1,000th star represents good luck.
Thank you.
When will you come back, Qianyu?
At the end of the year.
I'll be back when it snows in Jiangyi.
Hopefully, you will be more mature
when I'm back, little brats.
I'm only one year younger than you.
And I've always been mature for my age.
Remember? I always
let you play with my toys.
You only let me have
the ones you didn't like.
You never concede what you really like.
It's almost time.
You guys should go.
I have to go through security.
-Let's play ball when you get back.
-Sure.
All the best to you.
I'll get going.
Bye.
Is it because I can't bear to see him go?
Why do I feel so anxious?
Isn't it because the final exam results
will be released later?
Isn't our class starting in 20 minutes?
Don't just stand there. Run!
-Let me see.
-Over there.
-Where am I?
You scored well.
I really did.
-I'm so envious.
-Look.
ZHANG LURANG
-Where is it?
You improved a lot.
Rangrang, you got 95 in English!
This test was incredibly hard
and the passing rate was only 20%.
This is what I just heard.
Despite the unbelievably difficult level,
someone actually scored 137 in English.
I think improving with each test
is amazing enough.
Don't compare yourself
to those crazy geniuses.
Honestly, you're talking about yourself.
SU ZAIZAI
We all did pretty well on this exam.
Shall we go to Baichuan
for the summer break?
Baichuan?
Lurang,
it's not that I prohibit you
from having fun with your friends.
But you're entering Grade 11 soon.
And your grades...
Let's just talk about your final exam.
You only got 95 in English.
Do you know
the difference that one point makes
in the college entrance exam?
Before coming to Jiangyi,
you said you would study hard
and be more focused here.
Looking back,
you should've stayed in Suyang.
Look, the exam was difficult this time.
Lurang's results are considered good.
But regardless of the difficulty,
Luli's English scores
have never been lower than 130.
Don't lower your own standards
just because the test was hard.
Ever since coming to Jiangyi...
Ever since coming to Jiangyi,
I haven't done worse than before.
Also,
I'm allergic to shrimp.
I know that.
I was just distracted
while talking about your grades.
Eat something else. Try another dish.
Okay, now. Just eat.
The food is getting cold.
Actually, I think it's fine for kids
to go out and see the world.
Also, they just finished exams.
They must be hoping to go to Baichuan
to check out the university.
It could motivate them to do better.
As his uncle,
you shouldn't indulge him so much.
We'll listen to your uncle.
The train is leaving in an hour.
Why isn't Rangrang coming out yet?
Do you think he is grounded?
Or his parents secretly took him back
to Suyang last night.
We can always change our tickets
to Suyang.
The destination isn't important anyway.
What matters is that we are together.
There's no need, Zaizai. He's coming.
I was held up looking for my ID card.
Sorry about that.
An excuse. Definitely an excuse.
Be honest. Were you secretly dressing up?
The train we're taking
passes not only lakes but also grassland.
It will be beautiful. I brought my camera.
Let's talk on the train. We'll be late.
Without further ado, let's go.
Go!
Wait for us!
Over here.
Let me.
Thank you.
My last card.
Pair of eights.
Pair of twos!
Ready, three,
two,
one.
SUMMER TASTES OF ORANGES
AND SALT LIKE THE SEA BREEZE
-Hurry.
-I'm coming.
Three, two, one!
-Cheese!
It's so nice to go out with friends.
That's handsome.
It doesn't matter if we're just strolling.
-It's still fun.
-What do you think? Handsome?
Right there. Look there.
Jiang Jia!
Your big head is blocking the view.
You should be grateful
that at least half
of the picture looks nice.
The half without you.
Forget it.
I'll take a picture of you.
Is this okay?
Can your smile be faker?
Your pose is...
You're so clumsy even when taking photos.
You're annoying.
Zaizai, let's go. I'll buy you ice cream.
None for him though.
It looks nice.
What's the matter?
My wallet is missing!
Is it the pink one?
That's the one.
This is bad.
Gu Ran's and my money was in it.
I just had it
when I was buying the candied hawthorn.
Where is it?
What should I do?
It's okay. Keep looking.
Did you leave it somewhere by mistake?
I don't remember.
Was it stolen?
It's okay if it was just my money.
But all our money was in it.
Don't panic.
We haven't gone far. I'll look for it.
Let's ask the stall owners along the way.
Maybe we'll find it.
Let's go.
Look at how pretty the moon is tonight.
It's like this.
We all
have limited memory,
so we should remember the good things.
Look at you.
Your long face looks ugly.
You look better when you smile.
It's my fault
for losing all of your money.
No, it's not.
I didn't want the hassle
and left it with you.
You did a great job already.
We didn't have a worry
for the past few days.
The money would've been long gone
if it were with me.
Yes, it's not your fault.
Come on. It's okay.
I have some money left.
We can share it.
Yes, I have some too.
But we planned to go
to the amusement park tomorrow.
Your money won't cover it.
RECRUITING
We can earn the money that we lost.
It's not like we have a set itinerary.
It can be nice to try new experiences.
I agree.
I'll do it.
I should make up for my carelessness.
Yes, count me in.
With my good looks
and physique,
I should put them to good use.
So let me see.
SECURITY TEAM CAPTAIN, 2 PEOPLE
The security team captain role suits me.
BAICHUAN MUSIC FESTIVAL
Not bad. It suits you.
How about this?
You two can work outside.
How many tickets can be sold today
will depend on you guys.
That's right.
Right, here.
Take these for me.
Get more from me
once you've passed them all out.
Okay?
Careful. Don't break it.
Hang on.
How could he not make good use
of my super good-looking face?
He wants me to cover everything up.
What the heck?
Stop complaining.
Guan Fang is assembling things.
Even Zaizai and Zhang Lurang
are doing manual labor.
Our job is comparatively easy.
Even in that costume, you look handsome.
"Even"?
So you're saying I was already handsome.
Be more specific.
Which part of me is handsome?
My eyes? My nose?
Jiang Jia, so that's what you think of me.
You're so annoying.
Put it down here.
Here.
Thank you.
Thank you, Rangrang.
I think we forgot to get the number signs.
Miss, can you go back to where we were?
They should be in the equipment room,
beside the light sticks.
It's just one bag and not very heavy.
I have to move these things quickly.
Okay.
Why don't I go?
If you go,
she will have to move your things.
They are too heavy for her.
It's okay.
I can go. It won't take long.
Are you two...
No.
We're just friends.
I haven't even said anything.
Eleven...
This should be it.
The third room after turning right
at the entrance.
I came in from the right.
So now,
I go this way.
Sorry, the number you have dialed
cannot be reached at the moment.
Please try again later. Sorry.
Why is this locked too?
It's okay.
I'll just go the other way.
This place is only so big.
I'm sure I'll find a way out.
Su Zaizai.
Rangrang, I'm so scared.
Come out if you dare!
Stop sneaking around and scaring people.
I'm not scared of you!
Are you not scared now?
That's because you're here.
-Hello.
-Hello. Can you hear me?
That's my phone.
Did you find it?
Where are you?
The hallway outside the equipment room.
I had a feeling I dropped it there.
Thank you so much, buddy.
Leave it there. I'll come get it.
How's this? I'll buy you dinner tonight.
You don't have to.
Just change your ringtone.
Let's go.
How is she so energetic?
I can't take it anymore.
It's like a sauna inside the headpiece.
Also, I have to jump and dance.
I almost couldn't breathe.
Who asked you to jump and dance?
We only have to pass out all the fliers.
Nobody would take it if I didn't dance.
Watch me.
The fliers.
You are so good at being lazy.
You have no sense of professionalism.
But I must say it's quite effective.
Of course.
This was my idea.
BAICHUAN MUSIC FESTIVAL
This is all your earnings.
Wait a minute.
I calculated that it should be 355 yuan.
I subtracted 30 yuan
because there was a complaint
about your work.
But we passed out all the fliers.
That's right. We did our job just fine.
We finished the job with half the effort.
-So I don't accept it.
-Me neither.
Someone said you two blocked the path.
I see.
Thank you.
We finally have money.
Where should we go tomorrow?
It feels so weird.
When we had no money,
we thought of earning money.
When we have money,
we can't think of what to do with it.
It was quite interesting though.
I heard them talk a lot
about the music festival.
I've never even been to one.
What is it?
Do you guys want
to buy tickets?
But you don't have enough money.
The five of you only earned enough
for four tickets.
Sir, can't you make an exception?
We worked so hard today
just to see the music festival.
We've never been to one.
That's right.
If we miss this one,
I don't know
when we might get another chance.
Many years later,
I will remember this day
when a kind man gave us a helping hand
when we were in need.
From now on,
you'll be my best buddy.
We can chip in 20 yuan if necessary.
Fine.
Fine, all right.
I know you're in a tough spot.
Here is what I can do.
I have some extra tickets.
You can have them.
Here.
Keep the change.
You should at least have something
to show for your long day of work.
-Thank you, sir.
Let's go.
-Happiness is easy to attain
-Money that I earned myself
-only at their age.
-just feels different!
I'm coming back in two days.
We'll talk after you get home.
We planned for English tutoring lessons
for two months.
Now it will probably only be a month.
Luli has already gone over
all the Grade 12 material at home.
Lurang,
I hope you can have some sense of urgency.
Okay.
I'll pick you up at the station then.
No need. I'll be with my friends.
BAICHUAN HOTEL
I've always thought
that these popsicles taste better
when shared.
Unfortunately, I don't have any siblings.
I used to eat the whole thing myself.
Rangrang, are you also an only child?
I have a younger brother.
Younger brother?
Do you two look alike?
Probably, yes.
Do you have similar personalities?
No.
He is nice.
You are nice too.
I mean, you're nicer.
Which one of you is better looking?
My brother.
No.
You are the most handsome.
You're probably the only one that says so.
Rangrang, look.
These five coins
are just enough for us to each have one.
I've never made money
with my own hands before.
I had planned
to bring this special coin home
and keep it safe.
But now,
I'm giving it to you.
You said I'm the only one
who thinks you are better
than your brother.
Not only do I think that you're better,
but I will also always think that way.
If he's worth 100 marks,
then you are worth 101.
That special extra point
will always be saved for you.
The popsicle is yummy.
I'll buy you one next time.
Okay.
Pair of tens!
Pair of...
Q.
Pair of Ks!
I'm done.
I win again! Come here.
-Show me your forehead.
-This is the fifth time.
My forehead is swollen.
Come.
Is that it?
You're so biased toward her.
My hand slipped, so it doesn't count.
No way!
I'm so lucky.
Are Zaizai and Lurang back?
No, it's Qianyu.
He says he has nearly adjusted
to living in England.
Qianyu?
What else did he say?
I've found the person
who is very important to me.
Let's continue playing.
Wait, I haven't finished reading it yet.
Well...
I finished my cola. How about you guys?
Should I go buy some more?
Cola?
There are some in my room. I'll go get it.
Jiangjiang?
Jiangjiang.
What did you say?
What's on your mind?
You're totally in a daze.
Did Qianyu get a girlfriend?
So are you feeling okay?
I'm okay.
I just didn't expect it to happen so soon.
I guess fate often comes unannounced.
Let me tell you. That girl is so pretty.
Qianyu was smiling so happily beside her.
I guess
you did think of him as just a brother.
I guess so.
Something got into my eye.
Are you all right?
Don't rub it so hard.
Hold on a second, Grandma.
The signal isn't good here.
Let me try up on the rooftop.
Are you okay?
I'm better now.
Weren't you going to call your grandma?
That was quick.
I went to the rooftop just now.
But I saw Jiang Jia crying there.
So I came back.
I guess Qianyu having a girlfriend
is a big shock to her.
Is she very upset?
She kept rubbing her eyes.
Hopefully, she'll be in a better mood
when we go to the music festival tomorrow.
-Hurry up and take a photo so I can see.
-Sorry to keep you waiting.
-This...
-They're so hot!
BAICHUAN MUSIC FESTIVAL
Zaizai, look.
It's so pretty.
I think they draw those over there.
Come on. Let's go take a look.
Hello. Would you like a face painting?
It's quite popular.
Yes.
What would you like me to draw?
Draw me a white cloud.
It's just like me, a free spirit.
I want a star.
Me too.
Why are you copying me?
There's more than one star in the sky.
No one is copying you.
Please draw me a sun.
My nickname is Little Sun.
Sun and summer are the best match.
What about you, Lurang?
A sunflower.
Rangrang, do you like sunflowers?
I never knew.
Come on.
This...
All right, you guys.
BAICHUAN MUSIC FESTIVAL
Here they come.
Welcome to the Baichuan Music Festival.
Are you guys ready
to have fun with the band today?
BAICHUAN MUSIC FESTIVAL
I wish my grandma were here.
She loves festivities.
You can tell her all about it.
I told you the battery wasn't dead yet.
Good thing I brought extra
or we wouldn't get to record this.
You're always prepared, Zaizai.
We're at a music festival right now.
Isn't it so lively?
It's my first time at one.
There are so many people.
Zaizai, the quality of your DV is awesome.
It's giving me an oval face.
I look so good.
Good-looking people? Here I am.
Can you not pop up out of nowhere?
Do you need another handsome guy?
Don't waste storage space.
I don't mind.
But I must film the most handsome one.
I'll buy one when I get back.
Let's make a joint purchase.
It turns out
that the sunflower and the little sun
shine for each other.
It turns out
that the sunflower and the little sun
shine for each other.