Three, two, one!
-Cheese!
ADAPTED FROM ZHU YI'S NOVEL,
SHE'S A LITTLE CRAZY, ON JJWXC.NET
-Kiss!
I Like It When You Frown
and Call Me Coward.
So did you get back so quickly
because you took a shortcut?
How did you know about the shortcut?
Luckily, I was smart
and checked gossip posts
about military training in advance.
Did you check? How?
Look. I preserved this last precious item.
You are really something, Su Zaizai.
Is everyone here?
-Hurry.
-Assemble.
All of you, conduct a check
for any prohibited items.
This is your last chance.
If I find something...
Ma'am, I have something to hand in.
I feel that it's wrong to hide snacks.
So I've decided to hand in my chocolate.
Hey, buddy.
How about a bag of chips
for an hour on your PSP?
You can get an hour
with barbecue-flavored chips.
But tomato-flavored?
Half an hour tops.
Take it out.
Wait, why is there a surprise inspection?
Go now.
Hey, where are you going?
Sir, I heard that we must fold our quilts
into cubes.
-Stop.
-I don't know how to do it.
Stop right there.
Hurry.
Go quickly.
Mr. Fang is behind me.
Go now.
The boy in front.
I told you to stop. Didn't you hear me?
Mr. Fang.
Where is it?
What?
Do you mean this herbal syrup?
Do you want some?
Please just leave it
at the fire hydrant by the door.
It contains anime merchandise.
My parents mustn't know about this.
All right then.
That's it. Thank you, sir.
Bye.
You...
Are you...
Mr. Fang!
Someone passed out in our dorm!
I'm coming.
He left.
I said the instructor had left.
Don't tell me you are feeling shy.
No.
There is dust on you.
Let's get out of here.
Hurry. The instructor is coming.
The instructor is coming.
What's wrong?
Mr. Fang.
I have low...
Low blood pressure.
Low blood sugar.
Mr. Fang,
I have low blood sugar.
Could you please
buy a piece of chocolate for me?
Ferrero will do.
Low blood sugar, is it?
Chocolate is unnecessary.
I have a secret remedy.
What secret remedy?
I think we can save the trouble.
You should sweat and strengthen your body.
What?
That is to say,
you will clean the office
after the training tomorrow.
You can't join the singing contest
until you clean it.
Do you understand?
Ranran,
the wallet you found on campus yesterday
was actually mine.
Thank you so much.
What did you call me?
Ranran.
A nickname for Gu Ran.
It's friendly to use nicknames.
My new friends in my class
already call me Zaizai.
By the way,
are you close with Zhang Lurang,
who is in your class?
Just so-so.
I see.
Then are you two friends?
Or did you two just meet?
We've known each other since birth.
That's a long time.
Then you must know him well.
Yes.
But I think...
I'll just be honest with you, Ranran.
Zhang Lurang was late yesterday
and pretended to be from our class.
He's not honest at all.
I think he's problematic.
Is that so?
Yes, I saw it with my eyes.
By the way, Ranran,
do you know that you are famous?
But Zhang Lurang is the most popular
in the online forum.
I don't agree with that.
Were you hiding
because you kept your phone too?
This.
Let me keep it for you.
I'll keep this and my phone
in the cabinet.
I assure you it's safe.
We don't have strict inspections
in the girls' dorms.
Don't worry. I'll keep it safe.
Thank you,
Su Zaizai.
He knows my name!
Don't bother looking.
You're staying until you finish cleaning.
Sir.
Come in.
Go away.
You stepped on my foot.
Sir,
the singing contest is about to start.
Can they...
Sir, the singing contest
is a group activity.
We must join.
Yes, we're team players.
What did I just tell you?
We can't leave until we're done.
Sir, can Zhang Lurang help us
clean the office?
It will take forever
if it's just the two of us.
Are you willing to do it?
I...
Lurang.
I'll do it.
Everyone, we have ten minutes left.
I just discussed this with Ms. Zhang.
We'll have an individual match
with Class 1.
Which of you would like to sing?
Singing in front of everyone?
That would be so awkward.
I won't do it.
Does no one want to sing?
You are already in high school.
Why are you still so shy?
Does nobody want to volunteer
and set a good example?
No?
Say my name.
What?
I want to sing. Say my name.
Su Zaizai!
-Su Zaizai!
I feel so shy about it.
Then I'll sing a song.
I'm going to sing "Secret."
This song
is for Gu Ran in Class 1.
What's happening?
A girl from Class 9 wants to sing for you.
And it's "Secret."
This is not much of a secret, is it?
Gu Ran, sing along.
-Gu Ran, join in!
Why are you still sitting here? Stand up.
Well, she made the first move, right?
I shouldn't reject her.
I guess
I'll sing along.
Is he Gu Ran?
Where should we start singing?
It's pouring now.
Let's shelter from the rain first.
Wait, don't go.
Let me sing first.
-Zaizai, let's go.
-Don't go yet.
I got the wrong person.
-Let me sing first.
-His name isn't Gu Ran.
Forget about it. It's raining. Let's go.
-Hey, Zaizai!
-Let me sing.
Come on.
It's raining so heavily.
Gu Ran?
Is that your name?
You already know that.
There's no need to pretend.
What a coincidence.
The rain.
The shelter.
An encounter.
A secret.
It was planned out.
Meticulously planned out.
You...
Did you do it on purpose?
What?
It's so obvious.
There are so many people. How did I...
I already told you.
I can tell.
You want to take advantage of me.
It's so obvious.
Hey.
Since you left, don't come back in.
There is no space left.
-That's right.
-Return to your dorm now.
Wait, I was there just now.
I get it now.
You are feeling shy, aren't you?
I'm leaving.
Zhang Lurang.
Sorry, I...
So his name is Zhang Lurang.
The person I encountered in the rain,
met under the stairs, and wanted to know
has always been Zhang Lurang.
But I kept calling him Ranran.
He must think I'm an idiot.
Don't worry.
Zhang Lurang seems reasonable,
unlike Gu Ran.
Actually, it's all Gu Ran's fault.
If he hadn't pretended to be Zhang Lurang,
we wouldn't have made such a mistake.
I already got it wrong.
What should I do?
We happen to be standing guard soon.
Why don't you ask him out and explain?
Gu Ran is with him.
Leave him to me.
Name a time and I'll bury him in advance.
I'm sure he won't want to see me.
That's not true.
I'll arrange the storyline for you.
When you first saw Zhang Lurang,
did you call him an idiot for no reason?
When you two left from under the stairs,
did you call him out
and say he was problematic?
Yes.
There you go.
Think about it.
If someone repeatedly insulted you,
would you put up with it?
You would be eager to see this person
and scold them to their face.
How did you know he scolded me?
What?
I'm sorry.
-Just now, I...
-Zhang Lurang.
Come on. This way.
Run if it's raining.
Idiot.
Maybe he was praising you.
It's okay.
Jiangjiang, this is so scary.
The instructor said
this base had been abandoned for years.
I guess so.
I don't know if anyone has been
to the location that we're guarding.
The grass is so messy.
There isn't even a light.
Jiangjiang.
I think I heard a baby crying.
Zaizai, it's all your imagination.
It's not that scary.
How about this, Zaizai?
I'll fetch two flashlights
from the equipment room.
You'll feel more secure with a light.
Then I'll go with you.
One of us has to be here
so we can explain
if an instructor checks on us.
All right.
How about this?
I'll teach you how not to be afraid.
How?
Clear all the random thoughts
from your mind.
Just bear one thing in mind.
Building 1 is up ahead.
In front of Building 1
is Zhang Lurang.
I feel a little cold.
It's warmer if we stand closer.
It's summer right now.
I feel cold in my heart.
Are you scared?
Nonsense!
That's for kids.
Lurang.
I think there is something weird
about this base.
The power went out.
Wait. Where are you going?
I'll get flashlights
from the equipment room.
Let's go. I'll go with you.
Then you go.
What's wrong?
Are you afraid to go?
What? Me?
Stop kidding.
I used to watch horror movies
to fall asleep.
Let me tell you.
I can calmly finish three math papers
in a haunted house.
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm going.
I'm really going.
Don't be afraid. I'll be right back.
Zhang Lurang.
Good evening.
Are you not calling me Ranran anymore?
That was a misunderstanding.
Are you here alone?
Do you need me to protect you?
Are you sure?
Behind you.
Behind me?
What is it?
I'm afraid to look!
It's a leaf.
A leaf.
Didn't you say you would protect me?
We can protect each other.
It's quite windy tonight, isn't it?
I brought the PSP
that you asked me to keep.
Here.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I also have to apologize to you.
I previously called you an idiot
at the corner store.
Sorry for that.
It's all right.
That won't do.
I learn from my mistakes.
Anyway, I also called you an idiot.
You did a good job.
I think you are so courageous
when you scold others.
I see.
Do you know it's emotional abuse
to respond so brusquely?
How can you bear treating me like this?
Classmates should be friendly.
STORAGE ROOM
Is this the equipment room?
What happened?
Don't joke with me.
I just got locked inside.
It's not scary at all.
The wind
is quite strong.
Luckily, I was the one who came here.
If it were Zhang Lurang,
he would be scared to death.
Hey!
Is anyone outside?
I'm locked inside!
Is anybody there?
Hello?
What was that sound?
STORAGE ROOM
Nobody is inside.
Hey, shine that somewhere else!
I'm a living person.
Who are you?
I'm a new student
in military training.
I got locked inside.
-It's you.
Why isn't she back yet?
It has been a while since my friend
went to the equipment room.
I wonder if something happened.
I want to go and look for her.
The equipment room?
Are you going alone?
Yes.
But if I leave you alone here,
will you be okay?
Will you be afraid?
It's okay.
I'll be right back. Wait for me here.
Do you want me to get you out?
Fine. Give me a reason.
If you can convince me, I'll save you.
Okay, fine.
I'll give you my QQ number when I get out.
All right?
Are you out of your mind?
Then what else do you want?
I'm a man of principles.
Please just help me.
Since we've met, it must be fate,
right?
Hey, don't go!
Should I break in with my hands
if I don't call for help?
Or could it be
that you are afraid?
I'm afraid?
Impossible.
Just go.
It's pretty dark up ahead.
If you are afraid, you can call my name.
My name will give you power.
Hey!
Wait a second.
I suddenly remembered something.
What if you don't come back?
If you leave now,
I'll tell others you locked me up
once I get out.
How can you be so shameless?
I was born like this.
How about this?
Stay here for a while.
When the instructor comes by for a patrol,
he will save us.
Save you, not me, okay?
I can't believe you.
Your name is Jiang Jia, right?
So what?
Jiang Jia.
What now?
Nothing.
I'm just making sure you're still here.
I don't think someone will come.
I should find someone
to open the door.
Hey!
I suddenly remember
that the door isn't firmly locked.
Why don't you try to break it open?
Break it open?
Yes.
It's possible though.
But I'm a girl.
It may be too much for me
to break the door open.
If I don't get anything out of this,
it might be...
Tell me.
I haven't decided yet. You owe me one.
Okay.
Deal.
A kind reminder.
Step back.
Hey.
If you can't do it, why don't you...
It hurts so much.
I don't believe it.
Forget it, all right?
Step back!
Why don't we just...
Let's go.
Okay.
Who is it?
I won't turn around.
I will never turn around.
Please!
Don't catch me!
Su Zaizai.
Please spare me!
It's me.
Zhang Lurang, I ran into a ghost.
I ran into something as well.
A coward.
So it's a cat.
I thought it was a ghost.
Well, I'm not a coward.
I'm usually brave.
Just now, I...
That was to blame.
Zaizai,
why are you guys here?
I was about to go and look for you.
I thought something happened to you.
What would happen to me?
-Gu Ran just...
-Hey!
The instructor will check on us soon.
Let's go.
Hurry.
I'll tell you when we get back.
How much longer do we have to stand here?
The instructor might not notice
if one of us is missing.
That's possible.
But I'll report you if you leave.
The instructor might let me leave
after seeing how impartial I am.
Gu Ran, Zhang Lurang.
Is it cooked?
I don't think so.
We can eat it if it's soft.
It's hot.
I wish it were cooked already.
I bought these from an old man
selling roasted sweet potatoes
beyond the fence.
He was about to leave.
Only raw ones were left.
It's edible at least. Don't be so picky.
Will these cicadas
ever cease chirping?
How did they offend you by chirping?
I've been holding a grudge against them
since I was little.
At that time,
I was about five or six years old.
I was tricked
into catching a jar full of cicadas,
only to find out
those were all cockroaches.
Who was so mischievous?
He's sitting right next to you.
Did you really do that?
I don't remember.
I feel
that all those fun things in our childhood
are gone.
I agree.
I used to see fireflies all the time.
Zhang Lurang,
what did you do for fun as a kid?
Study.
His family is strict with him.
It always took me a lot of effort
to get him out of his house.
I see.
The moon tonight
is beautiful.
Is it any different?
It's different.
Zhang Lurang, what do you think?
Yes.
What are you doing?
Let's go. Quick!
-Hurry, go.
-Hurry.
Don't run. Stop!
My biggest gain
from the military training that year
is that I seem
to be less afraid of ghosts.
Maybe it is
because a quiet and arrogant guy
came into my heart
and wouldn't leave.
This is how things work in the world.
Beyond the mountains is the sea.
At the end of the night is light.
UNYIELDING, COURAGE, STRENGTH
Things that are not so cute
may leave a print in your memory
when you turn around.
Adults always say
there are too many uncertainties in youth.
But it's because of these uncertainties,
which may bring us surprises or horrors,
that we would
look forward to every new day
as we never did before
at the age of 16.
This is the last day that we stand guard.
I don't think he will notice
if I include him in the shot.
Who is there?
I'm doomed.
I'm not a coward.
At least when I stand before you,
I'm the bravest one.